<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WC22 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WC22 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2022 CSR</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-1&#34;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;qatar-v-ecuador&#34;&gt;Qatar V Ecuador&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../e5c7a415cca84837cbe6a0ff753672c2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;e5c7a415cca84837cbe6a0ff753672c2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably the worst opening match in the history of the whole tournament. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I really thought Qatar could give a match against Ecuador. This is also the first time ever in the history of the World Cup that the host nation has lost its first match. Even Russia had a better game than this lot. Ecuador hardly broke a sweat in this game. The second half was really just chilling from them. Qatar was happy to give them the possession in the opening stages and Valencia scored the opener after around 3 minutes but it was ruled out by VAR for offside(Highly Highly controversial but was reasoned out by the fact half his leg..was..in an offside position. God these rules seem dumb). However, it would be justice served when the goalie pulled down Valencia clean through on goal for a clear penalty which was put away perfectly. The second goal was brilliantly crafted though. A really great cross from Preciado to the head of Valencia and a good header. Qatar&amp;rsquo;s best chance was probably with the last play in the first half when they managed to somehow get an unmarked header and he completely fluffed it. That probably would have made the second half more interesting but they weren&amp;rsquo;t good enough to do that so it became a very dull second half. Given the fact they have Senegal(Even without Mane they are still decent enough) and the Netherlands, I don&amp;rsquo;t have many hopes for them honestly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;qatar&#34;&gt;Qatar:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../qatar.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;qatar.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ecuador&#34;&gt;Ecuador:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ecuador.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ecuador.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Serbia</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_serbia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_serbia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---serbia&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Serbia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhVYGPCWAAAWfmA.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhVYGPCWAAAWfmA.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a group that contains Brazil, Cameroon and Switzerland. Honestly, I think they and Switzerland are genuine contenders for the second spot. Those 2 teams can cause an upset too. My lineup is solely based on their values so bear with me. In goal, a Milinkovic Savic could be trusted or Rajkovic. In defense, it&amp;rsquo;s a back 3 of the likes of Pavlovic, Milenkovic, Erakovic mostly with the usual Veljkovic injured with an unknown return date so let&amp;rsquo;s see if he&amp;rsquo;ll be back. In midfield it&amp;rsquo;s a set of 4. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.transfermarkt.com/sergej-milinkovi%C4%87-savi%C4%87/profil/spieler/266302&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SMS&lt;/a&gt;
 should mostly start. Maybe alongside him, Racic could play or the likes of Ilic as well. Kostic will mostly for sure be at LM and Zivkovic at the right. Captain Tadic will be the lone CAM there. Upfront, it is a front 2 with Vlahovic and Mitrovic(He will mostly be back in time for the WC).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_serbia.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_serbia.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Argentina</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_arg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_arg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---argentina&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Argentina&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhSqitzX0AAhtan.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhSqitzX0AAhtan.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright. Copa America winners. Winners of the Finallissima. Their team looks amazing actually. I genuinely hope they do another 2014. In goal, Emi Martinez is a lock-in. In defense, Lisandro Martinez should definitely play after his amazing start at United. Alongside him, Romero or Otamendi should be good enough. In the fullback positions, I would perhaps go Tagliafico and Montiel. In midfield, Paredes or Palacios for the CDM role. Ahead of him, De Paul is for sure to start. I feel beside him I would trust Enzo Fernandez ahead of Papu Gomez. On the wings, Di Maria or Alvarez for LW and Messi at RW. Dybala was said to be missing the WC but he has been picked in the squad. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if he will play but it would be nice to see him in the as soon as possible. In ST, Lautaro Martinez is for sure on lock there. He has been amazing for Argentina so far and he will be crucial for them in this WC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_arg.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_arg.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Spain</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_spain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---spain&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Spain&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhR8bEfWIAEWo5h.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhR8bEfWIAEWo5h.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of controversy from Enrique with De Gea being left out of the provisional 55-man squad. My feeling is that the relationship severed after Euro 2020. He relies on playing well from the back including the goalie. Even though De Gea has relatively improved under Ten Hag in that aspect, he still has a long way to go. Unai Simon is already good at that aspect. So are Robert Sanchez and Raya. Another omission is Ramos who will not be going to his 5th World Cup like Messi and Ronaldo which is sad. I think there are young and good players who can do the job well. Guillamon who is a young CDM is actually named as a defender which is interesting. Fullbacks are mostly Gaya and Carvajal. In midfield, he could either go Rodri but he does seem to trust Busquets as well. I would go with Rodri for the form. In the center, Soler and Koke could mostly be the ones he goes for but Pedri and Gavi could very well start a game or two here and there instead of them. Maybe not as a duo yet but one of them along with Soler or Koke. I think my pick is Soler and Pedri. To the attack, Fati and Torres could fight for the LW spot. In the RW spot, Nico Williams is going to a major tournament which is amazing for him. I think Asensio, Sarabia, and Pino are also rather good options. In ST, he only has Morata and no Moreno which is weird. Torres and Fati could also be at ST but let&amp;rsquo;s see how that goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_spain.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_spain.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Netherlands</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_dutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_dutch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---netherlands&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Netherlands&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../3e8ea2cb19f22724972dad132dc4423b.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;3e8ea2cb19f22724972dad132dc4423b.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, I am liking the look of this squad. This is the first World Cup for the likes of Van Dijk and Pasveer(Take a bow. Being the first choice for Ajax at 39). Van Gaal has really made a turnaround after that spell with Manchester United. The system is likely to be a 3-back system which has worked out well for them. In goal, Pasveer could be starting in goal but Bijlow is OTW as well so hoping he could have a game or so as well. At the back, you can&amp;rsquo;t look past De Ligt, Van Dijk and Timber. The options are Ake and De Vrij. On the wings maybe Malacia and Frimpong could be trusted. If not Malacia, Blind could be present as well. In midfield, it is likely to be a 3 with a CAM. Frenkie De Jong will mostly start since he has been consistent for FC Barcelona. Along with him maybe De Roon or Koopmeiners can be expected. In CAM, I&amp;rsquo;d rather have Berghuis or Klaasen. Maybe the likes of Xavi Simons could have a start. Up front is usually 2 strikers. One of them has got to be Cody Gakpo after the season he&amp;rsquo;s had in PSV. Alongside him, the options are Bergwijn, L. De Jong or even Weghorst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_dutch.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_dutch.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Senegal</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_senegal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_senegal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---senegal&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Senegal&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhRonSNXEAEIaKw.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhRonSNXEAEIaKw.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Left: Goalkeepers, Midfielders, Manager/Coach
Right: Defenders, Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well well well. This is an interesting selection from the coach. Sadio Mane will in fact be going to the World Cup despite being injured. They are hoping he will make a comeback during the tournament at the very least. With the Netherlands being the only possible threat, I think they have what it takes to finish second at least. In goal, we can&amp;rsquo;t look past Mendy but given his bad form for Chelsea(He is second choice now sadly), maybe the coach will trust one of the other two GKs. In defense, Koulibaly is a mainstay and is expected to lead them out after a successful Africa Cup of Nations triumph. Alongside him, it is between Diallo and Cisse. On the right, Formose Mendy is expected to start(Young and OTW) or Sabaly could start as well. On the left, it is between young Ismail Jakobs and the experienced Ballo-Toure. Moving onto midfield, Gueye is expected to hold the midfield alongside Mendy or Kouyate. In the frontline, Diatta could be at CAM. Ismaila Sarr could be a fix at RW. On the left, maybe Jackson could be there instead of Mane and finally up top, you could see Dia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_senegal.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_senegal.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Brazil</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_brazil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_brazil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---brazil&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Brazil&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Fg-ZVsgWQAAz8Wh.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Fg-ZVsgWQAAz8Wh.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guess my fears were true in the end. Fullbacks seem like the only weakness for Brazil here with only Alex Sandro/Alex Telles on the left and Danilo/Dani Alves on the right. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I am happy Alves is somehow there in the lineup but it&amp;rsquo;s seriously weird seeing weak options there compared to literally everywhere else in the team. In goal, I think Ederson would mostly start but Alisson has made many saves but it will be a headache. In defense, you can&amp;rsquo;t look past Marquinhos and Thiago Silva(Valiant Captain). In the fullback position, I would probably start Telles(LB) and Danilo(RB). In midfield, Casemiro deserves the start ahead of Fabinho. Instead of Fred partnering with him, I think Bruno G deserves a shout alongside him. He is on form for Newcastle. He is good physically and can pass around well so I think he deserves a go, ahead of Fred. The attack is where it is a real headache for anyone. How Firmino is not selected ahead of the likes of Richarlison I will never know. What to do when you have so much quality, you have to make tough calls. In attack, Neymar is obviously going to be on the left. Paqueta could be good at CAM and on the right, there are options galore with the likes of Antony, Raphinha, Rodrygo and more. Or Neymar could be shifted to CAM to allow Vini Jr to be LW. At ST, it should definitely be Gabriel Jesus after his great season with Arsenal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_brazil.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_brazil.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - England</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_england/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_england/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---england&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - England&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhNTSa_XEAEHdsM.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhNTSa_XEAEHdsM.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The big one I was actually waiting for. My expectations for Southgate were low but wow he absolutely went even low. Heavy imbalance, too many out-of-form players, some fatigue and dropping people who you would rather build the team around. It&amp;rsquo;s an absolute joke how the FA(Football Association) is allowing this League 1(Tier 3 of English football) coach even manage a bloody NATIONAL TEAM. The worst part of it is they are scared to hire anyone foreign. Anyways, the bottom line is it&amp;rsquo;s sad seeing a golden generation of attacking talent being wasted by a very conservative coach. Alright anymore and this post will be very big so let&amp;rsquo;s decipher the lineup and you bet your top dollar I am doing a best-ever England lineup as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In goal, I am fine with the picks of Pickford, Pope and Ramsdale with Pickford being the de facto starter. At the back I am certain it&amp;rsquo;s a back 3 of Dier, Maguire and Stones. On the left Shaw is mostly a lock and on the right, I would trust Trippier based on his form for Newcastle. Going into midfield, it picks itself with Rice and Bellingham. Going forward, the left will mostly be between Sterling and Rashford. I would trust Rashford on form and Foden or Saka on the right with Kane leading the line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup will look something like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_eng_1.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_eng_1.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are a few things to note:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;White was picked due to injuries to James and Chilwell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only 1 LB and 5 RBs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 CAMs for a formation that does not use a CAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No different CB like Tomori or even Guehi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bellingham only one outside England who is picked&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No James Ward-Prowse despite being in amazing form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kane is tired and his only backup is Wilson. No Toney or Tammy Abraham&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what I would have done:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked Tomori because he is a modern CB to partner Stones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked JWP on his amazing form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked Toney and Abraham along with Wilson and drop people like Grealish and Philips since they have hardly played and one of them was injured for a long time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Switch to a 4 back formation to actually make use of the attacking talent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is how the lineup would look like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_eng_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_eng_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Uruguay</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_uruguay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_uruguay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---uruguay&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Uruguay&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Uruguay_Squad.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;Uruguay_Squad.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So Suarez and Cavani are picked for the squad which is nice to see. One final time seeing that attacking duo probably but with Nunez coming up it&amp;rsquo;s hard to keep them together. In goal, the coach seems to trust Rochet more than Muslera so I would probably do the same. In defense Araujo is a very surprising pick given his expected return is in December if he underwent surgery he could maybe play but we need to wait and see how it develops. Apart from him, Gimenez is a surety alongside probably Caceres and the fullbacks will mostly be Olivera and Varela on the left and right respectively. Olivera and Vina are OTW on the left. In the center of midfield, we can for sure expect Valverde to start given his amazing form for Real Madrid and Bentancur will mostly start alongside him. Vecino and Torreira are present for more defensive options. On the wings, I would really like to see Pellistri on the right. He&amp;rsquo;s OTW along with Canobbio as well who usually can be found starting as well. On the left, you can expect to see probably de la Cruz. In attack, you will most definitely see Suarez and Nunez will start more compared to Cavani I think due to him being younger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_uruguay.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_uruguay.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Portugal</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_portugal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_portugal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---portugal&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Portugal&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232200.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232200.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the left: Goalkeepers and Defenders &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
On the right: Midfielders and Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stacked team. Ronaldo&amp;rsquo;s possible last dance. Isn&amp;rsquo;t in the greatest of form but will be expected to lead this team after their Euro win in 2016 and Nations League win in 2019. They have really good quality everywhere. They will miss Jota through injury but have good players instead of him. Starting at the back Diogo Costa has to start every game because he has been on it for Porto and recently signed a new contract. At the back, Pepe is injured but is picked anyways with no concrete return date. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how that develops. Instead of him, Danilo Pereira can do a job despite him being a CDM. He will be partnering Dias. However, there is a conundrum with the full backs. Dalot has been amazing for United and Cancelo has been no pushover for City either. Mendes is OTW at LB but I think I would rather see Cancelo at LB given that&amp;rsquo;s where he plays for City and Dalot at RB. Plus Dalot will have a game&amp;rsquo;s rest since he is suspended for the game before the tournament. Moving into Midfield we have options for the CDM in William and Palhinha and at CM we have Neves and also OTW in Nunes and Vitinha(Nunes is currently injured but will be back by the WC). Moving to the 3 behind Ronaldo, we have either Bruno or Silva at CAM, Leao or Felix at LW and Silva, Otavio and maybe Joao Mario as well for RW and Ronaldo is mostly going to be immovable at ST but for an option, Andre Silva could be a good option and maybe Felix as a false 9.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_portugal.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_portugal.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>