<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WC22 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WC22 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2022 CSR</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:42:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Poland</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_poland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_poland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---poland&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Poland&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_231935.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_231935.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Order: Goalkeepers, Defenders, Midfielders, Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the likes of Mexico and Argentina in their group here is hoping Lewandowski can do well in possibly his last World Cup. The usual system at play for Poland seems to be a 3 at the back formation so I&amp;rsquo;ll probably be centering my lineup with the same formation. In goal, Szczesny is a mainstay and Dragowski is a young development keeper who can hopefully take over from him. In the defense, the 3 CBs I would trust are Bednarek, Glik and Kiwior. On the left Zalewski seems to be trusted by the coach. He plays for Roma, is young and OTW. On the right, I would probably put my trust in Cash. I mean he decided to join Poland from England for crying out loud. In midfield, Zielinski is a lock-in. On the defensive side, it will probably be Krychowiak and Zurkowski. Up front, we could expect to see Lewandowski and probably between Milik and Piatek. However, Swiderski was starting in their last game against Wales(L). I would rather trust Milik or Piatek but let&amp;rsquo;s see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_poland.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_poland.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Belgium</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_belgium/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_belgium/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---belgium&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Belgium&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232011.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232011.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like I said in my team summary this is a decent squad in general and the one selected for this tournament is no different. This team has been forever named a dark horse but with the sheer quality they have I expected them to do really well at tournaments but they haven&amp;rsquo;t delivered as much as I thought. A 3rd place finish last time in the World Cup is good but not enough. Coming to the team, Courtois is unshakeable in goal. In defense, I would rather see Faes and Theate rather than Vertonghen and Alderweireld. Maybe one of the latter can be started for the experience. Vertonghen is injured however so it seems like Alderweireld will start mostly. Debast is a young CB also who could be OTW at 19. He played in Belgium&amp;rsquo;s last match(1-0 L to Netherlands). Onana is another OTW. Young CDM and a decent season for Everton. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how he develops along with either Witsel or Tielemans. On the left, it is between Castagne and Carrasco but I would trust Carrasco because of his work rate. Another one for the LM option could be Trossard who has had a great season for Brighton and deserves a run-out. On the right, Meunier is ever present and Doku is OTW who is young and can offer an attacking option. The 2 CAMs in this formation are 2 mainstays: De Bruyne and Eden Hazard. Up front is the conundrum. You have Lukaku who is the usual option or Batshuayi. You have Openda who is OTW: Young and promising and also De Ketelaere who has had a good start at AC Milan and can play either at CAM or ST.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_belgium.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_belgium.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Morocco</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_morocco/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_morocco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---morocco&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Morocco&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_231956.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_231956.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The order is: Goalkeepers, Defenders, Midfielders, Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an okay team in my opinion. With the likes of Belgium and Croatia, it is an uphill battle for Morocco. Ziyech is selected despite playing fewer games and being out of form for Chelsea but I get the reasoning. You sometimes have to have your most talented players.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In goal, we have Bono who is a half-decent keeper for Sevilla and is no slouch. In defense, the fullbacks are sorted with Hakimi and Mazraoui on the left and right respectively. I hope Hakimi can train to be an inverted fullback even more because both he and Mazraoui are young and really good talents. In the middle, you have captain Saiss and the second CB is between Dari and Aguerd. In midfield, Amrabat is ever present at CDM and a combo of Ounahi and Harit is interesting to see(Harit - OTW). In attack, Ziyech is set at RW and up front, En-Nesyri is a good option and Boufal is a constant presence at LW. Ez Abde is an interesting one because although he is OTW, he is injured currently and I have no news on when he&amp;rsquo;ll be back but if he does get fit during the cup, we can hopefully see him in some games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The probable lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_morocco.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_morocco.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Switzerland</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_swi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_swi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---switzerland&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Switzerland&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232107.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232107.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Credit to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goal.com/en/lists/switzerland-2022-world-cup-squad/bltab6e9f29cd83f728#csbf9b00ac759d0aff&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Goal.com&lt;/a&gt;
 for the simplification&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../1e5296fd12c6801b635f0269cfbf54fa.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;1e5296fd12c6801b635f0269cfbf54fa.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../346916016d96f2c4383ff762f9dab888.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;346916016d96f2c4383ff762f9dab888.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../d81bc7f50be37672dcd92522c1261afb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;d81bc7f50be37672dcd92522c1261afb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../8efc69542bdf6a9b45c9a49126c4e6b0.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;8efc69542bdf6a9b45c9a49126c4e6b0.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fairly decent time in the last Euros where they managed to knock out the current WC defending champions France on penalties. The squad is fairly decent with a few young options up front like Okafor and Embolo and a GK in Kobel. Sommer is injured but will be back in time for their first fixture maybe it could be time to trust in Kobel a little more. In defense, Mbabu is not present as he is not in form at Fulham. In the center, it&amp;rsquo;s Akanji and Schar with Widmer at RB and Ricardo Rodriguez at LB. The usual formation for them is a 4-2-3-1. The midfield pivot would be mostly Xhaka(Amazing form for Arsenal lately) and the second one can be between Zakaria and Freuler. Moving forward we have Big Shaq at RW and in CAM Sow has been used there so expect to maybe see him there again there and it is mostly Vargas on the left. Up at ST, we have Breel Embolo who has I think nailed down his spot there. Really good pace and is a decent finisher. On the bench, they have a good target man in Seferovic as well and one to watch in Okafor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_swi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_swi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - USA</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_usa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---usa&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - USA&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../USA_Roster.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;USA_Roster.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the days of seeing only Clint Dempsey and Landon Donovan, I have got to say I am liking the look of this USA team honestly. A good keeper in Matt Turner. Good defense in Robinson, Dest, Scally, Yedlin and Zimmerman. There is a decent midfield in Mckennie, Acosta, Aaronson and Adams. The forward line is also really good with the LeBron James of Soccer(C. Pulisic - LW), Gio Reyna who is doing well for Dortmund. A few ones to watch include Ferreira and Tim Weah.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One point is Mckennie is injured currently and maybe he could be back in time for the first game I think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think a 4-2-3-1 would work with this USA side but a 4-3-3 is also a good shout. This is how those 2 formations would look like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_usa_1.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_usa_1.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_usa_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_usa_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Cameroon</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_cameroon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_cameroon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---cameroon&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Cameroon&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232032.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232032.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fairly normal squad you could say. I am excited to see how Choupo-Moting will perform after being in form for Bayern but I don&amp;rsquo;t know if the coach will play him ahead of Aboubakar cause he is the captain of the team. Maybe he may play at LW but they already got Toko-Ekambi there and Mbuemo is a lock-in at RW. In midfield, the likes of Zambo Anguissa will be vital in shielding the defense. He has had a good season with Napoli so hoping he does well. Ntcham is one of the CM ahead of him along with maybe Hongla or Kunde. In defense, we have the experience of N&amp;rsquo;Koulou and youth in Wooh. In GK it&amp;rsquo;s for sure going to be Onana(Although I would like to see the third GK play to see the commentator struggle).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think the lineup will look something like this. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if this is how they usually play but this is the best from what they have got:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_cameroon.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_cameroon.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EMCM - Eric Maxim Choup-Moting&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Croatia</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_croatia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 22:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_croatia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---croatia&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Croatia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232117.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232117.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just to make sure the spaces are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goalkeepers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Defenders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Midfielders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WC Finalists last time out. Looking at the squad strength, they have a good midfield and a fairly decent target man in Kramaric(Despite my personal feeling about him). Gvardiol at the back should be OTW. I&amp;rsquo;m guessing he will be paired with Lovren who isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly the fastest currently so maybe you can get at him. In the fullbacks, you have Sosa for the LB position and Vida and Juranovic at RB. In midfield, the 3 picks themselves: Brozovic(CDM), Kovacic and Modric(CM). Up front, we could mostly see Vlasic and Perisic with Kramaric(ST)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup would look as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_croatia.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_croatia.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - France</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_france/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_france/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---france&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - France&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_225130.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_225130.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, defending champs. Strong squad. The only thing I am probably worried about is the lack of fullbacks with only Pavard and Theo Hernandez. No Ferland Mendy which is surprising. Maybe it could mean Deschamps is trying to push the 3 at the back system I think. Glad to see Varane in the squad still despite him missing the first game as a United fan. The midfield will be without Pogba and Kante who are very influential in general but in their stead, I am hoping Camavinga and Tchouameni will step up. They have been developing really well at Real Madrid so let u see how they do. The forward line will be Mbappe obviously. Along with him, I think Benzema would be great to have as Mbappe has said he would work well in a 2 ST formation. So keeping that in mind, if Deschamps wanted the 3 back formation,  it would probably look like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_france_1.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_france_1.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we looked at a different type of formation then this could be worth a shout:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_france_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_france_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group H - Summary</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-h/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-h&#34;&gt;Group H&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quite possibly the last dance for Ronaldo he isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly in the greatest of form but will most definitely be leading out this team in a tough group with the likes of Uruguay and so on. Unlucky that Diogo Jota is injured for this tournament. The attack is really well stacked anyways with the likes of Neto and Felix. The midfield has the likes of Bruno, Silva, Rafa Leao and Neves. The youngsters to watch could be Vitinha and M. Nunes. In defense, we have a solid group of players in Dias, Pepe, Cancelo and Dalot. Mendes is a young LB to watch. GK has some interesting ones like Patricio, Jose Sa and a younger keeper in Costa. Hope he could get some games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ghana&#34;&gt;Ghana&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ghana has a good team. I don&amp;rsquo;t know much about the keeper but they have quality in other areas. The fact that they&amp;rsquo;re paired with Uruguay after what happened in &lt;a href=&#34;http://news.bbc.co.uk/sport2/hi/football/world_cup_2010/8785140.stm&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;2010&lt;/a&gt;
 is going to be interesting to see. In defense, you can see the likes of Lamptey(OTW - One to Watch), Salisu(OTW) and Amartey. The midfield has a good CDM in Thomas Partey and a good CM/CAM in Kudus(Ajax OTW) and attack, they have the Ayew brothers obviously. Another youngster to watch could be Felix Afena Gyan if he&amp;rsquo;s selected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;uruguay&#34;&gt;Uruguay&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good young talents have arrived in Uruguay and hoping to see them all come good. GK is obviously Muslera. The defense has the likes of Gimenez and Araujo(Man&amp;rsquo;s injured unfortunately). Midfield has really good quality with Fede Valverde(Absolutely on fire for Real Madrid), Pellistri(Hopefully has a good tournament. Young and OTW), Torreira and Vecino. In attack, we have got the likes of Nunez. I am not sure if both Suarez and Cavani will be selected. Maxi Gomez is another one who is fairly decent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;korea&#34;&gt;Korea&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Known famously for knocking Germany out with a wonderful performance, Son will be hoping to have a good tournament this time around. I only know probably 3 players overall. Kim Min-Jae will hopefully be a rock at the back with his form for Napoli. Hwang Hee-Chan and Son up front is a really good threat. With the quality of the other teams, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to say how well they could do. Then again they knocked out Germany so you never know.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group G - Summary</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-g/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-g/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-g&#34;&gt;Group G&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;brazil&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can Brazil finally make sure to win another World Cup after 2002? Can Neymar banish the ghosts of the critics by winning a WC finally? These are the few questions that I am most certainly thinking about when coming to Brazil. I would really like to see the South American teams giving a tough fight to the European teams. In the last world cup, even with Neymar they went out on a whimper in the knockouts which was disappointing, to say the least. Now hopefully Tite can get the absolute best out of this team. In goal, it&amp;rsquo;s a toss-up between Alisson and Ederson. In defense, we have the rock-solid pair of Marquinhos and Thiago Silva. Fullbacks are my only worry with this team with options like Danilo, Telles and Sandro. Midfield is also really solid with the likes of Casemiro, Fred, Bruno G(Having a stonking season for Newcastle) and Fabinho. The attack is absolutely stacked with obviously Neymar, Gabriel Jesus, Rodrygo, Antony, Martinelli, Vini Jr. God that attack is good if it gels together which the coach has to manage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;serbia&#34;&gt;Serbia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This group low-key has teams that should probably not be underestimated apart from Brazil only. I don&amp;rsquo;t know anyone in particular in their defense apart from their goalie(Dmitrovic). Midfield is quite decent with the likes of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sofascore.com/player/sergej-milinkovic-savic/331447&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SMS&lt;/a&gt;
, Tadic, Kostic, Gudelj and Racic. The attack has options in Mitrovic and Jovic. Vlahovic is a doubt due to his injury so we don&amp;rsquo;t know if the manager will pick him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;switzerland&#34;&gt;Switzerland&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think this team on their day with the players they have could be really good and finish 2nd in this group. They had a wonderful Euros by beating France in a penalty shootout. Sommer is the mainstay at GK with a younger one in the wings in Kobel. Defense will mostly be Rodriguez, Akanji, Schar and Mbaby which is alright. Midfield has the likes of Xhaka(In good form for Arsenal), Zakaria, Freuler. The attack is obviously incomplete with the Big Shaq(X. Shaquiri - RW) and Embolo and led by the imposing Seferovic. I&amp;rsquo;ll be keeping an eye on Noah Okafor if he gets selected for sure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cameroon&#34;&gt;Cameroon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If Eto&amp;rsquo;o was the main player back then, they have pretty much an equal replacement for him now: Eric Maxim Choupo-Moting. As much as I laugh at him, he has absolutely been on it for Bayern this season and deserves the call-up. He will be a big threat based on form. Along with him could also be Mbuemo as well on the right as a threat. Midfield has the likes of Toko-Ekambi and Frank Anguissa which is really good. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know anybody major in defense apart from the GK(Andre Onana).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>