<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Categories on WC22 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/categories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Categories on WC22 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
        <atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Group F - Summary</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-f/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-f&#34;&gt;Group F&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;belgium&#34;&gt;Belgium&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Belgium, one problem I have always found is their defense somehow always lets them down and with the guard being Vertonghen(35), Alderweireld(33) and Boyata(31) I am not surprised. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be as big an issue now due to the rise of young CBs such as Faes(24) and Theate(22) combined with the experience of Denayer(27) should be a really good backline for Courtois now. The midfield is absolutely packed with the likes of De Bruyne, Tielemans, Witsel and so on with young talents like Onana(21) for the CDM role. On the wings, we have the ever present Eden Hazard, his brother Thorgan, Carrasco, Mertens along with young talents like De Ketelaere(ST) and Openda(ST). Will be keeping an eye on those talents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;canada&#34;&gt;Canada&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First WC since 1986. Phonzy(A. Davies - LB) and his men have a big task on their hands qualifying ahead of the likes of Croatia and Belgium who have pretty decent firepower on their side. Davies is also expected to be &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.transfermarkt.com/alphonso-davies-quot-i-will-be-100-for-the-world-cup-quot-canada-back-for-first-time-since-1986/view/news/413584&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;back&lt;/a&gt;
 just before the WC starts which is great news and will be on the left side of the defense. Another talent I want to keep an eye on is Jonathan David(ST). The young striker is doing numbers for Lille in France but this WC could be a good way to gauge his play style and see how he works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morocco don&amp;rsquo;t have a bad squad but with the likes of Belgium and Croatia, we don&amp;rsquo;t know if they can manage it. They have good players. Starting from defense they have Bono who plays for Sevilla and half-decent CBs in Saïss and Aguerd(Plays for West Ham) and the fullbacks have the quality of Hakimi and Mazraoui. The midfield is pretty standard with the likes of Amrabat, Boufal, Harit(One to keep an eye on) and the attack has the likes of Ziyech, En-Nesyri so it is not half bad. Let&amp;rsquo;s see if they can give tough competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finalists from the previous WC, Croatia won a load of hearts from that tournament for sure and they have a really good team to push Belgium and go through. In goal will probably be Livakovic. Gvardiol at the back is one to watch along with maybe Lovren. In midfield, the likes of Modric Kovacic and Brozovic are really solid. Up front, they have the likes of Kramaric(Man made me furious in a FIFA 22 Career mode I was doing and I dropped him). Brekalo and Pasalic could be good wing options maybe along with Vlasic.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group E - Summary</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-e/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-e&#34;&gt;Group E&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;spain&#34;&gt;Spain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spain has such a promising team in midfield and attack for sure. It all starts at the back with a great modern keeper in Unai Simon with Carvajal and Gaya at full-backs mostly and Torres and Laporte(if picked which is pretty certain). Midfield is amazing quality with Pedri and Gavi and Rodri holding fort over there. Pedri and Gavi are the ones to watch. Guillamón(CDM) is another one who is young and can play both CDM and CB. In attack, there are quite a few options in Ferran Torres, Sarabia and more with Morata or maybe Moreno at ST. The young players to watch here are Fati(LW), Nico Williams(RW), Yéremy Pino(RW) if they are selected. They can go far with Enrique.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;costa-rica&#34;&gt;Costa Rica&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keylor Navas has a huge mountain to climb here sadly cause this group is mighty tough with Spain and Germany. Maybe they could give Japan a fight but apart from that, I have no idea if they could do well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;germany&#34;&gt;Germany&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victims of the defending champions curse. They had a really solid team last time out but didn&amp;rsquo;t go beyond the group stages. Now they are looking much more dangerous under Hansi Flick. They have a good set of young players in Musiala, Bella-Kotchap(Who is pretty decent in the PL so far) and Moukoko. Hoping to see them go far in the tournament.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;japan&#34;&gt;Japan&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember the old days when Japan had players like Shinji Kagawa and Keisuke Honda who would absolutely ball out for Japan. Now there is a new wave of talent for these guys and I&amp;rsquo;m excited for it. The attack has players like Minamino, Kamada and Furuhashi. The wings are dangerous with the likes of Take Kubo and Ritsu Doan. In defense, we have the likes of Tomiyasu and Yoshida. Itakura is also someone who could be decent for them. There is a good bundle of talent here. Let&amp;rsquo;s see&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group D - Summary</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-d/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-d&#34;&gt;Group D&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Defending champions. Will the World Cup curse strike for the 4th time? (Victims include: Italy, Spain, and Germany). They have got an amazing team. In defense, although Varane will be a big miss, they have got the likes of Koundé, Konaté, Upamecano, Saliba, Lucas, Theo and Pavard. In Midfield, Kante is a huge miss but there is quality again in Tchouaméni and Camavinga who are promising and are ones to watch for. Paul Pogba can still do the business for France and can hopefully do good after coming back from injury(&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/FabrizioRomano/status/1587123217201713152&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Immediate Jinx&lt;/a&gt;
). Diaby and Guendouzi are also youngsters to keep an eye on. Dembele has had a massive resurrection at Barca so expect to see more of him. There is just a lot of quality to cover. Mbappe will always be the main man up top for the French. One thing is: Will we see Ballon D&amp;rsquo;Or winner Benzema at the WC? Time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;australia&#34;&gt;Australia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know their players as much apart from Mat Ryan(GK) and Mooy(CM). They are mostly going to be fighting with Tunisia for 3rd and 4th mostly. They arrived here by beating Peru via a penalty shootout(after a 0-0 draw)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;denmark&#34;&gt;Denmark&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These guys balled out in the Euros. A semi-final appearance in that tournament. They have got the team to finish comfortably in 2nd place in this group. Eriksen is a man reborn ever since the &lt;a href=&#34;https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020/posts/day-1/&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;bad news&lt;/a&gt;
 from the Euros and he will be a pivotal part once again for the Danish. Kasper Schmeichel is once again a great leader to have and a good keeper. Kjaer and Christensen will be vital at the heart of the defense. Maele and Damsgaard are good on the wings with Damsgaard hoping to back up his great Euros performance with another one here. Up front, the options are fairly decent in Dolberg and Poulsen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tunisia&#34;&gt;Tunisia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only know 2 players here in Khazri and Mejbri. Excited to see Mejbri if he does get called up which I hope he does. The last match wasn&amp;rsquo;t a great one: losing 5-1 to Brazil and getting a player sent off. Apart from that, another notable player is Skhiri who plays in the Bundesliga for Koln.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group C - Summary</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 19:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-c/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-c&#34;&gt;Group C&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last dance for Messi and Di Maria for sure will be bittersweet to watch as a Messi fan so I am planning to soak every moment. Messi has finally hit his GOAT stride at PSG so he is in really great form heading into the WC. Dybala&amp;rsquo;s injury will certainly be a big blow for them but they have capable players in Di Maria, Gomez and Alvarez. A solid defense led by Martinez in goal and Lisandro Martinez who has had a fantastic start to his United career. A really good midfield with the likes of Paredes, De Paul(Messi&amp;rsquo;s personal bodyguard), Lo Celso and more and an attack with La Pulga Lautaro should make Argentina at least go further in the knockouts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;youngters-to-watch-perezrb-alvarezst-palacioscdm&#34;&gt;Youngters to watch: Perez(RB), Alvarez(ST), Palacios(CDM)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;saudi-arabia&#34;&gt;Saudi Arabia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hardly know players from this team. All I can bring is their WC 2018 form where they finished 3rd after beating an Egypt side who had a half-fit Mo Salah. Apart from that at the time of writing this they still have a friendly against Croatia on the 16th of November so maybe that&amp;rsquo;s one match to keep an eye on to see how they will play but in all honesty, they have really tough competition in Mexico, Argentina and even Poland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;mexico&#34;&gt;Mexico&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Round of 16 in the last WC. Same record as Sweden(2-0-1). They have their version of Neuer in Ochoa. Their attack is their main threat with the likes of Raúl Jiménez, Hirving Lozano. They have some promising youngsters in &lt;strong&gt;Giménez(ST)&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Alvarez(CDM)&lt;/strong&gt;. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how they hold up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;poland&#34;&gt;Poland&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last time at the WC for people like Lewandowski, Szczęsny and a few more. Lewandowski will always be a starter and Milik is an option off the bench or as a winger. Zieliński is someone who can be good in the midfield area. The defense is rather good with the likes of Bednarek, Glik and Cash. Poland and Argentina should be a really great watch to see.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group B - Summary</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 19:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-b/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-b&#34;&gt;Group B&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;england&#34;&gt;England&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An absolute golden generation of players continuously ruined by a terrible manager (Seriously can&amp;rsquo;t wait till Howe or Potter manages this team). Anyways, they are pretty strong favorites to top the group but something is telling me in the later stages they can get found out. Patience is needed to break them down due to the 5 at the back system and their pace on the counter. Players to watch among a few are Sterling, Foden, Kane, and Mount. Keep an eye on Bellingham. Massive season so far and hoping he makes a bang in the WC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;youngster-to-watch-bellingham-cm&#34;&gt;Youngster to watch: Bellingham (CM)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;iran&#34;&gt;Iran&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have outside pressure to be replaced for Ukraine. Putting all that aside they have an ok team. Wales and the USA mean their work is cut out for them. Sardar Azmoun will be absolutely pivotal for them if he manages to stay fit and get service from the others. Alireza Jahanbakhsh is a fairly decent player. Maybe a few surprises could pop up from them&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;usa&#34;&gt;USA&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The US national team. Not as successful as their female counterparts but now they have quite a promising roster of young talent. We have gone from Landon Donovan and Clint Dempsey to the likes of Christian Pulisic and Gio Reyna. They have a good keeper in Matt Turner(Arsenal). A really decent midfield with the likes of Mckennie, Tyler Adams and Reyna. Maybe only a lack of experience is the only drawback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;youngsters-to-watch-weahst-busiocm--adamscdm&#34;&gt;Youngsters to watch: Weah(ST), Busio(CM),  Adams(CDM)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wales&#34;&gt;Wales&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wales is another team who is fairly average but have got good quality in some positions. Bale is always the main talisman for them. Brennan Johnson and Dan James are not bad. The goalie spot is the only one that doesn&amp;rsquo;t give much confidence with Danny Ward being poor and Hennessey hardly getting game time ahead of Dean Henderson. If the GK spot is somehow sorted before the start maybe they could do decent&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;youngsters-to-watch-johnsonrw-williamsrb&#34;&gt;Youngsters to watch: Johnson(RW), Williams(RB)&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group A - Summary</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 19:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/group-a/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-a&#34;&gt;Group A&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;qatar&#34;&gt;Qatar&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hosts of this World Cup. The reason for the shocking time to hold it. No use chatting about it now. Looking back on their previous games, the last game was a 2-0 win against Guatemala with 2 penalties. They did win a game against Egypt on penalties(They were without Salah and many major players but it still was a win). However, they are in for an uphill battle as they are grouped with Africa Cup of Nations winners Senegal, the Netherlands and a decent Ecuador. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what they can manage&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ecuador&#34;&gt;Ecuador&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking at just their Copa America run recently gone by they were quarterfinalists but got humbled extremely by eventual winners Argentina. I think they could be good for maybe best placed 3rd team but apart from that I don&amp;rsquo;t see them being ahead of Senegal and the Netherlands&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;senegal&#34;&gt;Senegal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;African Cup of Nations winners. They have quite a decent team that could challenge the Dutch and mostly do deserve to go at maximum 2nd place. Their last game was a 1-1 draw to Iran however and there are no more matches scheduled which doesn&amp;rsquo;t give much confidence but they have the capable players to go to at least the quarters if they get the right draw. Mane and Dia are the main men in attack. Mane is a big threat down the left and Dia down the middle. The midfield of Gueye and Mendy is alright not amazing but not bad. Sarr is a good winger to have as well. At the back, Koulibaly will have to be the main man for them as always.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;youngsters-to-watch-ismaila-sarrrm-ismail-jakobslb&#34;&gt;Youngsters to watch: Ismaila Sarr(RM), Ismail Jakobs(LB)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;netherlands&#34;&gt;Netherlands&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overwhelming favorites to top the group in my opinion. Louis Van Gaal has come back with a bang and the team has developed well. Van Dijk, De Ligt and Timber is a solid back 3 with depth in the fullbacks as well with Blind and Dumfries and Malacia and Frimpong. Midfield is maybe somewhere they have to be alert in cause I don&amp;rsquo;t think they have the greatest players in Berghuis, De Roon and Klaasen(This midfield however managed to beat Belgium 1-0 in the Nations League so it&amp;rsquo;s not that bad). Frenkie De Jong has finally hit some consistent games for Barca so hoping he gets in. Gravenberch could add some quality in that area if needed but he&amp;rsquo;s hardly playing for Bayern. The attack is where the firepower lies. Gakpo, Bergwijn, Depay, Malen to name a few. An outside shout is probably Xavi Simons from PSV to add to it as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;youngsters-to-watch-gakpolw-timbercb-malacialb&#34;&gt;Youngsters to watch: Gakpo(LW), Timber(CB), Malacia(LB)&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Cup - Groups</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/wc-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 13:03:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/wc-groups/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Groups in the World Cup&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../3f795c47ff9a27f0c820c89cdfc801d3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;3f795c47ff9a27f0c820c89cdfc801d3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Cup - Coming Soon</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 13:03:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;21st November 2022 - 18th December 2022&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>