<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Categories on WC22 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/categories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Categories on WC22 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2022 CSR</copyright>
    
        <atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-3&#34;&gt;Day 3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;argentina-v-saudi-arabia&#34;&gt;Argentina v Saudi Arabia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../eb4e2f5508580d3d362ed0cbfad674c3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;eb4e2f5508580d3d362ed0cbfad674c3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well. First of all massive kudos to Saudi Arabia. Their system was absolutely solid with a high line to catch the Argentina attack out regularly. Argentina actually scored 3 offside goals. They just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the runners in behind well enough. First, a soft penalty was given when Paredes was pulled down in the box during a corner. Fairly soft but VAR thought otherwise and Messi calmly slotted home. Later in the first half alone, it was more like Argentina had the chances but was offside most of the time. Messi was well-marked. Lautaro Martinez scored the second but it was disallowed by offside(I don&amp;rsquo;t understand the new rules where the whole player has to stay on the shoulder of the last defender unlike the leg of the player). Then a shock happened in the second half when Argentina was slow and Saudi capitalized by scoring from Al-Dawsari. Romero was at fault a little bit for over-committing too early. Then a moment of quality from Al-Shehri gave them the lead. After that, it was aggressive cutting out of the ball and parking the bus massively. They just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get close. Bringing on Martinez, Fernandez and Alvarez made me think that they could have started. The aggression from Martinez, the incisive passes from Fernandez and the pace and running from Alvarez. Credit to the Saudi goalie as well who made 5 saves including a point-blank one from Tagliafico.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;saudi-arabia&#34;&gt;Saudi Arabia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ksa.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ksa.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;denmark-v-tunisia&#34;&gt;Denmark v Tunisia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../7b10eff02f52eb0f0b6707bda1a5106d.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;7b10eff02f52eb0f0b6707bda1a5106d.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A very dramatic goalless draw honestly. I was backing Denmark but they had a hard time breaking Tunisia. In fact, Tunisia was the one putting the first few attacks with the first being an aggressive tackle on Eriksen(Ease up man. He just came back to a major tournament after the Euros). The first goal was scored by Tunisia but was struck out via offside. Later on a cracking save from Kasper Schmeichel kept out the same person again in a half one v one situation. Denmark managed to have a bit of intent moving deeper into the game with the golden chance arriving for Cornelius who managed to get his attempt blocked at the goal mouth. Another goal was ruled out to offside sadly because Damsgaard was well offside. Later on, there was penalty drama for Denmark but VAR, however, didn&amp;rsquo;t give it as well which I would agree with because it seemed kind of soft. Both keepers had one brilliant moment you could say among a few routine saves. From the players I know, I think Mejbri looked alright for a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;denmark&#34;&gt;Denmark&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../den.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;den.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tunisia&#34;&gt;Tunisia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../tun.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;tun.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mexico-v-poland&#34;&gt;Mexico v Poland&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a7fa2d91fe137661711999b8e3cc78ed.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a7fa2d91fe137661711999b8e3cc78ed.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lewandowski blunted. Ochoa has arrived. Don&amp;rsquo;t sleep on Mexico. Honestly, this game was pretty dull because of the lack of clear-cut chances compared to the previous game. Only the penalty was the main talking point which I will come to in time. Mexico were seriously threatening with the likes of Lozano and Vega constantly switching sides. I think Jimenez could have made a difference instead of Martin because it seemed like they didn&amp;rsquo;t have that presence in the box at times to fire to. The major incident came later on when Poland won a penalty via Lewandowski which was given after a VAR check. Step up Lewandowski who had put away all of the penalties before this. But he has never met Ochoa who managed to save it on his left. I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice his trademark stutter before hitting the ball which was weird. Anyways this draw means Saudi Arabia leads the bloody group after one game and Argentina are at the bottom(I am pretty sure almost everyone thought that table would be upside down after one game)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mexico&#34;&gt;Mexico&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mex.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mex.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;poland&#34;&gt;Poland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../pol.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;pol.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;france-v-australia&#34;&gt;France v Australia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../0ff72b98d855a6f6e307c781ea3202b2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;0ff72b98d855a6f6e307c781ea3202b2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You cannot keep them down. Maybe things may start to look up because for the first time the defending champions of the WC have actually won their opening game with the previous 3 being losses for Italy, Spain and Germany. The first one. My god did a lot of things happen. First of all, why did he pick Lucas Hernandez to play at LB when he had a capable Theo Hernandez for that? He got beat and injured in the build-up and a great cross was bundled home by Goodwin who was hardly marked. Later on, the equalizer came from Theo(Absolutely shocked /s) to Rabiot who headed home properly. The second was just sad. I don&amp;rsquo;t understand why you have to make a show of playing out from the back against the defending champs who pressed well and got it via Rabiot who squared it for Giroud who couldn&amp;rsquo;t miss it and made it 50 for France. Mbappe missed a sitter from a great Griezmann cross which was inch perfect from them every time. One person almost got it to 2-2 for Australia but it hit the post before the end of the first half. Dembele gave another cross to Mbappe who scored a good header to make it 3. Then it was a peach of a cross from Mbappe to Giroud who made it 4 to seal the game out. This means that Giroud has leveled Theirry Henry&amp;rsquo;s goal tally for France. A great achievement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;australia&#34;&gt;Australia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../aus.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;aus.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 13:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-2&#34;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;england-v-iran&#34;&gt;England v Iran&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../75eee5ddf5647d81a37f8bf7695699bf.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;75eee5ddf5647d81a37f8bf7695699bf.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great game from England. Southgate actually ditched the 5-back formation which means the sky is officially falling. Wowwwwww I am surprised. Iran was seriously not even close anywhere. There were like I thought. Very defensive and tried to break on the counter. Due to that, they got one of the goals from Taremi. Dunno why Azmoun didn&amp;rsquo;t start but he got some minutes. If they don&amp;rsquo;t get their act together I think USA and Wales will have good shot against them. Coming to the match, Iran was lost from the moment they lost their keeper to a possible concussion. Bellingham made the breakthrough, becoming the first teenager to score at the World Cup with a brilliant header(Cross from the great Shawberto Carlos - Luke Shaw). Then it was a great volley from Saka and a great finish from Sterling gave them 3 at the end of the half. Then it was just great work from Saka to make it 4. Later on, Taremi got one and Maguire was beaten for pace(Other teams take note. He is dangerous in corners but you can beat him for pace)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;england&#34;&gt;England&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../england.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;england.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;iran&#34;&gt;Iran&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../iran.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;iran.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;senegal-v-netherlands&#34;&gt;Senegal v Netherlands&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../50ef731442814c8e7ce44e2806e240da.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;50ef731442814c8e7ce44e2806e240da.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was an amazing game. I am impressed at Senegal with the way they managed to attack really well but without Mane, the dropoff was kind of evident. The threat from Sarr and Diatta was very evident and Dia and Dieng were ineffective at ST. The Netherlands however apart from Frenkie De Jong bottling a golden chance on the counter was semi-decent as well. They managed to get chances from the likes of Gakpo, Berghuis. Noppert made a start in goal(Man is 28 and was considering retirement to become a police officer and now he has got a WC clean sheet) and he was fairly decent. Managed to hold his own which is always good. In the end, it was 2 bad errors that were capitalized and credit to the Dutch for doing it. Gakpo starts a move and FDJ(Frenkie De Jong) provides a lovely ball for the first one. Finally, Klaasen scored after a good counter to take advantage of a tiring Senegal. Keep an eye on Gakpo. If he has a good WC, it will be dangerous for Man United(I&amp;rsquo;m a fan so I am worried). Another thing is: Is there a possibility of Timber starting because, as good as De Ligt is, he was rather shaky for the most part of the game. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what Van Gaal decides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;senegal&#34;&gt;Senegal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../senegal.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;senegal.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;netherlands&#34;&gt;Netherlands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../netherlands.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;netherlands.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;usa-v-wales&#34;&gt;USA v Wales&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ce5b239d406a7b33c413b588967c44b2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ce5b239d406a7b33c413b588967c44b2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weird referee. &amp;ldquo;Soccer&amp;rdquo; almost won and Bale had to bail out Wales again. Let me start by saying that the referee was really weird, to say the least, and that&amp;rsquo;s me being kind. He was dishing out the cards in the whole game, to be honest. First half: A good run by Pulisic at the defense and a good pass to Weah opened the scoring. Besides that Hennessey had to be alert to avoid conceding a weird own goal. In the second half, Wales slowly had an influence in the game with chances from the likes of Ben Davies and Kieffer Moore. Finally, a penalty was given when Zimmerman pulled Bale down and he converted with a fast and true penalty. I think these guys will be the major contenders for 2nd spot unless Iran pulls itself together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;usa&#34;&gt;USA&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../usa.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;usa.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wales&#34;&gt;Wales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../wales.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;wales.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-1&#34;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;qatar-v-ecuador&#34;&gt;Qatar V Ecuador&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../e5c7a415cca84837cbe6a0ff753672c2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;e5c7a415cca84837cbe6a0ff753672c2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definitely the worst opening match in the history of the whole tournament. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I really thought Qatar could give a match against Ecuador. This is also the first time ever in the history of the World Cup that the host nation has lost its first match. Even Russia had a better game than this lot. Ecuador hardly broke a sweat in this game. The second half was really just chilling from them. Qatar was happy to give them the possession in the opening stages and Valencia scored the opener after around 3 minutes but it was ruled out by VAR for offside(Highly Highly controversial but was reasoned out by the fact half his leg..was..in an offside position. God these rules seem dumb). However, it would be justice served when the goalie pulled down Valencia clean through on goal for a clear penalty which was put away perfectly. The second goal was brilliantly crafted though. A really great cross from Preciado to the head of Valencia and a good header. Qatar&amp;rsquo;s best chance was probably with the last play in the first half when they managed to somehow get an unmarked header and he completely fluffed it. That probably would have made the second half more interesting but they weren&amp;rsquo;t good enough to do that so it became a very dull second half. Given the fact they have Senegal(Even without Mane they are still decent enough) and the Netherlands, I don&amp;rsquo;t have many hopes for them honestly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;qatar&#34;&gt;Qatar:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../qatar.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;qatar.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ecuador&#34;&gt;Ecuador:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ecuador.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ecuador.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Serbia</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_serbia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_serbia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---serbia&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Serbia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhVYGPCWAAAWfmA.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhVYGPCWAAAWfmA.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a group that contains Brazil, Cameroon and Switzerland. Honestly, I think they and Switzerland are genuine contenders for the second spot. Those 2 teams can cause an upset too. My lineup is solely based on their values so bear with me. In goal, a Milinkovic Savic could be trusted or Rajkovic. In defense, it&amp;rsquo;s a back 3 of the likes of Pavlovic, Milenkovic, Erakovic mostly with the usual Veljkovic injured with an unknown return date so let&amp;rsquo;s see if he&amp;rsquo;ll be back. In midfield it&amp;rsquo;s a set of 4. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.transfermarkt.com/sergej-milinkovi%C4%87-savi%C4%87/profil/spieler/266302&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SMS&lt;/a&gt;
 should mostly start. Maybe alongside him, Racic could play or the likes of Ilic as well. Kostic will mostly for sure be at LM and Zivkovic at the right. Captain Tadic will be the lone CAM there. Upfront, it is a front 2 with Vlahovic and Mitrovic(He will mostly be back in time for the WC).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_serbia.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_serbia.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Argentina</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_arg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_arg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---argentina&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Argentina&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhSqitzX0AAhtan.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhSqitzX0AAhtan.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright. Copa America winners. Winners of the Finallissima. Their team looks amazing actually. I genuinely hope they do another 2014. In goal, Emi Martinez is a lock-in. In defense, Lisandro Martinez should definitely play after his amazing start at United. Alongside him, Romero or Otamendi should be good enough. In the fullback positions, I would perhaps go Tagliafico and Montiel. In midfield, Paredes or Palacios for the CDM role. Ahead of him, De Paul is for sure to start. I feel beside him I would trust Enzo Fernandez ahead of Papu Gomez. On the wings, Di Maria or Alvarez for LW and Messi at RW. Dybala was said to be missing the WC but he has been picked in the squad. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if he will play but it would be nice to see him in the as soon as possible. In ST, Lautaro Martinez is for sure on lock there. He has been amazing for Argentina so far and he will be crucial for them in this WC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_arg.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_arg.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Spain</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_spain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---spain&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Spain&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhR8bEfWIAEWo5h.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhR8bEfWIAEWo5h.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of controversy from Enrique with De Gea being left out of the provisional 55-man squad. My feeling is that the relationship severed after Euro 2020. He relies on playing well from the back including the goalie. Even though De Gea has relatively improved under Ten Hag in that aspect, he still has a long way to go. Unai Simon is already good at that aspect. So are Robert Sanchez and Raya. Another omission is Ramos who will not be going to his 5th World Cup like Messi and Ronaldo which is sad. I think there are young and good players who can do the job well. Guillamon who is a young CDM is actually named as a defender which is interesting. Fullbacks are mostly Gaya and Carvajal. In midfield, he could either go Rodri but he does seem to trust Busquets as well. I would go with Rodri for the form. In the center, Soler and Koke could mostly be the ones he goes for but Pedri and Gavi could very well start a game or two here and there instead of them. Maybe not as a duo yet but one of them along with Soler or Koke. I think my pick is Soler and Pedri. To the attack, Fati and Torres could fight for the LW spot. In the RW spot, Nico Williams is going to a major tournament which is amazing for him. I think Asensio, Sarabia, and Pino are also rather good options. In ST, he only has Morata and no Moreno which is weird. Torres and Fati could also be at ST but let&amp;rsquo;s see how that goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_spain.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_spain.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Netherlands</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_dutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_dutch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---netherlands&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Netherlands&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../3e8ea2cb19f22724972dad132dc4423b.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;3e8ea2cb19f22724972dad132dc4423b.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, I am liking the look of this squad. This is the first World Cup for the likes of Van Dijk and Pasveer(Take a bow. Being the first choice for Ajax at 39). Van Gaal has really made a turnaround after that spell with Manchester United. The system is likely to be a 3-back system which has worked out well for them. In goal, Pasveer could be starting in goal but Bijlow is OTW as well so hoping he could have a game or so as well. At the back, you can&amp;rsquo;t look past De Ligt, Van Dijk and Timber. The options are Ake and De Vrij. On the wings maybe Malacia and Frimpong could be trusted. If not Malacia, Blind could be present as well. In midfield, it is likely to be a 3 with a CAM. Frenkie De Jong will mostly start since he has been consistent for FC Barcelona. Along with him maybe De Roon or Koopmeiners can be expected. In CAM, I&amp;rsquo;d rather have Berghuis or Klaasen. Maybe the likes of Xavi Simons could have a start. Up front is usually 2 strikers. One of them has got to be Cody Gakpo after the season he&amp;rsquo;s had in PSV. Alongside him, the options are Bergwijn, L. De Jong or even Weghorst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_dutch.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_dutch.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Senegal</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_senegal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_senegal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---senegal&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Senegal&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhRonSNXEAEIaKw.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhRonSNXEAEIaKw.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Left: Goalkeepers, Midfielders, Manager/Coach
Right: Defenders, Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well well well. This is an interesting selection from the coach. Sadio Mane will in fact be going to the World Cup despite being injured. They are hoping he will make a comeback during the tournament at the very least. With the Netherlands being the only possible threat, I think they have what it takes to finish second at least. In goal, we can&amp;rsquo;t look past Mendy but given his bad form for Chelsea(He is second choice now sadly), maybe the coach will trust one of the other two GKs. In defense, Koulibaly is a mainstay and is expected to lead them out after a successful Africa Cup of Nations triumph. Alongside him, it is between Diallo and Cisse. On the right, Formose Mendy is expected to start(Young and OTW) or Sabaly could start as well. On the left, it is between young Ismail Jakobs and the experienced Ballo-Toure. Moving onto midfield, Gueye is expected to hold the midfield alongside Mendy or Kouyate. In the frontline, Diatta could be at CAM. Ismaila Sarr could be a fix at RW. On the left, maybe Jackson could be there instead of Mane and finally up top, you could see Dia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_senegal.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_senegal.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Brazil</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_brazil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_brazil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---brazil&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Brazil&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Fg-ZVsgWQAAz8Wh.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Fg-ZVsgWQAAz8Wh.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guess my fears were true in the end. Fullbacks seem like the only weakness for Brazil here with only Alex Sandro/Alex Telles on the left and Danilo/Dani Alves on the right. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I am happy Alves is somehow there in the lineup but it&amp;rsquo;s seriously weird seeing weak options there compared to literally everywhere else in the team. In goal, I think Ederson would mostly start but Alisson has made many saves but it will be a headache. In defense, you can&amp;rsquo;t look past Marquinhos and Thiago Silva(Valiant Captain). In the fullback position, I would probably start Telles(LB) and Danilo(RB). In midfield, Casemiro deserves the start ahead of Fabinho. Instead of Fred partnering with him, I think Bruno G deserves a shout alongside him. He is on form for Newcastle. He is good physically and can pass around well so I think he deserves a go, ahead of Fred. The attack is where it is a real headache for anyone. How Firmino is not selected ahead of the likes of Richarlison I will never know. What to do when you have so much quality, you have to make tough calls. In attack, Neymar is obviously going to be on the left. Paqueta could be good at CAM and on the right, there are options galore with the likes of Antony, Raphinha, Rodrygo and more. Or Neymar could be shifted to CAM to allow Vini Jr to be LW. At ST, it should definitely be Gabriel Jesus after his great season with Arsenal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_brazil.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_brazil.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - England</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_england/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_england/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---england&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - England&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhNTSa_XEAEHdsM.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhNTSa_XEAEHdsM.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The big one I was actually waiting for. My expectations for Southgate were low but wow he absolutely went even low. Heavy imbalance, too many out-of-form players, some fatigue and dropping people who you would rather build the team around. It&amp;rsquo;s an absolute joke how the FA(Football Association) is allowing this League 1(Tier 3 of English football) coach even manage a bloody NATIONAL TEAM. The worst part of it is they are scared to hire anyone foreign. Anyways, the bottom line is it&amp;rsquo;s sad seeing a golden generation of attacking talent being wasted by a very conservative coach. Alright anymore and this post will be very big so let&amp;rsquo;s decipher the lineup and you bet your top dollar I am doing a best-ever England lineup as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In goal, I am fine with the picks of Pickford, Pope and Ramsdale with Pickford being the de facto starter. At the back I am certain it&amp;rsquo;s a back 3 of Dier, Maguire and Stones. On the left Shaw is mostly a lock and on the right, I would trust Trippier based on his form for Newcastle. Going into midfield, it picks itself with Rice and Bellingham. Going forward, the left will mostly be between Sterling and Rashford. I would trust Rashford on form and Foden or Saka on the right with Kane leading the line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup will look something like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_eng_1.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_eng_1.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are a few things to note:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;White was picked due to injuries to James and Chilwell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only 1 LB and 5 RBs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 CAMs for a formation that does not use a CAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No different CB like Tomori or even Guehi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bellingham only one outside England who is picked&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No James Ward-Prowse despite being in amazing form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kane is tired and his only backup is Wilson. No Toney or Tammy Abraham&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what I would have done:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked Tomori because he is a modern CB to partner Stones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked JWP on his amazing form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked Toney and Abraham along with Wilson and drop people like Grealish and Philips since they have hardly played and one of them was injured for a long time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Switch to a 4 back formation to actually make use of the attacking talent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is how the lineup would look like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_eng_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_eng_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>