<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on WC22 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on WC22 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2022 CSR</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 13</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_13/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-13&#34;&gt;Day 13&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;final-matchday-in-groups-g-and-h&#34;&gt;Final Matchday in Groups G and H&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-h&#34;&gt;Group H&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ghana-v-uruguay-and-portugal-v-south-korea&#34;&gt;Ghana v Uruguay and Portugal v South Korea&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../7779555c0f0b7cc5ae6aeb6bf3179d74.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;7779555c0f0b7cc5ae6aeb6bf3179d74.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../dd360dd13f1b211ece411fc2dcbca16e.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;dd360dd13f1b211ece411fc2dcbca16e.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We called this group the &amp;ldquo;Group of Death&amp;rdquo;, at the very least me. It delivered massively on the final matchday. Uruguay prevented Ghana from getting revenge for 2010 but Korea provided it anyways by pipping Uruguay on goals scored(4 to Uruguay&amp;rsquo;s 2) by beating Portugal who had a host of rotations. They have &amp;ldquo;dreamed&amp;rdquo; and they have achieved passage into the Round of 16. Let&amp;rsquo;s get into each match.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uruguay prevents Ghana revenge. Ghana do the same thing again. Farewell Suarez and Cavani.
Damn you Ghana, I thought you could really pose a threat but this grudge match turned into a damp squib. This was complete Uruguay domination in terms of chances but a moment of controversy in the 16th minute where a penalty was given to Ghana after a foul by the keeper on Kudus who lifted the ball just past his outstretched hands. But Captain Andre Ayew had his penalty saved and the goalie made up for his mistake by making a great save. Funny thing you know: Asamoah Gyan missed a penalty against Uruguay in 2010 and Ghana got knocked out. Now Ayew misses his penalty and Ghana are knocked out but now its Uruguay who will be joining them after what happened in the other game. The goals came from a brace by De Arrascaeta. Man has great experience and does well. The first came after a cross missed Ghana&amp;rsquo;s defense 😅 and came straight to Suarez who floored a defender before shooting and it was saved before being bundled in by De Arrascaeta. Suarez switched on his prime form all of a sudden, one highlight being him nutmegging Inaki Williams 😆. The second came after a good passage of play led to Suarez who looped the ball perfectly for him for the volley. Later on, once it was notified that Korea had scored a stoppage time winner against Portugal, Uruguay needed one more goal to go through on Goal Difference. Despite all the pressure they posed(Coates did a Pique by going forward in attack) they were not clinical and it was crushing for Suarez to see such a pathetic showing in front of goal. Cavani was lackluster. He got a header on target but was offside anyways and he went diving for a penalty. Word of advice: Sometimes actually trying to get the ball on target is better than looking for a penalty. Anyways it is most definitely going to be the last WC for Suarez and Cavani which I think should mean a change of system hopefully and a bigger focus on Nunez up top and having more than 2 in the middle of the park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ghana&#34;&gt;Ghana&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../gha_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;gha_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;uruguay&#34;&gt;Uruguay&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../uru_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;uru_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dreamers make it through. Son comes through for his country. Hello from the other side by Cristiano Ronaldo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Korea have done a madness by pushing to the Round of 16 by beating Portugal. Son has finally delivered when they needed him most. It was a whole set of rotations from Portugal barring a few like Pepe, D.Costa and Ronaldo. The lead came via Ricardo Horta from a Dalot cross(He got in so easily and maybe the Cancelo and Dalot combination I mentioned is probably the way to go for Portugal). The lead didn&amp;rsquo;t last long from 5 minutes as Korea managed to get back into it with a helping hand from none other than Cristiano Ronaldo who made a scuffed clearance which fell perfectly for the defender to score the equalizer(That&amp;rsquo;s what I meant when I said Hello from the other side). Apart from a few chances for Ronaldo there was not anything much that happened. So as it stands Korea are not going through. But the sub of Hwang Hee Chan changed it and made a huge difference. The corner was botched by Portugal and the counter was on and it was led by Son who was quickly closed down but he managed to find Hwang by nutmegging Dalot 😑 and he kept his composure to finish it and Korea were going through on goals scored(That&amp;rsquo;s why 0-0&amp;rsquo;s can bite you). Sadly the other game was behind by around 5 minutes 😅 so Korea had to wait till the Uruguay game was done to know for certain and sure enough they had done it. Later on, &amp;ldquo;Dreamers&amp;rdquo; which was the so-called &amp;ldquo;official&amp;rdquo; WC track by Jung Kook from BTS was blasted in the stadium which was nice to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;south-korea&#34;&gt;South Korea&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../kor_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;kor_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../por_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;por.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-h-table&#34;&gt;Group H table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../5ce2db175fba4014bc6041a949f122bb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;5ce2db175fba4014bc6041a949f122bb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-g&#34;&gt;Group G&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;serbia-v-switzerland-and-cameroon-v-brazil&#34;&gt;Serbia v Switzerland and Cameroon v Brazil&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../0a13fb4437408da1721020c1dfe3710e.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;0a13fb4437408da1721020c1dfe3710e.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fa9bd47c4a6fe494c23ddf4d117328dc.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fa9bd47c4a6fe494c23ddf4d117328dc.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One interesting game with a record matched. One upset but at the expense of a red card 😅. These results now mean that Brazil and Switzerland are going through and will face South Korea and Portugal respectively. Let&amp;rsquo;s dissect both matches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-3&#34;&gt;Match 3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 goals and it was a Swiss win. Let&amp;rsquo;s break it down now. Switzerland were attacking from the get-go. No, literally their first chance came after 25 seconds but was saved twice by GK Milinkovic-Savic. The lead eventually came to the Swiss and it was scored by none other than Big Shaq. A powerful shot after Sow waited and set him up with the pass. Now Shaqiri has joined an elite club that only had Cristiano Ronaldo thus far by scoring in 5 consecutive tournaments and has scored in his 3rd World Cup. The only other players to do it are Messi and Ronaldo. Shaq loves playing in international tournaments. Serbia found an equalizer from Mitrovic who managed to score a pinpoint header from the cross by Tadic. Next Vlahovic(who didn&amp;rsquo;t even get a look in so far) managed to score after a bad touch from the defender. Next was Embolo who managed to score from close range after a great Widmer cross. The winner came from Freuler after a great set of passes including a backheel assist from Vargas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;serbia&#34;&gt;Serbia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ser_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ser_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;switzerland&#34;&gt;Switzerland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../swi_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;swi_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-4&#34;&gt;Match 4&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just 1 goal in it and Cameroon started both Choupo-Moting and Aboubakar and it paid off with Brazil doing hefty rotations. Sadly the main news apart from the winner from Aboubakar was the injuries sustained by Alex Telles and Gabriel Jesus which is difficult news only in defense as Brazil&amp;rsquo;s attack is stacked. This combined with Neymar&amp;rsquo;s rush to fitness after his ankle injury means Brazil is in a tough spot overall. Aboubakar&amp;rsquo;s finish was perfect. The cross was put in and he headed it in perfectly. Ederson was rooted to the spot. Sadly he was on a yellow card and took his shirt off to celebrate so he got the second yellow and got a red card. The way it was given though was funny. It is quite possibly the friendliest way to give a red card 😂.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../redditsave.com_9iw0vxjvkk3a1.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;redditsave.com_9iw0vxjvkk3a1.gif&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cameroon&#34;&gt;Cameroon&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cam_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cam_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;brazil&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bra_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bra_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-g-table&#34;&gt;Group G table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../083855a3f1bc9d532da8cc058a8c1289.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;083855a3f1bc9d532da8cc058a8c1289.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-knockout-bracket&#34;&gt;THE KNOCKOUT BRACKET&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b4e2754a9b06b05696773878a503db9a.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b4e2754a9b06b05696773878a503db9a.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 12</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-12&#34;&gt;Day 12&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;final-matchday-in-groups-e-and-f&#34;&gt;Final Matchday in Groups E and F&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-f&#34;&gt;Group F&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;canada-v-morocco-and-croatia-v-belgium&#34;&gt;Canada v Morocco and Croatia v Belgium&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../914774bfa8354d075cbc76a98331b760.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;914774bfa8354d075cbc76a98331b760.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../8d9c2ae7af7314e6c2bd38c7d45a06cb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;8d9c2ae7af7314e6c2bd38c7d45a06cb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One pretty alright game and one COMPLETE DUD from one of the teams in the other game. I thought Morocco will be able to give a great game to the other teams but never a group topper 😅. It is an amazing show from the African nations. Maybe we could see more teams from AFCON because it is coming up. Don&amp;rsquo;t sleep on them that&amp;rsquo;s all. The second game does not deserve the time here because it was YET ANOTHER 0-0.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Canada gave it everything but Morocco was just on another level. Bono was back after going off at the start of the last game because of a bout of dizziness. The first came after just 4 minutes with a crazy mistake from the Canada GK. The ball comes through and the keeper rushes forward and takes the biggest of touches and it comes straight to Ziyech who has an easy target to aim at now that the keeper did himself in with that horror touch. CAN SOMEONE CHECK THE BANK ACCOUNT OF THE KEEPER FOR A BIG STACK THAT SHOULD HAVE COME IN? 💰️.  Anyways, the next goal was by En Nesyri who finally has a goal in the World Cup. I really thought he could do business for Morocco but hey better late than never and they are in the knockouts as group toppers so amazing work. Morocco got another but it was ruled out for offside and everyone except En Nesyri knew that 🤣&amp;hellip;.for a while. Canada pulled one back when a cross that came in was deflected off Aguerd for what was the first own goal in this tournament so far. Later on, it was just damage control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;canada&#34;&gt;Canada&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../can_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;can_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll just keep it brief for Croatia. Gvardiol is a different-level beast. No wonder Chelsea want him. He has been a solid rock at just 20. Apart from that nothing major apart from a few chances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;belgium-belgium-belgium&#34;&gt;Belgium Belgium Belgium&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The major team I wanna bash on which is what I was waiting for because for starters I don&amp;rsquo;t know how this team of pathetic potato sacks is still number 2 in the world. They have been knocked out and deservedly so. No bad luck of any sort. They were just bad. Everyone does not have the right mentality including even Kevin De Bruyne. Calling out your own national team as too old to the press. I get they&amp;rsquo;re not your billion-dollar Man City team but why you gotta make that public I have no clue. Apart from that, I thought their squad selection was alright but as always the fault starts at the very top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;roberto-martinez&#34;&gt;Roberto Martinez&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a8dc2c26841e7752c2b7ff092f6997eb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a8dc2c26841e7752c2b7ff092f6997eb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Freshly unemployed after this idiotic campaign(Glory Hallelujah 🙌), this Belgian Baldi is downright arrogant and stubborn to the point where Gareth Southgate actually looks better and you know how much I hate Southgate. This guy you see loves picking absolute 🐌s in his lineup who are in various retirement leagues. Vertonghen and Alderweireld are in the Belgian league. No wonder he keeps picking them. You hardly have to move countries to check others out. You have Faes who has been solid for Leicester so far and he&amp;rsquo;s rotting on the bench. Tielemans is a top-quality player and has had a great season as well. But Monsieur Martinez is like &amp;ldquo;Oh i dOn&amp;rsquo;t wAnNa pIcK HiM BeCaUsE He iS NoT A sNaIl&amp;rdquo; and instead the fool picks Witsel and Dendoncker for this game who are as fast as a damn 18-wheeler without the 18 wheels. Don&amp;rsquo;t even get me started on the damn attack. Barring De Bruyne who while he has the quality DOES NOT have the mentality of a champion and is so used to Man City&amp;rsquo;s oil money squad, the others are a joke. Mertens plays in a Turkish retirement league. Hazard does not have the pace and agility of 4 or 5 years ago. You do not trust the likes of De Ketelaere(Plays for Serie A champions AC Milan) or even Doku who has amazing agility and pace. You still trust Lukaku who was the reason you didn&amp;rsquo;t even get a goal from this game. No focus on youth and trusting snails. Are you seriously picking snails because they&amp;rsquo;re the only ones who can keep your unemployed head shiny or what? I seriously don&amp;rsquo;t get your lineups at all. You got lucky with Canada because you sat back and managed to catch them out. Against the rest, you are just as clueless as they come. Castagne is great going forward and where does he sit: IN THE CENTER OF DEFENSE WITH THE OTHER 2 SNAILS. God this man just infuriates me. This so-called &amp;ldquo;golden generation&amp;rdquo; has been thoroughly ruined by this knockoff Sivaji and they are indeed &amp;ldquo;too old&amp;rdquo; De Bruyne to win anything unless your damn coach changes up his selection because he had 0 future-proofing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;belgium&#34;&gt;Belgium&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bel_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bel_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-f-table&#34;&gt;Group F table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f8af400b00c74670645ecbbb6e6c2f9e.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f8af400b00c74670645ecbbb6e6c2f9e.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;to-roberto-martinez-and-the-belgium-national-team&#34;&gt;To Roberto Martinez and the Belgium National Team&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/TxOxbS3NTcjgTMIEFd/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;Joe&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-e&#34;&gt;Group E&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;costa-rica-v-germany-and-japan-v-spain&#34;&gt;Costa Rica v Germany and Japan v Spain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../1c465834f7176647224253a47f733417.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;1c465834f7176647224253a47f733417.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../5470ea06aa6efb87bd41a3de0303c165.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;5470ea06aa6efb87bd41a3de0303c165.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The slightest of margins. The country with the highest xG(Expected goals) out and Spain gets beaten by a side who had only 14% possession 😳. With these results, Japan actually goes through as the group toppers and Spain survives to go second. This means the fixtures are: Spain v Morocco and Japan v Croatia. A historic moment also happened as an all-female refereeing team took charge of the game between Germany and Costa Rica in the men&amp;rsquo;s World Cup. A massive massive achievement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;since-so-much-happened-in-this-group-i-will-be-combining-both-matches-together-to-show-how-crazy-the-table-moved-in-this-final-matchday&#34;&gt;Since so much happened in this group I will be combining both matches together to show how crazy the table moved in this final matchday&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;first-half&#34;&gt;First Half&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10&#39; - Raum with a great cross for Gnabry who heads it home. Germany at this point still isn&amp;rsquo;t getting out of the group because it is still 0-0 in the other game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11&#39; - Great cross from Azpilicueta for Morata who managed to finish with a bullet header. Man has only started one game and has the same goals as Gakpo and Mbappe 😅. Now, Spain and Germany are going through at 1 and 2 respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After 1 half, Spain and Germany are going through from the standings with Spain on 7 points and Germany on 4 points and Japan on 3 points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;second-half&#34;&gt;Second half&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;48&#39; - Doan manages to pull Japan level after Spain makes a huge hash of playing out from the back. His goal was a bullet outside the box. Hard true and Simon is caught out. Game on. Now it is Spain on just 5 points and Japan are on 4(GD - 0) and Germany stay on 4(GD - 0) so second place is
going to be chosen by the number of yellows and all that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;51&#39; - Controversial moment here as Tanaka has scored but the goal is ruled out. Doan first makes a great run and manages to drill the ball in and Mitoma actually hit the ball back in for Tanaka after it ran out of play apparently here. VAR is checking it&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;and it is a goal. JAPAN LEAD SPAIN through Tanaka. Maybe this moment could be talked about for a long time but Japan don&amp;rsquo;t care they are celebrating like crazy. Now Japan are going through as group toppers and Spain are now on 4 points but ahead of Germany on the same points by GD and if Spain level it Germany could squeak through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;58&#39; - Bad defending from Germany and Costa Rica have thrown a spanner in the works by equalising now from Tejeda after Neuer makes a meal out of a cross yet again and as usual Germany are second best in getting to the rebound and its 1-1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;70&#39; - It is getting worse for Germany. After missing a slew of chances to go ahead. Costa Rica has managed to score again and I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I am saying this but JAPAN and COSTA RICA are poised to go through now because they both are on 6 points but Japan are ahead on GD. It was a scramble from the free kick and it looks like the final touch came from Neuer(off his right foot to be precise) so it will be classed as an own goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;73&#39; - Sane puts the ball in but it was cleared out till Kimmich managed to head to Fullkrug who managed to sneak Havertz in who manages to calmly slot it past Navas. So now Spain is now ahead of Costa Rica on goal difference(Funnily enough that 7-0 win for Spain keeping them alive 😅)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;85&#39; - Havertz puts Germany ahead and it was coming after a load of chances including a big chance from point blank range which was saved well by Navas. Gnabry with a peach of a cross to find him. Germany is third now. Unless Spain draws level, Germany ain&amp;rsquo;t going through and it still is 2-1 to Japan now&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;89&#39; - Fullkrug makes it 4 and it is the 3 points for Germany but with Spain still unable to find a way to equalize it seems to be all for nothing. A great pass from Kimmich again and Sane sets it up on a plate for Fullkrug who easily scores it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FT - And breathe 😱. With the results the table looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../47d7ff7e8174fcac918cd18f8dc3375f.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;47d7ff7e8174fcac918cd18f8dc3375f.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GD bailed Spain out. If they leveled against Japan, Germany would have gone through. A former Barcelona manager knocks out a former Bayern manager. You love to see it 😆&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lineups&#34;&gt;Lineups&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;costa-rica&#34;&gt;Costa Rica&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../crica_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;crica_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;germany&#34;&gt;Germany&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ger_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ger_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;japan&#34;&gt;Japan&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../jap_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;jap_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spain&#34;&gt;Spain&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../spa_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;spa_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-11&#34;&gt;Day 11&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;final-matchday-in-groups-c-and-d&#34;&gt;Final Matchday in Groups C and D&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-d&#34;&gt;Group D&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;australia-v-denmark-and-tunisia-v-france&#34;&gt;Australia v Denmark and Tunisia v France&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f3ecd40cbbdba9ad59addc7a80dd542c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f3ecd40cbbdba9ad59addc7a80dd542c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../c1e9bb4869e40c388891d714f48a2de7.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;c1e9bb4869e40c388891d714f48a2de7.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 surprise results but only one of them mattered and that was Australia v Denmark. I never realized how bad they were and the fact that Australia managed to get into the Round of 16. Denmark lost twice and never won once. I never realized how bad they look without a proper ST like Poulsen. At least Eriksen is getting a longer rest before the next Man United game. Denmark better use a better ST than the ones they used because they were shambolic. Tunisia got an amazing result but France was resting all their key players and was not in the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first time Australia has qualified for the Round of 16 since 2006. It is an absolutely amazing achievement and they deserve it with how lackluster Denmark was. Leckie scored the lone goal of the game after a great counter-attack and he managed to get past 2 defenders and slotted the ball really well past Schmeichel. Apart from that, I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything left to say apart from the fact of how SHAMBOLIC Denmark is in attack. The likes of Skov Olsen, Cornelius, Braithwaite and so on are so lackluster in their finishing. They are creating so many chances thanks to Eriksen and they are just letting him down. Eriksen went through hell and back for you lot and this is how you repay him? Just pathetic is all I can say about Denmark&amp;rsquo;s finishing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;australia&#34;&gt;Australia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../aus_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;aus_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;denmark&#34;&gt;Denmark&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../den_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;den_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TUNISIA STUNS THE WORLD CHAMPIONS. On a serious level though France was taking it easy and it showed from the get-go. Tunisia meant business from the start and really dominated France who rested quite literally everybody. The goal came from the legend of Tunisia Wahbi Khazri who managed to make his mark in this tournament. As someone who knows only 2 players in this Tunisia side and one of them hardly plays it was nice seeing him score. The goal itself was not a bad one. Just casually dribbling past many people and beating Varane with a quick shift and just tapping it past Mandanda. You know the one. France thought they came back via Griezmann who was brought on but it was ruled out for offside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tunisia&#34;&gt;Tunisia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../tun_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;tun_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-d-table&#34;&gt;Group D table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../43e46c4073af781d1b60ef5a4d36aece.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;43e46c4073af781d1b60ef5a4d36aece.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I AM ASHAMED OF YOU DENMARK. ASHAMED I SAY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-c&#34;&gt;Group C&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;poland-v-argentina-and-saudi-arabia-v-mexico&#34;&gt;Poland v Argentina and Saudi Arabia v Mexico&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../deae745c61f443e0cd5907146479c0dd.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;deae745c61f443e0cd5907146479c0dd.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f14962e669e221017340d0bfeeac02e7.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f14962e669e221017340d0bfeeac02e7.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first game was dominated by Argentina so that was a no-brainer but the second game decided so much. Mexico and Poland&amp;rsquo;s fate were in the balance for the second game and Mexico were knocked out via a goal from Saudi Arabia which meant they went out on goal difference. They were going home anyways because of more yellow cards if that goal had not been scored. They just switched off defensively and let in a goal by Saudi. This now means Poland and Argentina are through and the Round of 16 matches are France v Poland and Argentina v Australia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-3&#34;&gt;Match 3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From River Plate to the World Cup. An unwanted Messi record and Lewandowski survives&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Really dominant from Argentina. Poland tried to sit back deep and hold them but they found the gaps really well and managed to constantly get shots away. The first chance was a penalty which I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest was very soft because the keeper when saving hit Messi&amp;rsquo;s face it really wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big hit at all but it was given anyways(The keeper said he had a bet with Messi that a penalty will not be given by VAR which was just brushed off by Messi when it actually was given 😅) and Messi wound up having his penalty saved and with that, he has become the first player to have 2 penalties saved in the World Cup. Argentina didn&amp;rsquo;t stay down for long as they had a blistering start to the second half with a great cross by Molina bundled in by Mac Allister(from bloody Brighton 😂). The second was scored by Alvarez with a beautifully curled effort past the keeper. The first sentence was written because both Enzo Fernandez and Alvarez had started and they were winning things with River Plate in Argentina and are now on the big stage of the World Cup playing alongside Messi. Lewandowski is not too fussed about the result after seeing what happened in the other game&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;poland&#34;&gt;Poland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../pol_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;pol_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-4&#34;&gt;Match 4&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;saudi-arabia&#34;&gt;Saudi Arabia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ksa_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ksa_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mexico&#34;&gt;Mexico&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mex_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mex_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chavez becomes this World Cup&amp;rsquo;s Forlan. The minimum margins that didn&amp;rsquo;t matter. Mexican complacency and arrogance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🎵Let me sing a Kutty Story, pay attention, listen to me 🎵
There was a ball all the way back in 2010 known as the Jabulani and it was notorious and had a load of complaints from goalkeepers for being highly unpredictable but it was actually mastered by one person alone and that person was&amp;hellip;.Diego Forlan. He was called the best player of the tournament and scored 5 goals including a cracking free kick against Ghana(Had an infamous situationnnnnn as well 👀). And people around him said he trained relentlessly to get used to the ball and he used it well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So with that in mind, it seems like Chavez from Mexico seems to have a handle on this World Cup&amp;rsquo;s ball which is lighter and is actually discouraging players to take shots from range because a little power could be enough to send the ball flying into Row Z. Chavez had 2 freekicks and both were on target and one of em was a goal which was just beautifully struck. Just slightly below the absolute top corner but amazing nonetheless. The second was for the left corner but it was saved well. The first goal was a simple flick from a corner bundled in by Martin who was alert. Technically with this scoreline, they had a chance to go through but they had more yellow cards so which meant Poland will go through so they pushed really hard for a third and got one but were ruled out for offside by VAR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mexico got complacent and was weak towards the end of added time and Saudi had a chance and took it. With the lack of defenders, he easily got past and slotted it home. This meant with Poland&amp;rsquo;s loss Mexico was eliminated on goal difference anyways. And now we say goodbye to a World Cup legend: Memo Ochoa, the goalkeeper for the big stage and the big stage alone&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../2acec77cffdd46dd46706adbb1642e5f.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;2acec77cffdd46dd46706adbb1642e5f.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/rHR8qP1mC5V3G/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;Salute&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;gracias-por-los-recuerdos&#34;&gt;Gracias por los recuerdos&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-c-table&#34;&gt;Group C table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../group_c_table.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;group_c_table.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;remember-when-you-were-at-the-top-of-the-group-at-one-point-saudi-arabia-funny-how-life-has-a-way-of-hitting-back-&#34;&gt;Remember when you were at the top of the group at one point Saudi Arabia? Funny how life has a way of hitting back 😂&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-10&#34;&gt;Day 10&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;final-matchday-in-group-a-and-b&#34;&gt;Final Matchday in Group A and B&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-a&#34;&gt;Group A&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;netherlands-v-qatar-and-ecuador-v-senegal&#34;&gt;Netherlands v Qatar and Ecuador v Senegal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../8e6a1b981514567fb8660e21d51fe5e4.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;8e6a1b981514567fb8660e21d51fe5e4.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../9df8aabcfecc3d57bd6fbe430d618a1a.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;9df8aabcfecc3d57bd6fbe430d618a1a.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With these results, Netherlands and Senegal have officially gone through. A massive kudos to both Senegal and Ecuador. Senegal after being AFCON champions is now through to the WC knockouts. I was skeptical because Mane was really influential but they managed to pull through. Ecuador you have a really young squad that will definitely learn from this and get stronger. Take heart in that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I feel Qatari&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really loved seeing you say that Infantino. Because now it exposes what a big idiot you are. To tell the people to focus on the tournament but completely try to sweep the issues under a rug is just plain stupid. So yes today I really do feel Qatari because I have seen the first World Cup hosts that have lost all 3 of their World Cup group games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was complete domination by the Dutch, with Gakpo and De Jong providing the goals. The first goal was a good one where Gakpo latched onto a pass and managed to slot it home perfectly(I don&amp;rsquo;t see those guys who told Gakpo was &amp;ldquo;just a winger&amp;rdquo;. Funny they disappeared). He has become the first player to score in every WC game. A header, a goal with each foot. His stock is steadily rising. The second was from De Jong who managed to bundle in the loose ball after a shot. Never doubt the Manchester United Heisenberg. He knew their quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;netherlands&#34;&gt;Netherlands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../net_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;net_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;qatar&#34;&gt;Qatar&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../qat_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;qat_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great match from both teams. They gave it everything. If it was a draw I think it was Ecuador going through. Senegal got a chance when Sarr was brought down. He managed to slot it in with a sort of no-look penalty(Ballsy  I&amp;rsquo;ll admit). Second half things changed when Caicedo managed to put the ball in and he was&amp;hellip;..COMPLETELY UNMARKED. I am not angry here FYI but I was more surprised at the level of space being afforded. In terms of attack, both sides were equal and Senegal managed to put themselves ahead through their captain Koulibaly who managed to get a good volley past the keeper. Again he was pretty much not marked as well. Later on, it was just more of time wasting. All those tactics you would see normal teams do. Ecuador tried its hardest to speed things along but in the end, it was Senegal who managed to go through. Take a bow Aliou Cisse. An AFCON title and now pushing Senegal through to the Round of 16. I tip my hat to you. Ecuador has a really young squad with talent. It is just about having the right experienced head and a bit of nurturing to make them great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ecuador&#34;&gt;Ecuador&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ecu_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ecu_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;senegal&#34;&gt;Senegal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../sen_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;sen_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-a-table&#34;&gt;Group A table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f5ccc696821091ddaab9cae1a1b044c8.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f5ccc696821091ddaab9cae1a1b044c8.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sigh&lt;/strong&gt; I just love seeing the team at No 4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-b&#34;&gt;Group B&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wales-v-england-and-iran-v-united-states&#34;&gt;Wales v England and Iran v United States&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../79cbd62a8fffd05dd05496c64b093d85.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;79cbd62a8fffd05dd05496c64b093d85.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f8ffe49994453039be83251624aa6669.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f8ffe49994453039be83251624aa6669.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;England and the USA make it through completing the first 2 matches of the Round of 16 brackets where the Dutch will face the USA. Should be an equal game and England will face African champions Senegal. Can Senegal replicate what the USA did to England or will England&amp;rsquo;s quality get the better of them? Let us see. England should have been winning all the group stages and they needed the star boys Foden and Rashford to bail themselves out. They made a great difference. If Southgate started his usual squad they definitely would have struggled. Bellingham was given more license to move forward while Henderson and Rice stayed back even though Henderson felt like the odd man out from the team selection. The World War derby was won by the USA. For context, the countries are obviously at loggerheads and Iran obviously has their issues. I think Taremi was their only bright spark. Other than that I have nothing to say to a nation that does not give the same respect for people of the opposite sex. The US has such a young midfield which I am excited to see develop(Musah at 20, Adams at 23 and McKennie at 24) and obviously Tim Weah(Son of George Weah) and the LeBron James of &amp;ldquo;soccer&amp;rdquo;, Eye of the tiger Pulisic as well. I hope they all develop well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-3&#34;&gt;Match 3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Star boys bail out Southgate. Wales needs new tricks. Rashford reborn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As much as I bang on Southgate, he actually listened and gave the likes of Rashford and Foden the start and they did well. Bellingham seemed to have more freedom and was so much better than Mount who was dreadful thus far. The lead only came in the second half from a moment of quality from Rashford from the freekick. Well struck and brilliantly curled in. Next, it was Foden who managed to score after nipping the ball back in the Welsh half and Kane provided a great cross to him. I honestly think Kane has become less of a goal-poacher and more of a provider because he was setting up chances left right and center. The second was another from Rashford who managed to score on his left past the keeper pretty easily. His development under ten Hag has been nothing short of brilliant. He is a man reborn
England hardly had anything for their defense except one chance from Moore which was heavily deflected by Maguire. Wales just needs something new. This overreliance on Bale is just getting stupid at this point. They have decent youngsters with the likes of Neco Williams, Brennan Johnson, Dan James, and Ampadu and they just don&amp;rsquo;t fire if Bale doesn&amp;rsquo;t. Just change things up because I don&amp;rsquo;t like seeing talent wasted ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wales&#34;&gt;Wales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../wal_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;wal_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;england&#34;&gt;England&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../eng_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;eng_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-4&#34;&gt;Match 4&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The World War derby. I&amp;rsquo;ll mostly keep it brief because I hardly want to talk about one of the countries here. They were lackluster and clueless. Much like their own leadership. The USA just need to be more clinical and smarter and I think they could have gotten more goals out of this fixture. Pulisic put his body on the line for his country to score what was the only goal of the game. The USA had really good attacking intent from the get-go with the likes of Dest being the threat down the right side. The only goal was from a delightful cross from Dest and Pulisic managed to score but he did clatter into the goalie after scoring which left him in fairly considerable pain. He did carry on after some treatment but he was withdrawn at halftime which was sad. Here&amp;rsquo;s hoping he is back by the time they face the Netherlands which is NOT an easy game. As much as Weah and Sargent are young and promising they are not Pulisic. In the end, Iran was calling for a penalty after a possible foul by Carter-Vickers but there was hardly enough contact to even rule it as a penalty. The USA had a few hairy moments but the lackluster finishing helped them. They have got to be more solid in defense if they want to stand a chance against the Dutch because their defense will be solid as well and they can nick a goal and sit back if they&amp;rsquo;re not careful. The midfield is so promising with the likes of McKennie, Adams and Musah. In attack, Weah needs to be more clinical and also check his runs because he scored a goal that was offside in this match.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;iran&#34;&gt;Iran&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ira_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ira_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;united-states&#34;&gt;United States&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../usa_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;usa_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-b-table&#34;&gt;Group B Table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../9d4d0cd17471ecd3bc0aaf1fe18635a3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;9d4d0cd17471ecd3bc0aaf1fe18635a3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;gianni-infantino&#34;&gt;Gianni Infantino&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../74ec3909c36ea43a7a66ba91c8d2fd8c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;74ec3909c36ea43a7a66ba91c8d2fd8c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/danroan/status/1593879961706049536?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1593879961706049536%7Ctwgr%5E949e60b4f87d815d00ab89ebd749123178ff045b%7Ctwcon%5Es1_c10&amp;amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cbssports.com%2Fsoccer%2Fnews%2Ffifa-boss-gianni-infantino-slams-world-cup-critics-in-bizarre-speech-i-feel-qatari-i-feel-arab-i-feel-gay%2F&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;The interview&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/samindrakunti/status/1593880270352093185?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1593880270352093185%7Ctwgr%5E949e60b4f87d815d00ab89ebd749123178ff045b%7Ctwcon%5Es1_c10&amp;amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cbssports.com%2Fsoccer%2Fnews%2Ffifa-boss-gianni-infantino-slams-world-cup-critics-in-bizarre-speech-i-feel-qatari-i-feel-arab-i-feel-gay%2F&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;One reaction&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ce00c2a5be3485012a0e74232552b884.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ce00c2a5be3485012a0e74232552b884.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The man who feels Qatari, Arab and so many other countries and also various feelings(Such a multi-faceted individual /s). The person who somehow knows what it is like to be queer and bullied for that. He is trying to sympathize by saying his bullying experience is the same as what the LGBTQ+ groups feel when in fact he does not take into account that it is in fact so much worse. He says that we should be proud Qatar is recruiting workers from poor countries. Yeah, they come expecting money and leave in a flipping body bag to their native countries. But yeah let&amp;rsquo;s focus on Qatar being soooooo gracious, shall we? /s. The fact that he ran unopposed just shows how incompetent FIFA is as a whole. This whole bid itself was given in an absolutely corrupt way and the president who did do it was sacked completely due to the corruption. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how deep the Qatar guys have their hook in him but I don&amp;rsquo;t really care about any of that. You do not know what it feels like to be gay and enslaved. Qatar basically did modern slavery by recruiting so many workers and trying to build the infra which didn&amp;rsquo;t exist when they won the bid in the first place. So much blood spilled because of it. This fool says &amp;ldquo;Oh yEaH LeT&amp;rsquo;S JuSt fOcUs oN ThIs wOrLd cUp bEcAuSe iT Is gOiNg tO Be tHe gReAtEsT EvEr&amp;rdquo; when in reality this tournament will always be a marker as to how dirty the beautiful game can really get. I really hope you can see the error of your ways and I hope someone with good values can be the head of this huge organization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;csr-out&#34;&gt;CSR Out.&lt;/h4&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 9</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-9&#34;&gt;Day 9&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cameroon-v-serbia&#34;&gt;Cameroon v Serbia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b58a94997ad88960ba6deeaa1826417f.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b58a94997ad88960ba6deeaa1826417f.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game of the tournament. Why be picky when you can have both? Serbia complacency or not?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What a game this was. By far the game of the tournament. Serbia did well to come back from an early goal from Cameroon via Castelletto from the corner with goals from Milinkovic-Savic(Outside the box) and Pavlovic(Free kick). The second half is where the craziness began with Mitrovic giving Serbia a 2-goal lead after a load of passes inside the box. I remember when the Cameroon squad came &lt;a href=&#34;https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_cameroon/&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;out&lt;/a&gt;
 I said that I would have liked to see Choupo-Moting start compared to Aboubakar due to form and he did. But it felt like a bad thing when that level of quality was on the bench. This coach decides to have both of them by bringing on Aboubakar. What an impact he made. First, he scored a really great chip when there were doubts about offside but it was later given after a VAR check. Next Aboubaker was sent through again and managed to cut it back for Choup-Moting who leveled. The game could have gone either way. Serbia just couldn&amp;rsquo;t find their main men. Cameroon also had its chances here and there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A controversial moment before the game as Onana was dropped and completely axed from the Cameroon squad after a fallout with the coach who wanted someone more traditional which is quite stupid but to each their own. In the end, he wanted someone who could defend well from freekicks. Well, Serbia&amp;rsquo;s equalizer came from a freekick so&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cameroon&#34;&gt;Cameroon&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cam_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cam_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;serbia&#34;&gt;Serbia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ser_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ser_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;korea-v-ghana&#34;&gt;Korea v Ghana&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../98c513fcb2517ee487a9892569fa77e0.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;98c513fcb2517ee487a9892569fa77e0.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11 goals in 2 games today. We are getting spoiled for good matches after what is forever. Seeing so many teams park the bus and not want to attack in the damn group stages was getting painful to watch as you might have seen in some of my previous writing on the goalless draws. Ghana came to play with Salisu from the corner after a scramble there. Then it was a peach of a cross onto the head of Kudus to make it 2-0. The second half was a different story yet again. Cho Guensung made an immediate impact with 2 great headers to level for Korea. It was neck and neck between both teams before Kudus managed to score his second after the ball fell kindly to him. Korea huffed and puffed massively toward the end after Ghana decided to park the bus but they could not find a breakthrough. The number of crosses they managed to put in the 10 minutes of added time alone was just insane. Toward the end, Korea was not allowed to take a corner and the coach was furious. So furious that he managed to get a red card.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;korea&#34;&gt;Korea&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../kor_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;kor_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ghana&#34;&gt;Ghana&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../gha_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;gha_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;brazil-v-switzerland&#34;&gt;Brazil v Switzerland&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../1927d0fb6b1e419ce2c420157aa64b2b.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;1927d0fb6b1e419ce2c420157aa64b2b.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another goal of the tournament contender. Swiss were lackluster. I want that offside rule GONE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another dominant display that could have been even more honestly. Their chances were from Vini(VAR ruled it out for offside because Richarlison was offside and came back to be involved in the play before the ball went to him) and Rodrygo(Who should have scored but was defended out). Brazil have managed to qualify for the knockouts but with Neymar, Danilo and Alex Sandro in this match being injured, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the coach is going to go with but let&amp;rsquo;s see. Brazil were fluid but I think Neymar&amp;rsquo;s influence was missed. Paqueta was alright but not that great. I don&amp;rsquo;t get why Fred was starting ahead of Bruno G who made a great impact when he came on. Brazil actually had no shots on target from Switzerland. They bossed that defense compared to Switzerland. The winner, in the end, came from Casemiro which is definitely another goal of the tournament contender after quick one-touch passes between Vini, Rodrygo and finally Casemiro with a quick volley which had a slight deflection from Akanji.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;brazil&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bra_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bra_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;switzerland&#34;&gt;Switzerland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../swi_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;swi_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;portugal-v-uruguay&#34;&gt;Portugal v Uruguay&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../4670942c1a7213824cb712c8d5b94bc3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;4670942c1a7213824cb712c8d5b94bc3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Third team through. Greedy(in a good way) Ronaldo wants more goals. Bruno Magnifico.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next team to go through. Even though I can&amp;rsquo;t understand Ronaldo going wide it kind of worked here and there and Uruguay are left ruing the chances they had to go ahead. I think Bentancur had the best chance when he went all the way but just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the shot past Costa. It would have been a great goal to see if he got it. The breakthrough came in the second half via Bruno except&amp;hellip;it was shrouded in controversy as Ronaldo actually got his head towards it and was claiming it sort of. In the end, the stadium announcer gave it to Fernandes and eventually, Adidas proved that the ball did not graze Ronaldo&amp;rsquo;s head and it was indeed Bruno&amp;rsquo;s goal. I think that was a genuine cross and if not for Ronaldo I think the keeper would have saved it. Because of that Ronaldo distraction looking back on it, the keeper was completely bamboozled. The second was a penalty after Gimenez handled Bruno&amp;rsquo;s pass that was given after a VAR check which felt harsh because it was not at all intentional. Bruno stepped up as Ronaldo was already subbed off at that point and calmly slotted it home. To be honest he could have very well had a hattrick towards the end with 2 shots: One of them cannoning off the post and the other being just wide. Portugal through and Uruguay will have to get past Ghana in what is a grudge match from 2010 when Luis Suarez heroically handled the ball and got himself sent off, Ghana missed the spot kick and Uruguay went through. Will history repeat itself in a way with Uruguay going through at Ghana&amp;rsquo;s expense? Let&amp;rsquo;s wait and watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../por_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;por_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;uruguay&#34;&gt;Uruguay&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../uru_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;uru_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-8&#34;&gt;Day 8&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;japan-v-costa-rica&#34;&gt;Japan v Costa Rica&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../38a2c7f84a4e06602b66276b5f188fd6.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;38a2c7f84a4e06602b66276b5f188fd6.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t even wanna say much about this game. I have the highest disgust for the Japanese. They were all as inefficient as Timo Werner for Chelsea. It was a hard watch that I almost expected them to miss almost every time they attacked. Costa Rica held on so much and somehow managed to score with their first shot. If I am being brutally honest the goal wasn&amp;rsquo;t that great because he managed to dig it out of his feet but the keeper should be doing better because he did get a hand on it. With this win now, Germany still has a good shot now after their loss against this Japanese side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;japan&#34;&gt;Japan&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../jap_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;jap_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;costa-rica&#34;&gt;Costa Rica&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../crica_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;crica_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;belgium-v-morocco&#34;&gt;Belgium v Morocco&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f8d1983c77c63a1d57f897101861f4e3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f8d1983c77c63a1d57f897101861f4e3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stubborn Martinez. Belgium are &amp;ldquo;too old&amp;rdquo;. Deserving Morocco.
This game was one where Belgium really was absolutely nowhere. Martinez was stubborn going with his snail defense yet again. You have Faes who has been alright for Leicester and Theate who is young and promising and yet he still trusts the snails. That came back to bite him in the end as Morocco was attacking from the get-go. Hazard had his flaws with his lack of dribbling. He did not trust the likes of De Ketelaere, Openda and Trossard(Although he did bring him on later). Morocco did get the lead right before halftime when Ziyech&amp;rsquo;s freekick went in but it was disallowed because of offside. Saiss was adjudged to be interfering as well in a way which was annoying. We need a rewrite of the offside rule. Just bring the normal way back. If his foot is beyond the defender he is off otherwise he is on. This would have changed the dynamic completely and made Belgium attack. They did go ahead finally from Sabiri in the same fashion. Even though the official score says Saiss, I am giving it to Sabiri who hit a really good freekick and Saiss was onside and managed to disrupt Courtois again. The second was the nail in the coffin after Ziyech&amp;rsquo;s perfect cutback. De Bruyne is right. Belgium are &amp;ldquo;too old&amp;rdquo; to win the World Cup. They have a manager who trusts literal snails over youth so I can see why he would think that. He&amp;rsquo;s probably too used to Man City.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A side note. Bono who is the usual keeper for Morocco was originally named in the lineup. He went all the way to the photo but was replaced by Munir. Hope it isn&amp;rsquo;t serious. Munir was rather decent in this match overall but he isn&amp;rsquo;t Bono&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;belgium&#34;&gt;Belgium&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bel_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bel_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;croatia-v-canada&#34;&gt;Croatia v Canada&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![117f8eadaffba548555aa89ac242d986.png]Canada has become the next team to bow out. After topping CONCACAF qualifying, they managed to lose their second game and are now out. This was a drubbing and the score actually could have been way more. We got the fastest goal of this tournament from Davies who was unmarked from a great cross. Later on, Kramaric managed to score but it was offside. He managed to score again however from a great pass by Perisic. Next, it was Livaja who managed to score outside the box after a great run from Juranovic. Overall Canada just didn&amp;rsquo;t have much going forward and they were barely hanging on. Kramaric doubled his tally after half time and Majer just managed to add further salt to the wounds at the end. Davies gave everything for Canada. Here&amp;rsquo;s hoping they build on that and work hard for 2026 when they are one of the hosts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;canada&#34;&gt;Canada&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../can_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;can_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;spain-v-germany&#34;&gt;Spain v Germany&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../9bdf4c2200c06eeb9eae5209dad3dc9c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;9bdf4c2200c06eeb9eae5209dad3dc9c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a thoroughly entertaining game. Yes, it was a draw but Germany is still in it after the disgrace from Japan. The first chance came after just 6 minutes with Olmo working Neuer who tipped it onto the post. Spain was fluid as always and created really well. One chance from Germany came after a bad pass from Unai Simon but Gnabry couldn&amp;rsquo;t hit the target. Flick made an interesting change playing Muller as a ST. Problem is, he ain&amp;rsquo;t a ST either. Like come on man why can&amp;rsquo;t u trust anyone other than Werner? He is injured get over it. At the 40-minute mark, Rudiger was completely unmarked and managed to head it in easily but after a VAR check, it was ruled out for offside. The new semi-automated offside tech working well so far in this tournament. One thing was evident from Germany: They pressed well from the front and created a few openings that way. At those times Spain felt a little shaky but Simon stood firm. Spain managed to take the lead via Alvaro Morata who managed to score from a brilliant low cross from Jordi Alba. Sule had to be doing better there sadly as he was the one caught out badly. Musiala had a good chance to bring Germany back but his shot was easily parried by Simon. Germany did come back thanks to an actual ST who was brought on. Fullkrug managed to beat Simon who really was lazy if I&amp;rsquo;m being honest. The assist was from Musiala who actually messed up a little but he was there luckily. This is what a goal poacher ST does. Hopefully, Flick will start Fullkrug at least in the last game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spain&#34;&gt;Spain&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../spa_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;spa_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;germany&#34;&gt;Germany&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ger_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ger_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-7&#34;&gt;Day 7&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tunisia-v-australia&#34;&gt;Tunisia v Australia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../733149d843d76e09546297dd3cc1b9cf.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;733149d843d76e09546297dd3cc1b9cf.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What a win for Australia. This is their first win since 2010. 12 years in the making and they deserved it. They managed to have the attacking threat and they found the breakthrough via Duke who managed to head in perfectly off a deflected cross from Goodwin. Apart from that one moment in the first half, the whole half was good defending from Australia after managing to block a golden chance from Tunisia. Australia also had some chances here and there but just weren&amp;rsquo;t clinical. You could say the same about Tunisia. There seems to be a general amount of long shots being very very wild. I am starting to doubt the ball. We all know the legend of the Jabulani which was the ball in 2010 and was notorious for its unpredictability. Forlan was the one who managed to tame it well when he trained relentlessly with it. I am not sure if we have that same situation with the fact that the ball has that offside ball-tracking tech inside it. With the goalless draws and the wild long shots, I have been wondering a few things about the actual ball.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tunisia&#34;&gt;Tunisia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../tun_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;tun_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;australia&#34;&gt;Australia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../aus_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;aus_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;poland-v-saudi-arabia&#34;&gt;Poland v Saudi Arabia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f37a711653c47616d4700c18252a1d97.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f37a711653c47616d4700c18252a1d97.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First goal for Lewa. The Wojciech Wall. Unlucky Saudi.
This game could have gone either way if I am being honest because Saudi did look menacing on the attack against Poland but the combination of experience and youth in Glik and Kiwior respectively held firm through it all. Poland took the lead through Zielinski after a goalmouth scramble. Saudi were looking threatening really and had a chance to get back into the game when a penalty was given after a VAR check when Bielik brought down the Saudi attacker. Seemed a bit soft because he managed to use the slightest contact but hey whatever works for them. However, Szczesny did a madness: saving the first penalty and the follow-up as well to keep them in it. Later on, in the second half, Milik hit the post and Lewandowski finally managed to get his first goal in the WC after a mistake from a Saudi midfielder Al-Malki allowed him to get through and slot it easily. All I&amp;rsquo;ll say for that is: You never do that when you have a goal poacher like Lewandowski. After that goal, it was just setting up shop in defense and just holding on for the points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;poland&#34;&gt;Poland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../pol_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;pol_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;saudi-arabia&#34;&gt;Saudi Arabia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ksa_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ksa_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;france-v-denmark&#34;&gt;France v Denmark&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../56b9066faf018e0eb9f7394ab436eb1d.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;56b9066faf018e0eb9f7394ab436eb1d.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First nation through. Mesmerizing Mbappe. Dreadful Denmark
With this win, France is now the first nation confirmed in the Round of 16. It was a masterful performance but also it also helped with the misses Denmark chalked up. France took their chances, Denmark couldn&amp;rsquo;t and sometimes that is the difference. Mbappe scored after linking up brilliantly with Theo Hernandez. Denmark did manage to get back into it from a corner when Christensen managed to score past Lloris. But Mbappe made sure the 3 points came when he managed to bundle a cross in from Griezmann(He is doing very well for France at CAM honestly). Apart from that, it was not good enough for Denmark in terms of their finishing. This also means the end of the World Cup curse where the defending champions always went out in the group stage of the next tournament.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;denmark&#34;&gt;Denmark&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../den_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;den_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;argentina-v-mexico&#34;&gt;Argentina v Mexico&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../48f19e324d10346467c73ed2adefe8ea.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;48f19e324d10346467c73ed2adefe8ea.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One final is a success. Never doubt Messi. Star in the making - Enzo Fernandez&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This game was weird from the very beginning. Mexico adopted a 5 back system to neutralize Argentina. It was working all the way in the first half. Looking at Mexico, they played both Vega and Lozano as forwards. Argentina went for Lisandro, Mac Allister(Suprise), G. Rodriguez and all which was different but I don&amp;rsquo;t know why Enzo Fernandez and Alvarez were starting at CM and LW respectively.  Argentina and Mexico were really liking going to the ground easily which made the referee&amp;rsquo;s job really hard due to the amount of playacting. The second half was when the fun began so to speak. First Messi was somehow afforded a little extra space and he managed to score outside the box past Ochoa who is well known for being a GOAT keeper at only the World Cup. A massive achievement. The second came from a corner when the ball was passed to Enzo Fernandez(Fresh sub) and he managed to dribble past 2 defenders and managed to curl an absolute beauty past Ochoa. He becomes the youngest player to score for Argentina since&amp;hellip;..yep Messi. Messi with that first goal has now matched Maradona in terms of goals(8) and matches(21). By that time Mexico actually switched to a 4-back system and Argentina to a 5-back system. However, after that Fernandez special, it felt pointless even though Mexico were pretty dangerous as well but just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the ball into the final third. Martinez(CB) was brilliant at the back as he has been for Manchester United.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mexico&#34;&gt;Mexico&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mex_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mex_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-6&#34;&gt;Day 6&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wales-v-iran&#34;&gt;Wales v Iran&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a305d874030a275c372f4d45c31026d0.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a305d874030a275c372f4d45c31026d0.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have seen the first red card of this tournament and what surprised me is that they had to go to VAR to even give it. It was a clear high foot by Hennessey on Taremi which was a red from miles off. The irony that a new directive from FIFA managed to give Iran the win was kind of funny after my criticizing loads of added time. &lt;strong&gt;Simply put, a directive was put in place to prevent time-wasting and that was to add more than normal minutes at the end of each game. It is harder on the players because these guys have played at least 3 games each week for their clubs and now they are being forced to play 95 and 100 minutes each game. It is just a joke but I do not want to take it away from Iran because they deserved the win&lt;/strong&gt;. With the way Iran played, I was more shocked as to how they weren&amp;rsquo;t able to win easily. They were dominant and Wales were off their game so much. The reliance of Wales on Bale was too obvious. He was off his game by a long way and Wales was also off because of it. As much as he is a good player for Wales, other players do have to step up. Neco Williams, Harry Wilson and others. I get relying on one man alone but Wales has youngsters in promising positions. I hope they don&amp;rsquo;t waste that. Coming back to both goals by Iran, they were really good goals scored on the counter and also Danny Ward was in goal(Not exactly a keeper in form). The red card sub was Ward for Ramsey. The first one was a good shot outside the box after a fluffed clearance from Joe Allen. The second was just a trademark counterattack. Fewer numbers, and tiring legs and they managed to easily score. Besides this, I think the best chance they had was a shot that hit the post twice before being saved by Hennessey finally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wales&#34;&gt;Wales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../wales_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;wales_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;iran&#34;&gt;Iran&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../iran_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;iran_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;qatar-v-senegal&#34;&gt;Qatar v Senegal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../5dba53ad7821b1e516c5ca3dfb927103.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;5dba53ad7821b1e516c5ca3dfb927103.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have got the first elimination of the tournament and surprise surprise it is the hosts. For this match however they put up a little fight with an equalizer so I will give them that. Apart from that, I ain&amp;rsquo;t shedding any tears for them leaving. Senegal was confusing somehow. Not in the exact same selves, they were against the Netherlands but Qatar had good spells of defense too. The first goal came from a mistake when the defender slipped when taking the clearance and fell to Dia who managed to hit it home. Next was a good corner goal when Diedhiou managed to head it in from an Ismail Jakobs corner(I told you he will be one to watch. He took a good corner). Qatar however managed to put up a little fight when Muntari managed to get a great header past Mendy. But Senegal managed to put the game beyond them when Dieng scored a great first-time shot after a good move.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;qatar&#34;&gt;Qatar&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../qatar_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;qatar_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;senegal&#34;&gt;Senegal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../senegal_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;senegal_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;netherlands-v-ecuador&#34;&gt;Netherlands v Ecuador&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bb6a9798e9c3b610657bf2f06f56e09c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bb6a9798e9c3b610657bf2f06f56e09c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was uncharacteristic of the Netherlands. They did score early via Gakpo which was a really well-taken goal. His stock is rising and rising. Loads of power and hard for the keeper to quickly get to it. I guess the saying &amp;ldquo;You can be vulnerable when you score early&amp;rdquo; is true in this case. After that goal, they really didn&amp;rsquo;t create many chances and Ecuador was the one who was attacking for the most part of the game. That was quite literally the weird part of this game. Estupinan was dangerous down the left. Ecuador managed to get back but it was disallowed in a load of controversy. Plata shot it into the box and Esupinan managed to deflect it in but the goal was not given because one defender was in the middle and he was adjudged to have been interfering with the play which felt really harsh to them. They managed to score finally when a shot was saved by Noppert(Who had a rather decent game) and it came to Valencia who managed to score. He is the current leader of the Golden Boot. Sadly he came off after his leg(calf or knee) flared up again after the first match. There were loads of chances here and there for Ecuador but they could not find the finishing touch. One major chance came from Plata who struck it well but it hit the post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;netherlands&#34;&gt;Netherlands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../net_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;net_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ecuador&#34;&gt;Ecuador&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ecu_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ecu_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;england-v-united-states&#34;&gt;England v United States&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../4efdcdd537520c0df37f9dead9db1af0.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;4efdcdd537520c0df37f9dead9db1af0.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would not call it a dull goalless draw but it was more disappointing from England personally and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind seeing USA come away with the 3 points if they could actually finish their chances properly. With the way, England played in this match, any good team who creates as many or more chances as the USA did and they are getting through them. Maguire and Stones were good enough you could say but going forwards England had absolutely nothing in terms of creativity. Southgate does not know how to use Foden(An absolute baller for Man City) and Trent(Really good going forward) so he keeps them on the bench which was quite ridiculous. Mount, Kane, Trippier were having bad games and Southgate didn&amp;rsquo;t bother subbing them off. Kane was obviously sluggish toward the end coupled with his lack of pace. USA was great in creating chances from the likes of Pulisic, McKennie, Weah and Dest. Pulisic deserved his MOTM award.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;england&#34;&gt;England&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../eng_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;eng_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;united-states&#34;&gt;United States&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../usa_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;usa_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-5&#34;&gt;Day 5&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;switzerland-v-cameroon&#34;&gt;Switzerland v Cameroon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../5379f9d372d0aed8a477f096eb68af98.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;5379f9d372d0aed8a477f096eb68af98.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright game I would say. Cameroon started with Choup-Moting over Aboubaker which had a different outlook on the game. Real good chances from Cameroon but the Swiss defense stood firm through it all. Everybody did their job really well. Major chances in the first half came to Cameroon and the major chance came for the Swiss via Akanji from the corner. Second half Switzerland managed to increase their influence and Embolo managed to score after a good cross from Shaqiri. Weird one this because Embolo was actually born in Cameroon and he didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate. Major respect. After that, they managed to lock it all down really well and seal the points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;switzerland&#34;&gt;Switzerland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../swi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;swi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cameroon&#34;&gt;Cameroon&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cam.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cam.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;uruguay-v-korea&#34;&gt;Uruguay v Korea&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a02aa53118490e2b0ca3c362ac0c35db.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a02aa53118490e2b0ca3c362ac0c35db.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me try to keep this as brief as possible because this string of goalless draws is getting infuriating. Uruguay had 2 great chances from Godin off the corner and Valverde from range with both of them hitting the post. Apart from that Uruguay and Korea were not able to find the space to attack and shoot. Korea was mostly just not able to create solid chances. Son fluffed a golden chance when the keeper made a mistake with a pass with other chances being shot wide. Everyone loves sitting back and defending well I guess. I am starting to see how international football is really slow because there were instances where a club team would absolutely blitz some areas on the break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;uruguay&#34;&gt;Uruguay&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../uru.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;uru.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;korea&#34;&gt;Korea&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../kor.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;kor.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;portugal-v-ghana&#34;&gt;Portugal v Ghana&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../d13c8e9cb86efd7e26ff2aece20a3e69.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;d13c8e9cb86efd7e26ff2aece20a3e69.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GET.WRECKED.GHANAAAAAAA. ROFL God Portugal almost bottled it Jesus. Honestly, the system both teams adopted was a surprise but it worked for Portugal and not as much for Ghana. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry but with the quality Ghana possesses they should not be trying a 5 at the back system against Portugal. I get that it was Portugal but that was not an excuse. The first half was complete Portugal domination. Ghana could get nowhere. Second half things finally got interesting when Ronaldo was brought down by Salisu after he managed to get to the ball before the player. He managed to slot it away and he becomes the first player to score in 5 World Cups now. Unreal achievement. Later on, Ghana managed to get back in when Cancelo lost his man and when the cross came in Danilo couldn&amp;rsquo;t block it and Andre Ayew managed to score. Game on. Ghana finally switched systems to a 4 back and the game finally opened up. Portugal struck fast and quickly on the break. They pressed well and got the ball and Bruno passed it through to Felix who lifted it over the keeper beautifully. Next another pass from Bruno to the new sub Leao and he brilliantly curled the ball past the keeper. The game was not done yet when Kudus managed to cross the ball after managing to get past Cancelo again and found Bukari who headed the ball home. He did the &amp;lsquo;Siuuuu&amp;rsquo; when they should have brought the ball back. Man&amp;rsquo;s priorities are on pointttt. That was not all really because Diogo Costa who had a decent game almost bottled the 3 points when he dropped the ball down and didn&amp;rsquo;t see Inaki Williams coming behind him and he took the ball but slipped when he tried to shoot and they breathed a sigh of relief. Ronaldo had his heart in his mouth for a moment from the bench.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../por.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;por.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ghana&#34;&gt;Ghana&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../gha.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;gha.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;brazil-v-serbia&#34;&gt;Brazil v Serbia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../64aadcc68a61f0ceae99da27ff165077.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;64aadcc68a61f0ceae99da27ff165077.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jogo Bonito is officially up and running. This was a dominant show from Brazil honestly. The way they moved the ball around was really good. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t like Spain but it was more direct and fluid. Neymar is flourishing in this system by Tite but sadly had to come off due to an ankle injury. That means he will not be available for 2 matches. Danilo(RB) has the same issue. What a game from Richarlison. I was skeptical of taking him when the likes of Firmino were doing well. But this match showed how good he can be really. The first goal was classic ST instinct. Vini Jr took a great shot and he was alive to the parry by the keeper and managed to finish. The second was absolute quality. Probably currently the goal of the tournament. The ball comes in, his touch sends it up and he times a sweet aerial volley to score. Raphinha only felt like an odd man out. You hardly saw him and his replacement Antony felt more influential. Serbia I have got say, I thought their attack was their only major point but their GK wasn&amp;rsquo;t that bad honestly. He managed to keep all attempts from Brazil out in the first half which was really great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;brazil&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bra.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bra.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;serbia&#34;&gt;Serbia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ser.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ser.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-4&#34;&gt;Day 4&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;morocco-v-croatia&#34;&gt;Morocco v Croatia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b139dd02a43bbb41fa09026dc5afcd15.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b139dd02a43bbb41fa09026dc5afcd15.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 3rd goalless draw. This is already more than in 2018 when there was only 1. This was however one of the dud ones. There weren&amp;rsquo;t enough clear-cut chances yet again. It was eventful but the shots were all over the place. The keepers were hardly tested. Mazraoui had to come off due to an injury sadly. Ez Abde came on for Morocco. He was lively but he wasn&amp;rsquo;t much of a passer. He just wanted to dribble a lot and when he did put a cross in nobody was there which summed up the game really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;germany-v-japan&#34;&gt;Germany v Japan&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../75531da760113c6fedb412d7e1a7cae7.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;75531da760113c6fedb412d7e1a7cae7.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh wow. What a result for Japan. I said Asano was injured but he came in time and he was the star turn as a sub along with Doan who managed to make the second half count. The first half told a very different story however because Germany was really positive from the start with a few flashes from Japan on the counter. And they had the chance for the lead when Raum got tackled by the keeper and Gundogan slotted the penalty home. After that they were good and Musiala, Gnabry, Raum looked really threatening. In the second half things were turning around. Japan slowly managed to get back in terms of attacking threat. The subs did the star turn for Japan as the German attack was not attacking well enough. The lack of a proper ST hurting the situation even further. Havertz was not good enough as a false 9 or ST like player. I think they are a really really good team but without Werner who was the only proper ST that Flick relied on injured he has to trust in someone else like Moukoko or anybody else. The goals came from Doan who scored off the rebound when a cross was parried into his path by Neuer. Asano managed to score off a long free kick. He took a great touch and managed to finish at the near post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;off-topic&#34;&gt;Off-topic&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a form of protest from the German players which I am 100% behind. There were sanctions mentioned for the teams that used the OneLove armband(An armband the captain wears to show support for human rights and LGBTQ+ groups) like yellow cards and/or fines to the countries and some countries actually obeyed that stupid directive like England. Germany, however, didn&amp;rsquo;t and actually, the armband was hidden under Neuer&amp;rsquo;s shirt apparently and in the team photo, all of them were covering their mouths to show solidarity which I absolutely love. Just because we are in a country that disrespects human rights doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean we have to stop speaking against it. Well done Germany.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;germany&#34;&gt;Germany&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ger.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ger.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;japan&#34;&gt;Japan&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../jap.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;jap.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;spain-v-costa-rica&#34;&gt;Spain v Costa Rica&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../3e465587f15a13c41e33f48bac71c4dc.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;3e465587f15a13c41e33f48bac71c4dc.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A statement show. Young baller Gavi. Costa Rica ain&amp;rsquo;t gonna survive. This was an amazing show. Yeah, you could say it was just Costa Rica but the way they managed to pass the ball around. The possession. The spaces they got. The fact that they started without an out-and-out No 9 but still managed to move the ball well was very telling. Pedri and Gavi made a start. They are most definitely the future of Spain&amp;rsquo;s midfield. Gavi stood out brilliantly for his tenacity. Managed to draw fouls. Ran into space really well and even got a great goal with the outside of his foot. First Olmo scored after a good move and the ball fell to him and he scored. Asensio was next with another good bunch of passes which teed him up with a first-time shot. Later Torres slotted a penalty after Jordi Alba was tackled in the box. Next, in the second half, Torres scored after holding onto the ball for so long and managed to finish past Navas. Then it was Gavi&amp;rsquo;s outside foot volley from a Morata assist(He was shaky but got into the game well. Enrique still did the right thing benching him). Later Soler scored after Navas parried a shot right into his path and finally Morata scored after another great move. His finish was decent on his left. Good placement. I think Spain are favorites to top the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spain&#34;&gt;Spain&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../spa.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;spa.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;costa-rica&#34;&gt;Costa Rica&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../crica.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;crica.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;belgium-v-canada&#34;&gt;Belgium v Canada&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../4a71b999c9d0b2a58b89b2a31ca2ade3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;4a71b999c9d0b2a58b89b2a31ca2ade3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlucky Canada. Belgium experience shines through. Hazard rolls back the years. Take a bow Canada. 36 years since their last World Cup and they gave a good account of themselves. Belgium&amp;rsquo;s experience of being the dark horses forever in every tournament paid off as they came away with the points in this game. The game started well for Canada when they got a penalty when Carrasco handled the ball in the box after a VAR check. However, Courtois managed to save the penalty from Davies. Later on, a long ball from Alderweireld was taken well and finished by Batshuayi. After that, nothing major really happened in the game apart from a good performance from Hazard who was really decent. Both he and De Bruyne were really good as always.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;belgium&#34;&gt;Belgium&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bel.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bel.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;canada&#34;&gt;Canada&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../can.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;can.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>