<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on WC22 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on WC22 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2022 CSR</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Closing Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/final_thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/final_thoughts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;my-closing-thoughts&#34;&gt;My closing thoughts&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../320779216_2918371254962027_1029459079676825821_n.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;320779216_2918371254962027_1029459079676825821_n.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is probably the 2nd World Cup that I am properly covering. In 2014, since most matches were early in the morning I was just watching highlights at that time. I did all my posts in a notebook I set aside for 2018 actually and now I have evolved to these sites. Not a bad way to show your work isn&amp;rsquo;t it? 😂. Anyways, let&amp;rsquo;s get into this World Cup as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From off the field and in a footballing sense, this World Cup was just poorly timed and completely corrupt. I think however the final we just had completely made up for the lack of proper football in a way. We had it in the winter which is unheard of because it is usually a summer tournament but because of the country and its adverse climate we had to have it in the winter slap bang in the middle of the club season which lead to fixtures being cramped up and hardly any gap to breathe for people who watched club football. Injuries left right and center to so many key players due to the fixture congestion but on the field conditioning was a real issue for a load of teams. Despite that, there were so many upsets to talk about. Japan stood firm to beat Germany. The crazy group they were in on the final matchday was the stuff of absolute dreams. There was legit a moment where both Spain and Germany were going out and it lasted around 3 minutes. Morocco defied expectations and pushed hard all the way to 4th place. Belgium and England underperformed due to the &amp;ldquo;favorites&amp;rdquo; mania 🙄 and lack of proper mentality to fight like Croatia who gave a brilliant account of themselves by finishing 3rd after losing Mandzukic to the coaching staff. Brazil&amp;rsquo;s dance team gave us false hope after thrashing South Korea in the Round of 16 and then going on to lose on penalties. Chin up, guys, at least you made sure Argentina didn&amp;rsquo;t do the same mistake when they went to penalties against Netherlands and France 😂😂. England should have gone through but their lack of difference makers really held them back, especially against France. There were loads of stories everywhere. The unholy amount of injury time added to prevent time-wasting was actually a two-edged sword because while it exhausted players more than normal, it provided us with the big moments. Iran getting 2 quickfire goals against Wales. Netherlands pulling level after a smart freekick. I am mostly neutral about it for now and I am glad the leagues aren&amp;rsquo;t adopting it yet. The crazy end to Portugal&amp;rsquo;s group where Korea got a dramatic winner against Portugal and Ghana pulled Uruguay down with them 😂. All in all, I think this amazing final made up for the lack of proper football that was played overall. I am not taking anything away from the achievements that many people did but in a pure football sense it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t a good watch apart from the final 😂. How could anybody forget when Saudi Arabia bested Argentina and people were immediately on their case for not living up to the favorites tag? Well, the person that went viral for saying &amp;ldquo;Where&amp;rsquo;s Messi?&amp;rdquo; has become an Argentina fan so I guess it all worked out in the end as Argentina and France played out the final of the century and it ended with Messi finally winning the trophy which he came so close to winning all the way back in 2014 and putting him in a category all on his own. He has effectively completed football.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-little-note-to-the-people-who-read-these-posts&#34;&gt;A little note to the people who read these posts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started doing this all the way back before the 2014 World Cup when I ripped the covers off an old rough notebook and joined a few together to write the scorers and then it moved to write about matches a little bit and then sticking newspaper snippets into the same notebook. It got pushed to 2 notebooks which were later bound properly. It evolved to the 2018 World Cup where I set aside a separate and got more in-depth with my writing and still stuck with the newspaper clipping of the match always all the way till the final. The sites began when the Euros and Copa America came around at the same time when I learned about using Hugo(The server which is used) and Joplin(Where I write all my notes) to create a site and I started doing it for those 2 tournaments which you can find here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-2020&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Euros 2020 but happened in 2021&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://charlescsr.github.io/copa-america-2021&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Copa America 2021&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once this World Cup was planned and the dates were set I immediately got to thinking about taking my posts to the next level and that is what you see currently. When you see the 2 sites I have above you will realize how much I have changed things and how I have become way more in-depth than ever before. I hope you loved all of these notes which reported the score and also had a bit of a personal touch at the end of this great journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To all of those who read these to hear my take and the people who read these as their primary source of news:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/6tHy8UAbv3zgs/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;Thank you&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is Charles Samuel R signing off after a rather great World Cup 👋👋&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../CSR.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;CSR.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The World Cup Awards</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/wc_awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 18:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/wc_awards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-world-cup-awards&#34;&gt;The World Cup Awards&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;young-player-of-the-tournament---enzo-fernandez-argentina--benfica&#34;&gt;Young player of the tournament - Enzo Fernandez (Argentina &amp;amp; Benfica)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FkVaobfWAAAANaw.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FkVaobfWAAAANaw.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ralf found a star and United missed him and I will stay salty about it 😂 because he was suggested all the way when he was in River Plate and now Benfica have snagged him and I think he will grow more and more like he did this tournament and he will go for a massive fee in the near future for sure. He was amazing in both the CDM and CM role. It all started when I was watching his goal against Mexico on a train actually 😂. No regrets whatsoever about that. Keep growing and he&amp;rsquo;ll be the present and future of the Argentina midfield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;golden-glove-best-goalkeeper-of-the-tournament---emiliano-martinez-argentina--aston-villa&#34;&gt;Golden Glove: Best Goalkeeper of the Tournament - Emiliano Martinez (Argentina &amp;amp; Aston Villa)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../909219c40b8b4ab94e439dd8e5065eca.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;909219c40b8b4ab94e439dd8e5065eca.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weird picture aside 🤣, it is crazy to think that it all began when Maupay(A French player) injured Leno from Arsenal and up stepped Emi Martinez in his stead and since that the rest is history. He was funnily enough in the stands supporting Argentina back in 2018(He saw Caballero playing and decided to intervene 🤣). And now, he is Argentina&amp;rsquo;s starting keeper by a landslide and he backs it up with his performances as well. In penalties, he loves getting inside people&amp;rsquo;s heads to put them off. Out of Mbappe&amp;rsquo;s 3 penalties(1 in the shootout), he was close to saving 2 of them but they were really well-struck. I think his standout moment was that save one on one from Kolo Muani&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b6ffbc6f71ab698f34bd29eea2d7b515.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b6ffbc6f71ab698f34bd29eea2d7b515.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If that had gone there would have been no hope for Argentina but Martinez stood firm and also made a save in the shootout to get the honors for Argentina.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;golden-boot-for-top-scorer-in-the-world-cup---kylian-mbappe-france--psg&#34;&gt;Golden Boot for top scorer in the World Cup - Kylian Mbappe (France &amp;amp; PSG)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../6fc80ebd3467080fce36e66dba355756.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;6fc80ebd3467080fce36e66dba355756.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What a tournament from him yet again. In 2 consecutive World Cups, he has performed amazingly and almost got France over the line if not for that great Martinez save. His amazing mentality to keep a level head was absolutely amazing because I don&amp;rsquo;t think  France is getting back into it twice without him. He was a monster and he will be one of the greatest in the near future because I don&amp;rsquo;t think there is no one else who has this level of quality for both club and country. An amazing hat trick and a great tournament all around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../519d6c8b21fa2d7221a2c934b1d66dcc.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;519d6c8b21fa2d7221a2c934b1d66dcc.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He will indeed 👏&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;golden-ball-for-best-player-of-the-world-cup---lionel-messi-argentina--psg&#34;&gt;Golden Ball for best player of the World Cup - Lionel Messi (Argentina &amp;amp; PSG)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../320567925_1218140925714285_9219082089528634974_n.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;320567925_1218140925714285_9219082089528634974_n.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who bloody else for the best player of the tournament 😤. Honestly, if roles were reversed Mbappe is taking both the Golden Boot and Golden Ball but it didn&amp;rsquo;t happen and now to focus on Messi. A great start to his second season at his club PSG after a rather underwhelming first season since leaving Barca he was clicking so well with both Neymar and Mbappe and he brought that exact level of form into this tournament. He had no goals scored in the knockouts till then and now he scored 4. All the way from the Round of 16 to the final becoming the first to ever do it. Still breaking records no matter the age. Dribbling past a 20-year-old Gvardiol who was undoubtedly one of the defenders of the tournament like it was nothing. There is so much to his game and he has become the ultimate playmaker characterized perfectly by that incisive pass to Molina against the Netherlands but he has got the goals in him at times as well with great finishes against Mexico and Australia among the bunch of penalties he expertly put away given the weird nature of the ball till it was changed for the semi-finals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fair-play-award-for-least-cards---england&#34;&gt;Fair play Award for least cards - England&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../what_a_fool.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;what_a_fool.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have much for this in all honesty. Maybe they can make it a double if this award exists in the Euros in 2024 because Southgate is staying 🙄.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 29 - The Final</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_29/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-29---the-final&#34;&gt;Day 29 - The Final&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;argentina-v-france&#34;&gt;Argentina v France&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../19f7849ed8c108dfec49857d2fddabaa.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;19f7849ed8c108dfec49857d2fddabaa.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../158175ceea8cbd3d6ac82bd2019c0ff6.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;158175ceea8cbd3d6ac82bd2019c0ff6.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best-ever final of the entire World Cup. Messi and Mbappe both show their class. Messi finally finished the G.O.A.T puzzle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whoooo. WHAT. A. GAME 😱. Definitely one of the best finals in World Cup history. Had an end-to-end game with 4 goals at the end of normal time and 6 at the end of extra time. This delivered on the major clash of Messi v Mbappe a million times over and I am still not over it. Messi has finally achieved his dream and more than anything it is redemption and vindication. Let me get into what happened before telling you how I felt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Argentina started really really well. They were on the front foot and started di Maria for the final(He never scored his final goal till now 😉). He was on the left and Messi on the right and they came out swinging which was completely surprising knowing how well France normally attacks before sitting back. I think overall I think Argentina managed to score before letting France back so that was something(Even though I hated when they equalized 😅). The first goal was shrouded in a bit of controversy(Looking back on it the player actually has the slightest contact with the opponent so it is soft but a penalty) when di Maria who was so lethal on that left side terrorizing the likes of Kounde and Dembele managed to get past Dembele who clipped him slightly and it was given. It was put away by none other than Messi. With that goal, he has now become the first person to score in EVERY SINGLE KNOCKOUT GAME  from the Round of 16 to the final. 🐐 standards 😤. The second was a good ball recovery and came to Mac Allister who managed to get in behind and tee up di Maria who finally chipped in with his final goal 😂. I think he has scored now in all the finals where Messi has won an international trophy. The Copa America in 2021. The Finalissima this year and now the World Cup. What a way to bow out of the national team Angel 😭. Your experience will definitely be missed. The first half ended and France was looking down and out because they had&amp;hellip;0 shots. Yes, that is right. No shots whatsoever from them all through the first half. Mbappe and Theo Hernandez were marked down well by both Molina and de Paul and Giroud was so isolated that even Romero helped cover on the left and Griezmann didn&amp;rsquo;t look the same on the pitch too. There were early first-half subs made by France and Mbappe moved centrally to have a bigger threat with his pace with Kolo Muani and Thuram coming on as wingers. The second half began and Argentina suddenly was slowly going on the back foot. THEN. KYLIAN MBAPPE ARRIVED 😰. 97 seconds. That&amp;rsquo;s all it took for Kylian Mbappe to level the game. First Kolo Muani was sent through and was fouled by Otamendi and Mbappe buried the pen with amazing power which couldn&amp;rsquo;t be stopped by Martinez. The next goal was absolutely pure quality. I have no words to describe it. The balls he had to try that lofted pass on the volley first time. It was amazing. It all started however with Messi getting dispossessed by Coman before a few passes and Thuram finally lofted it up for Mbappe on the volley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../69ced148c9890bf15dbe8376894c83eb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;69ced148c9890bf15dbe8376894c83eb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/BXJ9o9cTWQX5IqR1uW/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;Mbappe Brilliance&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will definitely say something about him in a separate passage after covering the whole match. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry about that. They did do a switch to an attacking 3 back. Meanwhile, Argentina only made a single change bringing Acuna on for di Maria. France definitely had so many chances to nick it in the end but Argentina held on for extra time. Also of note was a Messi piledriver before the end which was parried well by Lloris (90+6). Montiel was later on brought on in extra time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking it at overall it was rather level. France did have lots of attacking threat but Argentina wasn&amp;rsquo;t always defending and they found spaces to attack as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The story of extra time was Lautaro Martinez. You may be Serie A&amp;rsquo;s biggest marksman but you were definitely the reincarnation of Higuain from 2014 🤦‍♂. Where do I begin? He was brought on along with Paredes for Alvarez and de Paul respectively. He misses a chance to put Argentina through in minute 104 when Messi ran through and teed him up only to hit a sliding Upamecano before Montiel&amp;rsquo;s shot was deflected by Varane. Next, an outside-the-boot pass from Acuna sent Lautaro through and he completely fluffed it(Although that actually should have been a corner since the last touch was by Upamecano) in minute 105. Moving to the second half of extra time. In minute 108, the breakthrough comes after a long ball from Montiel was cushioned by Lautaro for Messi who passed to Fernandez and passed it back to Lautaro beautifully whose shot hit Lloris and Messi was on hand to hit the rebound home. It was cleared but the watch said enough to give it. He was finally back level with Mbappe in the Golden Boot. They had the lead finally. Argentina quickly shifted to a back 5 by bringing on Pezzella for Mac Allister(who has had a brilliant tournament overall 👏 and an assist in the final). Later on, however, disaster struck when Mbappe&amp;rsquo;s shot from the corner struck Montiel on the arm and it was just below the elbow and on the actual arm and so it was given. Mbappe managed to send Emi Martinez the wrong way this time to complete a WORLD CUP FINAL HATTRICK. The last person to do that was Geoff Hurst all the way back in 1966. It&amp;rsquo;s only them both who have scored a hat trick in the finals. Just saddened it ended the way it did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next came the moment that for sure defined the World Cup final because it was absolutely crucial and if France had got their way, they would have won back-to-back World Cups. Minute 119 should have been on target at the very least when Mbappe&amp;rsquo;s cross found Kolo Muani but he hardly had much contact and it was wide. He, later on, got an ABSOLUTELY GOLDEN CHANCE to give France the cup when a long ball from defense found him and was misjudged by the defender which meant Kolo Muani was one on one with Emi Martinez and he managed to save it. It was an absolutely crucial save and was well done. He made himself big and reduced the space to aim at. That resulted in a counter from Argentina when Messi was through on the right and his cross went begging by none other than&amp;hellip;yep you guessed it Lautaro BLOODY Martinez 😠. Mbappe had another chance which he created on his own and if he did score I would have been so angry at Lautaro. Thankfully the scenario never happened. A long ball found Mbappe and he managed to twist past 1, 2, and 3 but the fourth managed to clear it. It was a combination of Enzo disrupting Mbappe and Dybala clearing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This meant yet another penalty shootout but there was a problem for France. Mbappe and Thuram were probably the only competent penalty-takers on the team since the likes of Giroud, Griezmann, and Rabiot were all off the field now. It was kind of weird and Argentina had the likes of Lautaro(I know he isn&amp;rsquo;t the best finisher but he did score the winning pen against the Dutch), Dybala, Montiel and obviously Messi. Mbappe was on target yet again. Martinez guessed right but it was struck powerfully yet again. Messi made no mistake and made Lloris dive the wrong way(Although he almost got back to try and save it 😅). Next up, Coman for France and his penalty was saved by Martinez. Dybala, later on, made no mistake going down the middle. The next set was Tchouameni and Paredes where the former dragged his shot wide(E. Martinez got into his head 🤣) and the latter buried his kick. Last set was Kolo Muani and Montiel. Kolo hit a good pen and scored but Montiel managed to score to trigger the celebrations. Messi has done it 😭. The final piece of his elite G.O.A.T jigsaw is complete after a long time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../320432139_1579220789184932_8874365840387848886_n.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;320432139_1579220789184932_8874365840387848886_n.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/VgwxeVqfg0qtALwINW/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;The moment&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-final-lineups-of-the-world-cup&#34;&gt;The Final lineups of the World Cup&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_finals.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_finals.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra_finals.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra_finals.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;lionel-andres-messi&#34;&gt;Lionel Andres Messi&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../320489457_195090603100868_7252177604779913634_n.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;320489457_195090603100868_7252177604779913634_n.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has finally done it Diego (Maradona). He has finally done it. For me, It all started when I was playing an FC Barcelona career mode with him in FIFA 11 on a PSP and I was immediately hooked even though the first ever match I watched wasn&amp;rsquo;t your match(Manchester derby 2012), it was the second match I ever saw (2-2 El Clasico 2012 where you scored twice and Ronaldo did the very same). I was hooked by how easy you made football look. The way you used your low center of gravity to keep the ball glued to you and make situations either happen or you make a goal out of nothing. You have been out of this world from the moment you stepped in as a sub under Rijkaard and never looked back. It was meant to be a great love story of you and FC Barcelona but it didn&amp;rsquo;t last 😢. Later on, came the comparisons to Diego Maradona when you showed up for your national team. You had the chance of eternal glory in 2014 when you pulled them all the way to the final but it didn&amp;rsquo;t happen with Mario Gotze being the difference. Copa America and the Centenario. 2 finals yet again to win something for the nation and both of them ended in heartbreak in the absolute worst way possible with both being penalty shootout heartbreak. The voices started getting louder and louder: &amp;ldquo;CaN&amp;rsquo;T WiN AnYtHiNg fOr hIs nAtIoNaL TeAm&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;MaRaDoNa wOn a wOrLd cUp. WhAt hAvE YoU WoN?&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;BeEn tO 3 FiNaLs aNd cAn&amp;rsquo;t eVeN WiN OnE Of tHeM&amp;rdquo;. The voices were too much at one point. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand it because he did so much for them to even be at that place. He did leave for a while but came back and came back for a vengeance. 2018 just wasn&amp;rsquo;t meant to be after going out to France. 2022 was a breakthrough year. Fresh after winning his first-ever trophy with the Copa America last year, the pressure was finally off. He won a major tournament for his country besting one of their bitter rivals in Brazil. Next was the Finalissima beating the Euros winners in Italy convincingly. Now he was on a mission to get the final piece. This time, he went all the way and now more than ever has established himself as immortal. He has won every possible trophy in football. You have completed football pretty much 😂. More than anything, I feel vindicated by your redemption. The voices have been quietened down. Wonder why? 😜&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221210_113316_Instagram.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221210_113316_Instagram.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, your recent statement as well saying that you want to continue makes me happy too. Long may it continue. Lionel Messi everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;kylian-mbappe&#34;&gt;Kylian Mbappe&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../6168a030f8bad5f870537d1380f79b8b.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;6168a030f8bad5f870537d1380f79b8b.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honestly, hand on heart take a bow man. The next generation is headed by you and no one else. I don&amp;rsquo;t think Haaland can conjure a miracle with Norway anytime soon so you are on your own planet in this new generation. Insane to think that at 23 you have hit 12 goals already. I think Klose&amp;rsquo;s record can be shattered by you easily. Being that young and having such a massive winning mentality because if not for you I think France would be dropping more and more in morale. He was unlucky he didn&amp;rsquo;t have that many good penalty kick takers and most of those who do take them were subbed off sadly but he still never gave it up. Once you moved centrally you were more and more creative. Buried the penalty to give a bit of hope. Then a moment of absolute pure quality to equalize it. And you did it twice as well. It was mostly Mbappe against Argentina. You scored a damn hat trick in a World Cup final. Only one other person did that before you. Serious serious baller. You got mostly 1.5 decades left easily.  As much as I bash your ego, you have an amazing mentality. Let me show some stats:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 goals in 14 World Cup games (The highest ever is 16)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only the second player to score a hattrick in the final&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Almost led France to back to back titles since Italy(1934 &amp;amp; 1938) and Brazil(1958 &amp;amp; 1962)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of this at 23 just shows how bright of a future he&amp;rsquo;s got. I am looking forward to what you can achieve. Mbappe. Definitely one of the main men of this newer generation so to speak 👏.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;world-cup-awards-and-my-closing-thoughts-coming-in-a-few-hours-&#34;&gt;World Cup Awards and my closing thoughts coming in a few hours 😉&lt;/h1&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 28 - Third Place Game</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-28&#34;&gt;Day 28&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;croatia-v-morocco---third-place-game&#34;&gt;Croatia v Morocco - Third Place game&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../49c6db3fe0ff795fc666102e8c2ef46b.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;49c6db3fe0ff795fc666102e8c2ef46b.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Craziest first 10 minutes ever. Orsic special the difference maker. Modric bows out in style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first half was probably the major half in terms of chances and all that cause we had a bright bright start to it in 10 minutes. Croatia first got the lead through Gvardiol when a freekick was looped in and Perisic gave a good header towards him and he managed to throw himself to give the lead. However, just a minute or two later, Morocco found an equalizer from a similar situation 😅 when Ziyech floated in the freekick and it was deflected before Dari who was completely unmarked and managed to get the header in. What a way to begin this match. Later on, the breakthrough came after a moment of brilliance from Orsic when Livaja teed him up and he curled in a brilliant strike in off the post from an impossible angle(All through this tournament I swear this guy is a cut inside and inshallah merchant 😂 and this time it actually worked). After this, Croatia and Morocco had decent chances but Morocco could have used En-Nesyri better because he was very isolated. He did get a cross finally to hit but it was wide(Like why didn&amp;rsquo;t you give him more of that. He can jump as shown against Portugal 🤦‍♂️). In the end, it was a great sendoff for 37-year-old Luka Modric who has played quite possibly his last game for his country at the World Cup at least. What a mentality. What a player. Running the midfield show really well at that age isn&amp;rsquo;t easy but he made it look really easy which was amazing to see. He will definitely be in the leagues of Xavi and Iniesta(That&amp;rsquo;s coming from me an FC Barcelona fan who loved the Xavi, Iniesta era) as one of the greatest midfielders ever. He managed to win the biggest ever individual achievement ever one year for crying out loud: The Ballon d&amp;rsquo;Or. You did a very admirable job of carrying Croatia to 2nd last time and bringing them to 3rd place now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro_third.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro_third.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor_4th.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor_4th.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Cup Final Preview - Argentina v France</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/final_preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 04:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/final_preview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;argentina-v-france-preview&#34;&gt;Argentina v France Preview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../82903805e126c485b97eeb0c2dfaabb6.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;82903805e126c485b97eeb0c2dfaabb6.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is it. We have our 2 finalists. Argentina: Copa America and Finalissima winners and France: Defending Champions who have broken the status quo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;will-it-be-revenge-and-redemption-for-messi-and-argentina-or-will-mbappe-and-france-completely-shatter-the-defending-champions-curse&#34;&gt;Will it be revenge and redemption for Messi and Argentina or will Mbappe and France completely shatter the defending champions curse????&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As much as France have been great it hasn&amp;rsquo;t gone unnoticed that they have become more pragmatic towards the end of the knockouts. They have good attacking spells don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong. Against England, we saw it when they got back in front. It will all rely on a moment. It was more evident against Morocco when they took the lead so early and they just sat back and let Morocco attack and attack. They hit on the counter usually and managed to get a second. The lack of clinical finishing from Morocco helped even more. This fixture was played in the Round of 16 in the last World Cup and this was the score:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../731c99290606db26d1002e50b5953d41.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;731c99290606db26d1002e50b5953d41.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mind you Argentina had a way worse defense back then with the likes of Rojo and GK in Armani too and the midfield had Ever bloody Banega(He was decent-ish but has faded into obscurity. That&amp;rsquo;s all I&amp;rsquo;ll say). Aguero was benched and he almost pulled the game into extra time despite the fact they conceded 4. He scored one and missed a great chance to draw level. Argentina did huff and puff a lot after the 4 goals from France and almost came back. Shades of that same thinking have surfaced now it is seeming like. But now, both teams are at their absolute peak as well. Great players in each and every position. It will be hard to call. Like all great finals, it will rely on a moment of magic. Will it come from the nimble Messi or will it come from speedy Mbappe? We will find out. My guess on a scoreline is 2-1. Argentina scoring will push France to equalize and a moment of magic decides the World Cup and Messi retires with a World Cup 😆. Yes, I am an Argentina and Messi fan. Ever since I played a Barcelona career mode on a PSP I have been supporting him ever since so sue me 😂. If this win does happen. He will be virtually untouchable. That is mad to think about 😱. Honestly, it could go either way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-to-watch-for&#34;&gt;What to watch for&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mbappe v Molina and T. Hernandez v Messi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../IMG_20221216_122357.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;IMG_20221216_122357.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../IMG_20221216_122444.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;IMG_20221216_122444.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People think this is a normal matchup always and if the lineup goes like usual this is going to be interesting to watch. Not just because it is a match-up of quality. But also because both the wingers on that side will not track back. They usually don&amp;rsquo;t track back 😅. Mbappe on the left and Messi on the right. You see where I am going with this. Molina and Theo will have the big task of neutralizing their opposite marks. Molina especially with Mbappe&amp;rsquo;s reliance on his pace. Hernandez with Messi&amp;rsquo;s bag of tricks and sudden burst of speed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;lineups&#34;&gt;Lineups&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am mostly thinking both coaches will go for the same lineups that worked for them in their respective semi-finals. France with their usual 4-2-3-1 and Argentina with a 4-4-2 but maybe with wingers instead of the 4-man midfield but with the likes of Griezmann running all over the pitch along with Tchouameni and Fofana(Maybe Rabiot will be back by then. We don&amp;rsquo;t know). Alvarez will definitely keep his spot after his 2 goals and Messi will supplement him from out wide and central at times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_maybe.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_maybe.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was slightly seen in the semi-final when Mac Allister drifted wide and Messi dropped back to be on the right primarily and a 3-man midfield which was highly defensive and Enzo Fernandez will be the person to drive the ball forward and pick a pass. So I am going for something similar. Something that could be worth a shout is maybe Di Maria for the RW to support Molina and keep Messi up front like a CAM or second striker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra_maybe.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra_maybe.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fairly similar to their semi-final lineup and Griezmann could very well be at CM, CDM and CAM because he was everywhere(Griezmannkante as Pogba called him 😂) It is a hard lineup to face and with the pace provided by both Mbappe and Dembele the cross is very certain and with Giroud as the target man he won&amp;rsquo;t miss for the national team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-the-third-place-game&#34;&gt;About the third-place game&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If both teams are willing to give a good go at it, we could see a good game. Maybe Croatia could get it done due to the quality of their midfield and also it being Modric&amp;rsquo;s last game for his country quite possibly. Other than that I don&amp;rsquo;t see any standout moments.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 25</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-25&#34;&gt;Day 25&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;france-v-morocco&#34;&gt;France v Morocco&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../53245aabb6c655a2037956b25b14928b.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;53245aabb6c655a2037956b25b14928b.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holders make it easy. Morocco misfire. Mbappe v Messi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Easy game for France. Harder for Morocco because they actually finally conceded playing the same park-the-bus tactics(Love to see it shatter immediately when a goal goes in because it makes you look like a proper idiot 🤣). It completely shifted both teams&#39; game plans. France started sitting back which was pretty similar to England now that I think about it 🤔. They sat back and England attacked hard and got that penalty. They switched on and got the second and then sat back again allowing England to attack again and again. We got a sense of deja vu when the first goal went in from Theo Hernandez(I feel bad that he is balling out so hard at his brother&amp;rsquo;s expense 😅 but sometimes you have to take your chance and he has brilliantly even with that brain fart against England 😬). Morocco decided to go on the offensive even more so after their captain Saiss couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue(This is what happens when you risk their fitness like it&amp;rsquo;s nothing 🤦‍♂️). Aguerd, Saiss and Mazraoui were the main talking points due to their fitness and in the end, Aguerd didn&amp;rsquo;t start, Saiss and Mazraoui came off and they had to chase the game without their main defenders. Sorry for getting sidetracked. The first goal. Griezmann manages to get behind the 5 man wall and got the cross in which was defended but Mbappe tried a shot that looped up and Theo Hernandez was there to meet it on a half-flying volley. After this, it was a Morocco onslaught and France only countered. It was evident Saiss couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue when Giroud latched onto a through ball and managed to get the shot away. He just stopped running. So he was brought off for a midfielder which meant them switching to a back 4 system. The rest of the story before the second goal was mostly Morocco attacking hard but having no finishing touch. There was one bicycle attempt from one of the CBs El Yamiq from a corner and it hit the post and En-Nesyri was static for the ball. Ounahi was someone who had a rather decent game and he had a shot from range that was parried well by Lloris. The second goal was scored by a sub who was on for&amp;hellip;..44 seconds 😱. Absolutely insane. Kolo Muani was called up as a replacement for Nkunku who got injured before this tournament and he was at the right place at the right time. Mbappe was sent through and he managed to twist and turn past so much of Morocco&amp;rsquo;s backline before hitting the pass which was bundled in by an unmarked Kolo Muani. What a time to score your first international goal. After that, it was just defense defense defense from France and they held on. Konate was really solid alongside Varane compared to Upamecano who was shaky. They had him and Rabiot unavailable due to a virus from the news so Konate and Fofana were brought in. Griezmann was virtually everywhere in the midfield and this renaissance is amazing to see from him after his failed spell at FC Barcelona. We have a showdown of the PSG teammates: Messi v Mbappe. Morocco I love your achievement of making it this far but I absolutely ABHOR your tactics and I am glad you weren&amp;rsquo;t there to bore the final out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;preview-of-the-france-v-argentina-game-tomorrow-&#34;&gt;Preview of the France v Argentina game tomorrow 🤩&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra_semi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra_semi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor_semi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor_semi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 24</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-24&#34;&gt;Day 24&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;3-day-break-before-the-semi-finals&#34;&gt;3-day break before the semi-finals&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;argentina-v-croatia&#34;&gt;Argentina v Croatia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../2a16c9b30d5cb2bd139f24a923096e87.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;2a16c9b30d5cb2bd139f24a923096e87.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Messi messes up Gvardiol. Alvarez the new frontman. Lack of attack becomes Croatia&amp;rsquo;s undoing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was indeed pretty nervous thinking about this game due to Croatia&amp;rsquo;s ability to hold teams to a shootout but in the end, it was relatively easy. The surprising spaces being left from the start were exploited easily by the Argentina players(The manager going for a 4-man midfield to hold Croatia which was executed well). Molina and Tagliafico were the main threats compared to Mac Allister and de Paul. The spaces were evident and the first goal came from a penalty when Alvarez was found in loads of space and he managed to latch on and nudged it past Livakovic who was caught out and tackled him. There were significant protests. From my point of view, Alvarez did run into him but the keeper was unlucky in the end because he didn&amp;rsquo;t get the ball. Hence the stonewall penalty which Messi put away with ease and with that he has drawn level with his PSG teammate Mbappe. He is on a mission. To make sure his last World Cup will be a memorable one and that it will end with the trophy in his arms(Hopefully 🤞). In all the heated conversations between the Croatia players and the referee, Mandzukic was sent off 😅. I swear I forgot that Mandzukic was part of the coaching staff. Croatia is missing a player of your caliber mate and it was even more obvious in this match. Kramaric loved dropping deep too much, Petkovic was hardly able to twist and turn because of the lack of space and also the fact that this isn&amp;rsquo;t extra time 😉. The second goal was all Julian Alvarez. He has become the main frontman for them after Lautaro&amp;rsquo;s quite frankly horror show in this tournament and he&amp;rsquo;s delivering big time. This was a result of a corner gone wrong and Messi managed to carry it far before sending Alvarez through who went all the way from just behind the center circle all the way and scored. He managed to get a few 1-2s from the Croatian defenders before poking it past Livakovic. Croatia just didn&amp;rsquo;t have the attacking quality to fight back. Even though they pushed well in possession with their midfield, they just had no one to play to in the box because Kramaric was busy playing CAM like a certain Harry Kane 😑. Petkovic came on and hardly had any room because the coach decided to shore up on defense with Lisandro Martinez coming in. Perisic was so lonely he was pushed to LB because it was getting worse. The 3rd goal was from Alvarez again but all eyes were on that Messi assist because it was just vintage Messi. He absolutely OWNED one of the defenders of the tournament with that dribble. It was unbelievable. He is towards the right side. Closed down by Gvardiol. He just uses a burst of pace and uses all of his experience and dribbling to completely OWN him before supplying the ball for Alvarez who didn&amp;rsquo;t miss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/WPxtQiXaVHCcKaMF5g/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;Vintage_Messi&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a spectacle I was so happy to watch happen live 😄.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_semi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_semi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro_semi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro_semi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 21</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-21&#34;&gt;Day 21&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;morocco-v-portugal-and-england-v-france&#34;&gt;Morocco v Portugal and England v France&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../4e8cf446d59588bdf3a16301382e2690.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;4e8cf446d59588bdf3a16301382e2690.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../adc1c53397a2e3640fdc12583c02cfda.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;adc1c53397a2e3640fdc12583c02cfda.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 games that were actually settled in normal time. Surprisingly normal 😅. One was decided by a major error by the keeper otherwise it would have gone to penalties yet again. The second game was just well managed by France because England hardly had any open play chances and the one chance they had to equalize the second time Kane managed to bottle it. The second semi-final is now Morocco v France. The major matchup there is definitely going to be Hakimi v Mbappe but injuries to their backline are going to be hampering them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Major Costa error costs Portugal. Being pragmatic wins you games: This World Cup in a nutshell. Morocco history makers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morocco have become the first African nation to get into the semi-finals of the World Cup. A huge huge achievement from them and it was finished in normal time instead of penalties because of one Diogo Costa error. In the knockouts doing an error that big is inexcusable. The cross comes in and Costa massively misjudges the cross leaving En-Nesyri with an open net giving Morocco the lead. After that, it was chance after chance from Portugal. There didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be enough that were clear-cut chances. Ramos was isolated and hardly could do much(Ronaldo would have been criticized for that 😂 and yes he was benched again along with Cancelo). Felix had 1 chance but it was heavily deflected. He was rather decent actually with the second being a great setup and his left-footed shot was saved well by Bono. Later on, seeing the talent come on with the likes of Leao, Ronaldo, Cancelo and so on, Morocco moved to their trusty 5 at the back formation which had to happen after Romain Saiss their captain couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue further. Portugal tried everything. Chance after chance came and the passes were just misplaced due to the anxiety. And finally, it signaled the end of the road for Portugal. A vastly talented team with experience and youth but have been felled by what is Africa&amp;rsquo;s best team currently. It may also appear to be the end of the road for Cristiano Ronaldo at least in his international career which is just annoying. The smallest of errors lead to this and it is gut-wrenching in general to see this happen. This is one trophy and medal that will forever elude him in what has been an illustrious career. Morocco is on par with Croatia with their resilience for sure. They will not be shaken. In terms of attack, they had to be penned back due to Portugal constantly applying pressure but they managed to hold on. Saiss had a warriors performance despite his leg being heavily bandaged but had to come off eventually. Bono was a rock as always. One stupid moment was the substitute ST who came on. He got a yellow card for a bad challenge and immediately went and made another one and got himself sent off. Hakimi managed to hold on with Leao but Ziyech eventually had to track back and help. In terms of injuries, Saiss and Aguerd are out and so is Ziyech after he had to come off as well. As a certain Mr. Peter Drury put it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../08cb9fb8d867f0f961b211789f77f613.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;08cb9fb8d867f0f961b211789f77f613.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../por_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;por_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ENGLAND&amp;rsquo;S GOING HOME. ENGLAND&amp;rsquo;S GOING HOME. ENGLAND&amp;rsquo;S GOING HOME. 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣👋👋👋👋👋👋👋👋👋&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the first time since I think 1990 the defending champion and runner-up of the previous World Cup have made it into the semi-final of the World Cup now. This was a pretty decent performance from France apart from some shaky moments. England went with the wrong system and the wrong mentality. I strictly said if England doesn&amp;rsquo;t push from the get-go they can get overrun and they did. The beginning stage was all France and the breakthrough came from Tchouameni with a great strike after a little space opened up. It went through Bellingham&amp;rsquo;s legs and past an outstretched Pickford(Maybe a taller keeper like an in-form Ramsdale could have made a difference but he isn&amp;rsquo;t part of the FaVoRiTeS 🙄 because it was saveable being towards the bottom corner). Once France scored, there was a momentum shift as England remembered to suddenly play because they went a goal down and they were pushing but there was not any open play chance created from them throughout the game even if they had the momentum from scoring the penalty. Yes in the second half a penalty was given when Saka(England&amp;rsquo;s best player by a landslide and he gets subbed off 🤦) was fouled in the box and Kane stepped up to score it past his club teammate. With that goal, he has drawn level with Wayne Rooney as England&amp;rsquo;s all-time leading goal scorer. After that France managed to have it handled well because of a lack of a CAM like how Griezmann is for France Kane dropped back way too deep and Southgate didn&amp;rsquo;t trust the likes of Rashford, Maddison and so on to make the difference which it could have. England did have a second penalty but France did give a response back. Giroud missed a great chance from the cross and only put his effort close to Pickford who made a straightforward save and managed to score after a corner after said chance with the cross coming in from Griezmann and his header being on point as always. The second penalty for England was given after a VAR review when Mount was barged off by Theo Hernandez. It was a brain fart from the latter. But Kane could not bring them back in a second time as his shot sailed well over the bar. Since Theo did an NFL-style challenge on Mount, Kane decided to show his NFL side by blasting it home for the bonus point 🤣. Unfortunately, this is not the NFL Harry 🤣🤣🤣🤣. Everyone knows this ball is light. Why you went for it like that I will never know. After this England just didn&amp;rsquo;t have an answer after that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🎵They&amp;rsquo;re going home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re going home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re going&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;England&amp;rsquo;s going home🎵🤣👋&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;england&#34;&gt;England&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../eng_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;eng_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;gareth-southgate&#34;&gt;Gareth Southgate&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../2b0370b011943c8495a71ab72dd4bded.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;2b0370b011943c8495a71ab72dd4bded.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonjour Monsieur Boregate 🤣. The first major test and you have fallen. The World Cup was supposed to begin in the quarter-finals for yall and well I see that you have immediately gone 😂. From the start, the mentality and the system were all wrong. Given the talent is equal between England and France it would have been better to just replicate the same system as France. Griezmann had so much space and was really influential despite you having 3 midfielders 🤦. Kane dropped deep because the midfield couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite get the ball to him. When he did, there was no one in the box to aim at for the wingers and even if the wingers did cut inside they would be easily stopped by the defense and they had no one to also feed in because Kane would be all the way at the halfway line 🙄. The pace was needed and Kane is NEVER EVER going to provide that. Saka was your best player and you bring on Sterling who went through a damn burglary and had to go back to England and come back in. The favoritism has to stop mate. Rashford was in great form and he does not bring him in. I think an in-form Maddison would have made a better difference than Mount in all honesty. From the damn FaVoRiTeS gang to the bad squad choices and stubbornness, you have proved time and time again that you are not the right man to lead this great generation of talent. Misusing the likes of Foden(Pep gets the best out of him week in and week out), Rashford(EtH has got the best out of him and is in great form), Maddison(No minutes whatsoever which is just plain sad). You missed a CAM today and that cost you badly. You only started attacking after Tchouameni&amp;rsquo;s great strike. Just having a happy team is not enough FYI. You actually have to have a decent game plan of attack. Without a CAM, what were you even thinking? Why in the world were you relying on Kane who is a bloody STRIKER BTW for your linkup? It made defending a piece of cake for Varane and Upamecano. This was how you were playing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../what_a_fool.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;what_a_fool.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wingers looking up couldn&amp;rsquo;t see their target man ST which was absolutely hilarious to watch 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So with the utmost respect(which is virtually not much), I am saying to you and your bunch of FaVoRiTeS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/9u4TXfoIM7wQHnfR1p/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;So Long&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-final-four&#34;&gt;THE FINAL FOUR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../6ea0053ef4c00079faa89326a269cfb3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;6ea0053ef4c00079faa89326a269cfb3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 20</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-20&#34;&gt;Day 20&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2-day-break-after-the-round-of-16&#34;&gt;2 day break after the Round of 16&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;quarter-finals&#34;&gt;Quarter Finals&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;croatia-v-brazil-and-argentina-v-netherlands&#34;&gt;Croatia v Brazil and Argentina v Netherlands&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../6a69b541804b632154b59d31141edd12.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;6a69b541804b632154b59d31141edd12.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b2e463e7fafc2d48df423d7c6ced8d8b.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b2e463e7fafc2d48df423d7c6ced8d8b.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b82708c33fc8fbf32b0c2613eda27f9c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b82708c33fc8fbf32b0c2613eda27f9c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../e30eece2bb06bff87cd723c6fef752c7.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;e30eece2bb06bff87cd723c6fef752c7.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am writing this just after the heartbreak. While it is still raw. I am just not interested at all in seeing that sad excuse of a game from Brazil again. Just when I had hoped these guys could go all the way to the final, they had to ruin it. The second was heated, to say the least. We have a Croatia v Argentina showdown. 2 teams who are good at penalty shootouts will face off 😬. Argentina will have to be alert and try to get the game done and dusted and defend like crazy to prevent Croatia from coming back and make sure their lack of attacking threat is neutralized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Croatia hold on again. Build Livakovic a damn statue. Brazil just could not hold onto the ball&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brazil went into the game as favorites as we all know but Croatia played for a penalty shootout from the get-go. Trust me it was such an annoying watch. Chances were not as clear cut for Brazil and the chances that they did get Livakovic managed to save them all. The breakthrough came in extra time because before that in normal time Brazil would attack, and Croatia would defend and slow the game down. Juranovic and Gvardiol were on it throughout the whole 120. But surely I think this should be taking a toll. I know in 2018 they did 2 consecutive shootouts and were off the pace for France but maybe they could do the business if they keep this park-the-bus mentality. I think the problem with Croatia in normal time is they are missing a Mandzukic type ST badly and the likes of Kramaric just ain&amp;rsquo;t cutting it. They did bring on Petkovic for the ET period but he was starved of service for so long. The first goal was a moment of pure pure quality. Neymar passes it quickly and gets the ball in the box, quickly dribbles past Livakovic and manages to score. With that, he has equaled Pele as Brazil&amp;rsquo;s all-time top goal scorer. A truly amazing achievement and something that goes under the radar of all the criticism he always gets. I am sad for him especially considering the loss and this is yet again another failure for the national team to show promise but flounder when the chips are down. Now somehow Neymar is going to get the brunt of the fire from the media despite literally giving them hope. Croatia leveled when Brazil were caught out on the right side (It didn&amp;rsquo;t feel right that Paqueta had to play deep with Casemiro. Maybe a Bruno G could have been the more ideal player&amp;hellip;? We will never know) and Orsic crossed the ball in and Petkovic took the shot which I think if not for the right leg of Marquinhos Alisson would be saving that. The deflection takes it just beyond his reach. Fred was rather dreadful coming on. Thought he would be energetic but he got outran by Modric who was there FOR THE ENTIRE DAMN GAME. Penalties came and Livakovic saved Rodrygo&amp;rsquo;s penalty and Marquinhos hit the post to send Croatia through. Alisson saved a grand total of&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;0 penalties 😑. Neymar can&amp;rsquo;t catch a break 😥.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;brazil&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bra_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bra_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have finally seen the passion that many are trying to suppress. Messi masterclass yet again. Netherlands plays the ultimate bore game to force extra time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The single most heated game of this World Cup. This is what we always wanted to see. Passion and a little bit of fight. This is what the modern game is missing badly. I also think the referee was shambolic for both sides in all honesty. Both sides had the same formation to defend hard. Netherlands however did not have Messi and that was a major difference. For ALLLLL THE SMACK the fans, media and Van Gaal spoke about Messi being finished. Where are ya&amp;rsquo;ll now? 🖐️😤🖐️.  The first goal was from a beautiful defense-splitting pass by Messi to Molina who managed to score. That pass was the best I have ever seen. Nobody expected it. That is Messi for you 🐐. The first half had a few chances but nothing stood out apart from that amazing Messi assist for Molina. The second half began and there was a chance to make it 2-0 when Acuna was tripped by Dumfries. It was soft but the contact was there and it was given. Messi managed to score it with conviction by wrong-footing Noppert. Later on, Netherlands finally decided to play even more boring football 🥱 by bringing on the likes of Luuk de Jong and Wout Weghorst, the latter inspiring a star turn for the Dutch. Basically, Netherlands played a version I like to call &amp;ldquo;Cross and Inshallah&amp;rdquo;. It managed to work due to the lack of proper height in the defense apart from Romero. Weghorst managed to score after a cross from Berghuis. The bounce before coming to the keeper was the deciding factor. There was a moment that broke out when Paredes clattered Gakpo and later fired the ball straight at the Dutch bench and it kicked off a flurry of players rushing onto the pitch. This match saw a record 17 yellow cards alone. You can find the cards below. The second goal was smart. That is all I&amp;rsquo;ll give to the Dutch. It was a sloppy free kick conceded by Pezzella(Why did Romero have to come off ??🤦‍♂️). The freekick was smartly taken by Koopmeiners to Weghorst who managed to turn quickly and managed to slot it past E. Martinez. Going to extra time, 2 major chances were there for both L. Martinez and Fernandez. The former&amp;rsquo;s shot was deflected by van Dijk and the latter hit the bottom of the left post towards the end of extra time. The shootout came. E. Martinez made 2 great saves from van Dijk and Berghuis. The only miss from Argentina was by Fernandez who dragged his shot wide of the post he hit 😑. Finally, it was down to Lautaro Martinez to send them through after Weghorst, L. de Jong and Koopmeiners scored for the Dutch and he did not miss. With that I would like to say with absolutely no shame: &amp;ldquo;BYE BYE NETHERLANDS 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣. AIRPORT IS THAT WAY 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣&amp;rdquo;. This is all of the Argentina and Messi fans right now:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221210_113316_Instagram.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221210_113316_Instagram.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-cards&#34;&gt;The cards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a4742252c409391d4ae0f8798bfe478f.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a4742252c409391d4ae0f8798bfe478f.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;netherlands&#34;&gt;Netherlands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ned_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ned_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 17</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-17&#34;&gt;Day 17&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;end-of-round-of-16&#34;&gt;End of Round of 16&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;morocco-v-spain-and-portugal-v-switzerland&#34;&gt;Morocco v Spain and Portugal v Switzerland&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../48961dfb1505b3c88b4c91ffdacac703.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;48961dfb1505b3c88b4c91ffdacac703.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../0fdfc36a3c26d033847ba9fa251f9571.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;0fdfc36a3c26d033847ba9fa251f9571.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../e9f5878658756083930bbbe6c084406c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;e9f5878658756083930bbbe6c084406c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have found our dark horses of this tournament. Ronaldo was dropped but was happy with the team&amp;rsquo;s performance.  His replacement takes the headlines. We have the last quarter-final which is going to be between Morocco and Portugal. Morocco knocking out Spain yet again(They lost to Russia in a PK shootout last WC 🤭). Portugal outplay Switzerland and Ramos was at the center of it all. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morocco withstand Spain easily. Spain had no urgency. Hakimi as cool as can be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was completely embarrassing from Spain. Major major kudos to Morocco for managing to hold on. Spain honestly had just one trick and that was to make sure they just passed and passed and passed us allllll to 😴.  Morocco was also fairly threatening with the likes of Boufal especially. Amrabat was solid as a wall in the midfield holding back the likes of Pedri and Gavi. I think in a situation like this the experience of De Gea(He may not be a sweeper yet but at least he is one of the best shot-stoppers there is), Ramos(Laporte had a chance at the very end of the 90 minutes but completely miscued it. Ramos would have been on the end of it) and they looked lost with just Busquets on the field(Like seriously Enrique just stop being so arrogant and stubborn). Enrique made the players take 1000 penalties. Hah. Guessing they missed all of them because they didn&amp;rsquo;t score a SINGLE one in this shootout. Sarabia had the chance of a lifetime. He was brought on for the shootout and almost won the game at the end of extra time but his shot grazed the left post. He felt hard done by that so he decided to hit the right post in the shootout 🤦‍♂. Unless Enrique stops being stubborn and does not utilize the experience they have and groom the right players for each position they ain&amp;rsquo;t going far. Hakimi was born and brought up in Spain and could have played for them. In the end, he decided to score the winning penalty(A panenka no less 😱) to knock Spain out and he did Ramos&#39; penguin celebration for good measure. Bono also deserves the rightful shout for making 2 saves in this shootout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spain&#34;&gt;Spain&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../spa_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;spa_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goncalo Ramos center stage. Ronaldo dropped but was not fazed. Switzerland provided no competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Major news before the match even began was being circulated that Santos(Portugal coach) was unhappy about Ronaldo&amp;rsquo;s attitude when he was being substituted in the South Korea match. As a consequence of that Ronaldo was DROPPED from the starting 11 and 21-year-old Goncalo Ramos who has been putting up decent numbers for Benfica was starting in place of him and boy did he step up. Scoring the first hat trick at the World Cup that was a great performance. The first goal was Ramos who finished well after a pass from Felix. Top left near post leaving Sommer with little chance. The second was from Pepe. The man turns 40 soon and he is still at the top of his game at the back. A towering header over the likes of Schar and Akanji(The latter saw him late and Schar is usually good aerially) and was aimed brilliantly. He now becomes the second oldest player(39) to score at World Cups after Roger Milla(42) and before Ronaldo(37). Switzerland looked clueless overall. Next in the second half the demolition truly began. Dalot did well on the right and whipped a low cross to Ramos who finished well by squeezing it under Sommer. Next on the list was Guerreiro who managed to make a great forward run and was set up well by Ramos and his shot was in the top corner which Sommer didn&amp;rsquo;t even read properly(Psst. If you see the highlights you will see Ronaldo being happy at seeing the national team score. Some things that the media 🤡s won&amp;rsquo;t tell you). I like how the media just loves to scapegoat. They just conveniently remove the parts where Ronaldo actually was celebrating and just stick stubbornly to the narrative: &amp;ldquo;Oh cRiStIaNo rOnAlDo wAs dRoPpEd fOr rAmOs aNd hE ScOrEd aNd rOnAlDo wAs sUlKiNg aNd pEtTy&amp;rdquo;. Do your bloody research and look at every angle before putting out 💩 like this 😒. Later on, the Swiss brought one back but they knew they were beaten. The corner came in, and Akanji crept in unmarked at the back post to finish it. Funnily enough, Ramos was the one who had the last touch before Akanji(Guess it is a Portugal forward thing of assisting goals for the opponent from corners 😅). Ramos completed his hat trick after a great pass from Felix and he just cooly lifted the ball past the keeper. The final icing on the cake was from Leao who managed to put an outrageous curling effort into the right corner(How is he always smiling before his shots hit the target? 😂). Hit the griddy as well 🤣.  Surely he should be considered for Felix as well despite his 2 assists. He is more of a goal threat. Hopefully, we can see him starting the quarterfinal against Morocco.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../por_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;por_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;switzerland&#34;&gt;Switzerland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../swi_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;swi_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;quarterfinal-showdown&#34;&gt;Quarterfinal Showdown&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../e2e0246190d4fc07f5fd600021409f42.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;e2e0246190d4fc07f5fd600021409f42.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>