<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on WC22 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on WC22 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2022 CSR</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-6&#34;&gt;Day 6&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wales-v-iran&#34;&gt;Wales v Iran&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a305d874030a275c372f4d45c31026d0.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a305d874030a275c372f4d45c31026d0.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have seen the first red card of this tournament and what surprised me is that they had to go to VAR to even give it. It was a clear high foot by Hennessey on Taremi which was a red from miles off. The irony that a new directive from FIFA managed to give Iran the win was kind of funny after my criticizing loads of added time. &lt;strong&gt;Simply put, a directive was put in place to prevent time-wasting and that was to add more than normal minutes at the end of each game. It is harder on the players because these guys have played at least 3 games each week for their clubs and now they are being forced to play 95 and 100 minutes each game. It is just a joke but I do not want to take it away from Iran because they deserved the win&lt;/strong&gt;. With the way Iran played, I was more shocked as to how they weren&amp;rsquo;t able to win easily. They were dominant and Wales were off their game so much. The reliance of Wales on Bale was too obvious. He was off his game by a long way and Wales was also off because of it. As much as he is a good player for Wales, other players do have to step up. Neco Williams, Harry Wilson and others. I get relying on one man alone but Wales has youngsters in promising positions. I hope they don&amp;rsquo;t waste that. Coming back to both goals by Iran, they were really good goals scored on the counter and also Danny Ward was in goal(Not exactly a keeper in form). The red card sub was Ward for Ramsey. The first one was a good shot outside the box after a fluffed clearance from Joe Allen. The second was just a trademark counterattack. Fewer numbers, and tiring legs and they managed to easily score. Besides this, I think the best chance they had was a shot that hit the post twice before being saved by Hennessey finally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wales&#34;&gt;Wales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../wales_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;wales_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;iran&#34;&gt;Iran&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../iran_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;iran_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;qatar-v-senegal&#34;&gt;Qatar v Senegal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../5dba53ad7821b1e516c5ca3dfb927103.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;5dba53ad7821b1e516c5ca3dfb927103.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have got the first elimination of the tournament and surprise surprise it is the hosts. For this match however they put up a little fight with an equalizer so I will give them that. Apart from that, I ain&amp;rsquo;t shedding any tears for them leaving. Senegal was confusing somehow. Not in the exact same selves, they were against the Netherlands but Qatar had good spells of defense too. The first goal came from a mistake when the defender slipped when taking the clearance and fell to Dia who managed to hit it home. Next was a good corner goal when Diedhiou managed to head it in from an Ismail Jakobs corner(I told you he will be one to watch. He took a good corner). Qatar however managed to put up a little fight when Muntari managed to get a great header past Mendy. But Senegal managed to put the game beyond them when Dieng scored a great first-time shot after a good move.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;qatar&#34;&gt;Qatar&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../qatar_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;qatar_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;senegal&#34;&gt;Senegal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../senegal_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;senegal_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;netherlands-v-ecuador&#34;&gt;Netherlands v Ecuador&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bb6a9798e9c3b610657bf2f06f56e09c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bb6a9798e9c3b610657bf2f06f56e09c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was uncharacteristic of the Netherlands. They did score early via Gakpo which was a really well-taken goal. His stock is rising and rising. Loads of power and hard for the keeper to quickly get to it. I guess the saying &amp;ldquo;You can be vulnerable when you score early&amp;rdquo; is true in this case. After that goal, they really didn&amp;rsquo;t create many chances and Ecuador was the one who was attacking for the most part of the game. That was quite literally the weird part of this game. Estupinan was dangerous down the left. Ecuador managed to get back but it was disallowed in a load of controversy. Plata shot it into the box and Esupinan managed to deflect it in but the goal was not given because one defender was in the middle and he was adjudged to have been interfering with the play which felt really harsh to them. They managed to score finally when a shot was saved by Noppert(Who had a rather decent game) and it came to Valencia who managed to score. He is the current leader of the Golden Boot. Sadly he came off after his leg(calf or knee) flared up again after the first match. There were loads of chances here and there for Ecuador but they could not find the finishing touch. One major chance came from Plata who struck it well but it hit the post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;netherlands&#34;&gt;Netherlands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../net_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;net_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ecuador&#34;&gt;Ecuador&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ecu_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ecu_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;england-v-united-states&#34;&gt;England v United States&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../4efdcdd537520c0df37f9dead9db1af0.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;4efdcdd537520c0df37f9dead9db1af0.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would not call it a dull goalless draw but it was more disappointing from England personally and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind seeing USA come away with the 3 points if they could actually finish their chances properly. With the way, England played in this match, any good team who creates as many or more chances as the USA did and they are getting through them. Maguire and Stones were good enough you could say but going forwards England had absolutely nothing in terms of creativity. Southgate does not know how to use Foden(An absolute baller for Man City) and Trent(Really good going forward) so he keeps them on the bench which was quite ridiculous. Mount, Kane, Trippier were having bad games and Southgate didn&amp;rsquo;t bother subbing them off. Kane was obviously sluggish toward the end coupled with his lack of pace. USA was great in creating chances from the likes of Pulisic, McKennie, Weah and Dest. Pulisic deserved his MOTM award.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;england&#34;&gt;England&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../eng_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;eng_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;united-states&#34;&gt;United States&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../usa_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;usa_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-5&#34;&gt;Day 5&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;switzerland-v-cameroon&#34;&gt;Switzerland v Cameroon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../5379f9d372d0aed8a477f096eb68af98.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;5379f9d372d0aed8a477f096eb68af98.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright game I would say. Cameroon started with Choup-Moting over Aboubaker which had a different outlook on the game. Real good chances from Cameroon but the Swiss defense stood firm through it all. Everybody did their job really well. Major chances in the first half came to Cameroon and the major chance came for the Swiss via Akanji from the corner. Second half Switzerland managed to increase their influence and Embolo managed to score after a good cross from Shaqiri. Weird one this because Embolo was actually born in Cameroon and he didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate. Major respect. After that, they managed to lock it all down really well and seal the points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;switzerland&#34;&gt;Switzerland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../swi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;swi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cameroon&#34;&gt;Cameroon&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cam.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cam.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;uruguay-v-korea&#34;&gt;Uruguay v Korea&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a02aa53118490e2b0ca3c362ac0c35db.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a02aa53118490e2b0ca3c362ac0c35db.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me try to keep this as brief as possible because this string of goalless draws is getting infuriating. Uruguay had 2 great chances from Godin off the corner and Valverde from range with both of them hitting the post. Apart from that Uruguay and Korea were not able to find the space to attack and shoot. Korea was mostly just not able to create solid chances. Son fluffed a golden chance when the keeper made a mistake with a pass with other chances being shot wide. Everyone loves sitting back and defending well I guess. I am starting to see how international football is really slow because there were instances where a club team would absolutely blitz some areas on the break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;uruguay&#34;&gt;Uruguay&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../uru.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;uru.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;korea&#34;&gt;Korea&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../kor.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;kor.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;portugal-v-ghana&#34;&gt;Portugal v Ghana&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../d13c8e9cb86efd7e26ff2aece20a3e69.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;d13c8e9cb86efd7e26ff2aece20a3e69.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GET.WRECKED.GHANAAAAAAA. ROFL God Portugal almost bottled it Jesus. Honestly, the system both teams adopted was a surprise but it worked for Portugal and not as much for Ghana. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry but with the quality Ghana possesses they should not be trying a 5 at the back system against Portugal. I get that it was Portugal but that was not an excuse. The first half was complete Portugal domination. Ghana could get nowhere. Second half things finally got interesting when Ronaldo was brought down by Salisu after he managed to get to the ball before the player. He managed to slot it away and he becomes the first player to score in 5 World Cups now. Unreal achievement. Later on, Ghana managed to get back in when Cancelo lost his man and when the cross came in Danilo couldn&amp;rsquo;t block it and Andre Ayew managed to score. Game on. Ghana finally switched systems to a 4 back and the game finally opened up. Portugal struck fast and quickly on the break. They pressed well and got the ball and Bruno passed it through to Felix who lifted it over the keeper beautifully. Next another pass from Bruno to the new sub Leao and he brilliantly curled the ball past the keeper. The game was not done yet when Kudus managed to cross the ball after managing to get past Cancelo again and found Bukari who headed the ball home. He did the &amp;lsquo;Siuuuu&amp;rsquo; when they should have brought the ball back. Man&amp;rsquo;s priorities are on pointttt. That was not all really because Diogo Costa who had a decent game almost bottled the 3 points when he dropped the ball down and didn&amp;rsquo;t see Inaki Williams coming behind him and he took the ball but slipped when he tried to shoot and they breathed a sigh of relief. Ronaldo had his heart in his mouth for a moment from the bench.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../por.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;por.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ghana&#34;&gt;Ghana&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../gha.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;gha.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;brazil-v-serbia&#34;&gt;Brazil v Serbia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../64aadcc68a61f0ceae99da27ff165077.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;64aadcc68a61f0ceae99da27ff165077.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jogo Bonito is officially up and running. This was a dominant show from Brazil honestly. The way they moved the ball around was really good. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t like Spain but it was more direct and fluid. Neymar is flourishing in this system by Tite but sadly had to come off due to an ankle injury. That means he will not be available for 2 matches. Danilo(RB) has the same issue. What a game from Richarlison. I was skeptical of taking him when the likes of Firmino were doing well. But this match showed how good he can be really. The first goal was classic ST instinct. Vini Jr took a great shot and he was alive to the parry by the keeper and managed to finish. The second was absolute quality. Probably currently the goal of the tournament. The ball comes in, his touch sends it up and he times a sweet aerial volley to score. Raphinha only felt like an odd man out. You hardly saw him and his replacement Antony felt more influential. Serbia I have got say, I thought their attack was their only major point but their GK wasn&amp;rsquo;t that bad honestly. He managed to keep all attempts from Brazil out in the first half which was really great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;brazil&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bra.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bra.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;serbia&#34;&gt;Serbia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ser.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ser.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-4&#34;&gt;Day 4&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;morocco-v-croatia&#34;&gt;Morocco v Croatia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b139dd02a43bbb41fa09026dc5afcd15.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b139dd02a43bbb41fa09026dc5afcd15.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 3rd goalless draw. This is already more than in 2018 when there was only 1. This was however one of the dud ones. There weren&amp;rsquo;t enough clear-cut chances yet again. It was eventful but the shots were all over the place. The keepers were hardly tested. Mazraoui had to come off due to an injury sadly. Ez Abde came on for Morocco. He was lively but he wasn&amp;rsquo;t much of a passer. He just wanted to dribble a lot and when he did put a cross in nobody was there which summed up the game really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;germany-v-japan&#34;&gt;Germany v Japan&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../75531da760113c6fedb412d7e1a7cae7.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;75531da760113c6fedb412d7e1a7cae7.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh wow. What a result for Japan. I said Asano was injured but he came in time and he was the star turn as a sub along with Doan who managed to make the second half count. The first half told a very different story however because Germany was really positive from the start with a few flashes from Japan on the counter. And they had the chance for the lead when Raum got tackled by the keeper and Gundogan slotted the penalty home. After that they were good and Musiala, Gnabry, Raum looked really threatening. In the second half things were turning around. Japan slowly managed to get back in terms of attacking threat. The subs did the star turn for Japan as the German attack was not attacking well enough. The lack of a proper ST hurting the situation even further. Havertz was not good enough as a false 9 or ST like player. I think they are a really really good team but without Werner who was the only proper ST that Flick relied on injured he has to trust in someone else like Moukoko or anybody else. The goals came from Doan who scored off the rebound when a cross was parried into his path by Neuer. Asano managed to score off a long free kick. He took a great touch and managed to finish at the near post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;off-topic&#34;&gt;Off-topic&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a form of protest from the German players which I am 100% behind. There were sanctions mentioned for the teams that used the OneLove armband(An armband the captain wears to show support for human rights and LGBTQ+ groups) like yellow cards and/or fines to the countries and some countries actually obeyed that stupid directive like England. Germany, however, didn&amp;rsquo;t and actually, the armband was hidden under Neuer&amp;rsquo;s shirt apparently and in the team photo, all of them were covering their mouths to show solidarity which I absolutely love. Just because we are in a country that disrespects human rights doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean we have to stop speaking against it. Well done Germany.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;germany&#34;&gt;Germany&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ger.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ger.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;japan&#34;&gt;Japan&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../jap.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;jap.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;spain-v-costa-rica&#34;&gt;Spain v Costa Rica&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../3e465587f15a13c41e33f48bac71c4dc.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;3e465587f15a13c41e33f48bac71c4dc.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A statement show. Young baller Gavi. Costa Rica ain&amp;rsquo;t gonna survive. This was an amazing show. Yeah, you could say it was just Costa Rica but the way they managed to pass the ball around. The possession. The spaces they got. The fact that they started without an out-and-out No 9 but still managed to move the ball well was very telling. Pedri and Gavi made a start. They are most definitely the future of Spain&amp;rsquo;s midfield. Gavi stood out brilliantly for his tenacity. Managed to draw fouls. Ran into space really well and even got a great goal with the outside of his foot. First Olmo scored after a good move and the ball fell to him and he scored. Asensio was next with another good bunch of passes which teed him up with a first-time shot. Later Torres slotted a penalty after Jordi Alba was tackled in the box. Next, in the second half, Torres scored after holding onto the ball for so long and managed to finish past Navas. Then it was Gavi&amp;rsquo;s outside foot volley from a Morata assist(He was shaky but got into the game well. Enrique still did the right thing benching him). Later Soler scored after Navas parried a shot right into his path and finally Morata scored after another great move. His finish was decent on his left. Good placement. I think Spain are favorites to top the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spain&#34;&gt;Spain&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../spa.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;spa.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;costa-rica&#34;&gt;Costa Rica&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../crica.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;crica.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;belgium-v-canada&#34;&gt;Belgium v Canada&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../4a71b999c9d0b2a58b89b2a31ca2ade3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;4a71b999c9d0b2a58b89b2a31ca2ade3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlucky Canada. Belgium experience shines through. Hazard rolls back the years. Take a bow Canada. 36 years since their last World Cup and they gave a good account of themselves. Belgium&amp;rsquo;s experience of being the dark horses forever in every tournament paid off as they came away with the points in this game. The game started well for Canada when they got a penalty when Carrasco handled the ball in the box after a VAR check. However, Courtois managed to save the penalty from Davies. Later on, a long ball from Alderweireld was taken well and finished by Batshuayi. After that, nothing major really happened in the game apart from a good performance from Hazard who was really decent. Both he and De Bruyne were really good as always.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;belgium&#34;&gt;Belgium&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bel.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bel.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;canada&#34;&gt;Canada&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../can.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;can.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-3&#34;&gt;Day 3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;argentina-v-saudi-arabia&#34;&gt;Argentina v Saudi Arabia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../eb4e2f5508580d3d362ed0cbfad674c3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;eb4e2f5508580d3d362ed0cbfad674c3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well. First of all massive kudos to Saudi Arabia. Their system was absolutely solid with a high line to catch the Argentina attack out regularly. Argentina actually scored 3 offside goals. They just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the runners in behind well enough. First, a soft penalty was given when Paredes was pulled down in the box during a corner. Fairly soft but VAR thought otherwise and Messi calmly slotted home. Later in the first half alone, it was more like Argentina had the chances but was offside most of the time. Messi was well-marked. Lautaro Martinez scored the second but it was disallowed by offside(I don&amp;rsquo;t understand the new rules where the whole player has to stay on the shoulder of the last defender unlike the leg of the player). Then a shock happened in the second half when Argentina was slow and Saudi capitalized by scoring from Al-Dawsari. Romero was at fault a little bit for over-committing too early. Then a moment of quality from Al-Shehri gave them the lead. After that, it was aggressive cutting out of the ball and parking the bus massively. They just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get close. Bringing on Martinez, Fernandez and Alvarez made me think that they could have started. The aggression from Martinez, the incisive passes from Fernandez and the pace and running from Alvarez. Credit to the Saudi goalie as well who made 5 saves including a point-blank one from Tagliafico.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;saudi-arabia&#34;&gt;Saudi Arabia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ksa.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ksa.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;denmark-v-tunisia&#34;&gt;Denmark v Tunisia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../7b10eff02f52eb0f0b6707bda1a5106d.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;7b10eff02f52eb0f0b6707bda1a5106d.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A very dramatic goalless draw honestly. I was backing Denmark but they had a hard time breaking Tunisia. In fact, Tunisia was the one putting the first few attacks with the first being an aggressive tackle on Eriksen(Ease up man. He just came back to a major tournament after the Euros). The first goal was scored by Tunisia but was struck out via offside. Later on a cracking save from Kasper Schmeichel kept out the same person again in a half one v one situation. Denmark managed to have a bit of intent moving deeper into the game with the golden chance arriving for Cornelius who managed to get his attempt blocked at the goal mouth. Another goal was ruled out to offside sadly because Damsgaard was well offside. Later on, there was penalty drama for Denmark but VAR, however, didn&amp;rsquo;t give it as well which I would agree with because it seemed kind of soft. Both keepers had one brilliant moment you could say among a few routine saves. From the players I know, I think Mejbri looked alright for a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;denmark&#34;&gt;Denmark&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../den.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;den.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tunisia&#34;&gt;Tunisia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../tun.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;tun.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mexico-v-poland&#34;&gt;Mexico v Poland&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a7fa2d91fe137661711999b8e3cc78ed.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a7fa2d91fe137661711999b8e3cc78ed.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lewandowski blunted. Ochoa has arrived. Don&amp;rsquo;t sleep on Mexico. Honestly, this game was pretty dull because of the lack of clear-cut chances compared to the previous game. Only the penalty was the main talking point which I will come to in time. Mexico were seriously threatening with the likes of Lozano and Vega constantly switching sides. I think Jimenez could have made a difference instead of Martin because it seemed like they didn&amp;rsquo;t have that presence in the box at times to fire to. The major incident came later on when Poland won a penalty via Lewandowski which was given after a VAR check. Step up Lewandowski who had put away all of the penalties before this. But he has never met Ochoa who managed to save it on his left. I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice his trademark stutter before hitting the ball which was weird. Anyways this draw means Saudi Arabia leads the bloody group after one game and Argentina are at the bottom(I am pretty sure almost everyone thought that table would be upside down after one game)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mexico&#34;&gt;Mexico&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mex.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mex.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;poland&#34;&gt;Poland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../pol.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;pol.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;france-v-australia&#34;&gt;France v Australia&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../0ff72b98d855a6f6e307c781ea3202b2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;0ff72b98d855a6f6e307c781ea3202b2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You cannot keep them down. Maybe things may start to look up because for the first time the defending champions of the WC have actually won their opening game with the previous 3 being losses for Italy, Spain and Germany. The first one. My god did a lot of things happen. First of all, why did he pick Lucas Hernandez to play at LB when he had a capable Theo Hernandez for that? He got beat and injured in the build-up and a great cross was bundled home by Goodwin who was hardly marked. Later on, the equalizer came from Theo(Absolutely shocked /s) to Rabiot who headed home properly. The second was just sad. I don&amp;rsquo;t understand why you have to make a show of playing out from the back against the defending champs who pressed well and got it via Rabiot who squared it for Giroud who couldn&amp;rsquo;t miss it and made it 50 for France. Mbappe missed a sitter from a great Griezmann cross which was inch perfect from them every time. One person almost got it to 2-2 for Australia but it hit the post before the end of the first half. Dembele gave another cross to Mbappe who scored a good header to make it 3. Then it was a peach of a cross from Mbappe to Giroud who made it 4 to seal the game out. This means that Giroud has leveled Theirry Henry&amp;rsquo;s goal tally for France. A great achievement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;australia&#34;&gt;Australia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../aus.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;aus.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 13:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-2&#34;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;england-v-iran&#34;&gt;England v Iran&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../75eee5ddf5647d81a37f8bf7695699bf.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;75eee5ddf5647d81a37f8bf7695699bf.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great game from England. Southgate actually ditched the 5-back formation which means the sky is officially falling. Wowwwwww I am surprised. Iran was seriously not even close anywhere. There were like I thought. Very defensive and tried to break on the counter. Due to that, they got one of the goals from Taremi. Dunno why Azmoun didn&amp;rsquo;t start but he got some minutes. If they don&amp;rsquo;t get their act together I think USA and Wales will have good shot against them. Coming to the match, Iran was lost from the moment they lost their keeper to a possible concussion. Bellingham made the breakthrough, becoming the first teenager to score at the World Cup with a brilliant header(Cross from the great Shawberto Carlos - Luke Shaw). Then it was a great volley from Saka and a great finish from Sterling gave them 3 at the end of the half. Then it was just great work from Saka to make it 4. Later on, Taremi got one and Maguire was beaten for pace(Other teams take note. He is dangerous in corners but you can beat him for pace)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;england&#34;&gt;England&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../england.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;england.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;iran&#34;&gt;Iran&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../iran.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;iran.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;senegal-v-netherlands&#34;&gt;Senegal v Netherlands&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../50ef731442814c8e7ce44e2806e240da.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;50ef731442814c8e7ce44e2806e240da.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was an amazing game. I am impressed at Senegal with the way they managed to attack really well but without Mane, the dropoff was kind of evident. The threat from Sarr and Diatta was very evident and Dia and Dieng were ineffective at ST. The Netherlands however apart from Frenkie De Jong bottling a golden chance on the counter was semi-decent as well. They managed to get chances from the likes of Gakpo, Berghuis. Noppert made a start in goal(Man is 28 and was considering retirement to become a police officer and now he has got a WC clean sheet) and he was fairly decent. Managed to hold his own which is always good. In the end, it was 2 bad errors that were capitalized and credit to the Dutch for doing it. Gakpo starts a move and FDJ(Frenkie De Jong) provides a lovely ball for the first one. Finally, Klaasen scored after a good counter to take advantage of a tiring Senegal. Keep an eye on Gakpo. If he has a good WC, it will be dangerous for Man United(I&amp;rsquo;m a fan so I am worried). Another thing is: Is there a possibility of Timber starting because, as good as De Ligt is, he was rather shaky for the most part of the game. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what Van Gaal decides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;senegal&#34;&gt;Senegal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../senegal.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;senegal.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;netherlands&#34;&gt;Netherlands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../netherlands.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;netherlands.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;usa-v-wales&#34;&gt;USA v Wales&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ce5b239d406a7b33c413b588967c44b2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ce5b239d406a7b33c413b588967c44b2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weird referee. &amp;ldquo;Soccer&amp;rdquo; almost won and Bale had to bail out Wales again. Let me start by saying that the referee was really weird, to say the least, and that&amp;rsquo;s me being kind. He was dishing out the cards in the whole game, to be honest. First half: A good run by Pulisic at the defense and a good pass to Weah opened the scoring. Besides that Hennessey had to be alert to avoid conceding a weird own goal. In the second half, Wales slowly had an influence in the game with chances from the likes of Ben Davies and Kieffer Moore. Finally, a penalty was given when Zimmerman pulled Bale down and he converted with a fast and true penalty. I think these guys will be the major contenders for 2nd spot unless Iran pulls itself together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;usa&#34;&gt;USA&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../usa.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;usa.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;wales&#34;&gt;Wales&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../wales.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;wales.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-1&#34;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;qatar-v-ecuador&#34;&gt;Qatar V Ecuador&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../e5c7a415cca84837cbe6a0ff753672c2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;e5c7a415cca84837cbe6a0ff753672c2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definitely the worst opening match in the history of the whole tournament. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I really thought Qatar could give a match against Ecuador. This is also the first time ever in the history of the World Cup that the host nation has lost its first match. Even Russia had a better game than this lot. Ecuador hardly broke a sweat in this game. The second half was really just chilling from them. Qatar was happy to give them the possession in the opening stages and Valencia scored the opener after around 3 minutes but it was ruled out by VAR for offside(Highly Highly controversial but was reasoned out by the fact half his leg..was..in an offside position. God these rules seem dumb). However, it would be justice served when the goalie pulled down Valencia clean through on goal for a clear penalty which was put away perfectly. The second goal was brilliantly crafted though. A really great cross from Preciado to the head of Valencia and a good header. Qatar&amp;rsquo;s best chance was probably with the last play in the first half when they managed to somehow get an unmarked header and he completely fluffed it. That probably would have made the second half more interesting but they weren&amp;rsquo;t good enough to do that so it became a very dull second half. Given the fact they have Senegal(Even without Mane they are still decent enough) and the Netherlands, I don&amp;rsquo;t have many hopes for them honestly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;qatar&#34;&gt;Qatar:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../qatar.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;qatar.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ecuador&#34;&gt;Ecuador:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ecuador.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ecuador.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Serbia</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_serbia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_serbia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---serbia&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Serbia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhVYGPCWAAAWfmA.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhVYGPCWAAAWfmA.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a group that contains Brazil, Cameroon and Switzerland. Honestly, I think they and Switzerland are genuine contenders for the second spot. Those 2 teams can cause an upset too. My lineup is solely based on their values so bear with me. In goal, a Milinkovic Savic could be trusted or Rajkovic. In defense, it&amp;rsquo;s a back 3 of the likes of Pavlovic, Milenkovic, Erakovic mostly with the usual Veljkovic injured with an unknown return date so let&amp;rsquo;s see if he&amp;rsquo;ll be back. In midfield it&amp;rsquo;s a set of 4. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.transfermarkt.com/sergej-milinkovi%C4%87-savi%C4%87/profil/spieler/266302&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SMS&lt;/a&gt;
 should mostly start. Maybe alongside him, Racic could play or the likes of Ilic as well. Kostic will mostly for sure be at LM and Zivkovic at the right. Captain Tadic will be the lone CAM there. Upfront, it is a front 2 with Vlahovic and Mitrovic(He will mostly be back in time for the WC).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_serbia.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_serbia.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Argentina</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_arg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_arg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---argentina&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Argentina&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhSqitzX0AAhtan.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhSqitzX0AAhtan.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright. Copa America winners. Winners of the Finallissima. Their team looks amazing actually. I genuinely hope they do another 2014. In goal, Emi Martinez is a lock-in. In defense, Lisandro Martinez should definitely play after his amazing start at United. Alongside him, Romero or Otamendi should be good enough. In the fullback positions, I would perhaps go Tagliafico and Montiel. In midfield, Paredes or Palacios for the CDM role. Ahead of him, De Paul is for sure to start. I feel beside him I would trust Enzo Fernandez ahead of Papu Gomez. On the wings, Di Maria or Alvarez for LW and Messi at RW. Dybala was said to be missing the WC but he has been picked in the squad. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if he will play but it would be nice to see him in the as soon as possible. In ST, Lautaro Martinez is for sure on lock there. He has been amazing for Argentina so far and he will be crucial for them in this WC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_arg.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_arg.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Spain</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_spain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---spain&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Spain&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhR8bEfWIAEWo5h.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhR8bEfWIAEWo5h.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of controversy from Enrique with De Gea being left out of the provisional 55-man squad. My feeling is that the relationship severed after Euro 2020. He relies on playing well from the back including the goalie. Even though De Gea has relatively improved under Ten Hag in that aspect, he still has a long way to go. Unai Simon is already good at that aspect. So are Robert Sanchez and Raya. Another omission is Ramos who will not be going to his 5th World Cup like Messi and Ronaldo which is sad. I think there are young and good players who can do the job well. Guillamon who is a young CDM is actually named as a defender which is interesting. Fullbacks are mostly Gaya and Carvajal. In midfield, he could either go Rodri but he does seem to trust Busquets as well. I would go with Rodri for the form. In the center, Soler and Koke could mostly be the ones he goes for but Pedri and Gavi could very well start a game or two here and there instead of them. Maybe not as a duo yet but one of them along with Soler or Koke. I think my pick is Soler and Pedri. To the attack, Fati and Torres could fight for the LW spot. In the RW spot, Nico Williams is going to a major tournament which is amazing for him. I think Asensio, Sarabia, and Pino are also rather good options. In ST, he only has Morata and no Moreno which is weird. Torres and Fati could also be at ST but let&amp;rsquo;s see how that goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_spain.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_spain.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Netherlands</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_dutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_dutch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---netherlands&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Netherlands&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../3e8ea2cb19f22724972dad132dc4423b.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;3e8ea2cb19f22724972dad132dc4423b.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, I am liking the look of this squad. This is the first World Cup for the likes of Van Dijk and Pasveer(Take a bow. Being the first choice for Ajax at 39). Van Gaal has really made a turnaround after that spell with Manchester United. The system is likely to be a 3-back system which has worked out well for them. In goal, Pasveer could be starting in goal but Bijlow is OTW as well so hoping he could have a game or so as well. At the back, you can&amp;rsquo;t look past De Ligt, Van Dijk and Timber. The options are Ake and De Vrij. On the wings maybe Malacia and Frimpong could be trusted. If not Malacia, Blind could be present as well. In midfield, it is likely to be a 3 with a CAM. Frenkie De Jong will mostly start since he has been consistent for FC Barcelona. Along with him maybe De Roon or Koopmeiners can be expected. In CAM, I&amp;rsquo;d rather have Berghuis or Klaasen. Maybe the likes of Xavi Simons could have a start. Up front is usually 2 strikers. One of them has got to be Cody Gakpo after the season he&amp;rsquo;s had in PSV. Alongside him, the options are Bergwijn, L. De Jong or even Weghorst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_dutch.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_dutch.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>