<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on WC22 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on WC22 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2022 CSR</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:45:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - England</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_england/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_england/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---england&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - England&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../FhNTSa_XEAEHdsM.jpeg&#34;
        alt=&#34;FhNTSa_XEAEHdsM.jpeg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The big one I was actually waiting for. My expectations for Southgate were low but wow he absolutely went even low. Heavy imbalance, too many out-of-form players, some fatigue and dropping people who you would rather build the team around. It&amp;rsquo;s an absolute joke how the FA(Football Association) is allowing this League 1(Tier 3 of English football) coach even manage a bloody NATIONAL TEAM. The worst part of it is they are scared to hire anyone foreign. Anyways, the bottom line is it&amp;rsquo;s sad seeing a golden generation of attacking talent being wasted by a very conservative coach. Alright anymore and this post will be very big so let&amp;rsquo;s decipher the lineup and you bet your top dollar I am doing a best-ever England lineup as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In goal, I am fine with the picks of Pickford, Pope and Ramsdale with Pickford being the de facto starter. At the back I am certain it&amp;rsquo;s a back 3 of Dier, Maguire and Stones. On the left Shaw is mostly a lock and on the right, I would trust Trippier based on his form for Newcastle. Going into midfield, it picks itself with Rice and Bellingham. Going forward, the left will mostly be between Sterling and Rashford. I would trust Rashford on form and Foden or Saka on the right with Kane leading the line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup will look something like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_eng_1.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_eng_1.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are a few things to note:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;White was picked due to injuries to James and Chilwell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only 1 LB and 5 RBs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 CAMs for a formation that does not use a CAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No different CB like Tomori or even Guehi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bellingham only one outside England who is picked&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No James Ward-Prowse despite being in amazing form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kane is tired and his only backup is Wilson. No Toney or Tammy Abraham&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what I would have done:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked Tomori because he is a modern CB to partner Stones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked JWP on his amazing form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Picked Toney and Abraham along with Wilson and drop people like Grealish and Philips since they have hardly played and one of them was injured for a long time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Switch to a 4 back formation to actually make use of the attacking talent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is how the lineup would look like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_eng_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_eng_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Uruguay</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_uruguay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_uruguay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---uruguay&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Uruguay&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Uruguay_Squad.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;Uruguay_Squad.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So Suarez and Cavani are picked for the squad which is nice to see. One final time seeing that attacking duo probably but with Nunez coming up it&amp;rsquo;s hard to keep them together. In goal, the coach seems to trust Rochet more than Muslera so I would probably do the same. In defense Araujo is a very surprising pick given his expected return is in December if he underwent surgery he could maybe play but we need to wait and see how it develops. Apart from him, Gimenez is a surety alongside probably Caceres and the fullbacks will mostly be Olivera and Varela on the left and right respectively. Olivera and Vina are OTW on the left. In the center of midfield, we can for sure expect Valverde to start given his amazing form for Real Madrid and Bentancur will mostly start alongside him. Vecino and Torreira are present for more defensive options. On the wings, I would really like to see Pellistri on the right. He&amp;rsquo;s OTW along with Canobbio as well who usually can be found starting as well. On the left, you can expect to see probably de la Cruz. In attack, you will most definitely see Suarez and Nunez will start more compared to Cavani I think due to him being younger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_uruguay.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_uruguay.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Portugal</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_portugal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_portugal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---portugal&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Portugal&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232200.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232200.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the left: Goalkeepers and Defenders &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
On the right: Midfielders and Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stacked team. Ronaldo&amp;rsquo;s possible last dance. Isn&amp;rsquo;t in the greatest of form but will be expected to lead this team after their Euro win in 2016 and Nations League win in 2019. They have really good quality everywhere. They will miss Jota through injury but have good players instead of him. Starting at the back Diogo Costa has to start every game because he has been on it for Porto and recently signed a new contract. At the back, Pepe is injured but is picked anyways with no concrete return date. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how that develops. Instead of him, Danilo Pereira can do a job despite him being a CDM. He will be partnering Dias. However, there is a conundrum with the full backs. Dalot has been amazing for United and Cancelo has been no pushover for City either. Mendes is OTW at LB but I think I would rather see Cancelo at LB given that&amp;rsquo;s where he plays for City and Dalot at RB. Plus Dalot will have a game&amp;rsquo;s rest since he is suspended for the game before the tournament. Moving into Midfield we have options for the CDM in William and Palhinha and at CM we have Neves and also OTW in Nunes and Vitinha(Nunes is currently injured but will be back by the WC). Moving to the 3 behind Ronaldo, we have either Bruno or Silva at CAM, Leao or Felix at LW and Silva, Otavio and maybe Joao Mario as well for RW and Ronaldo is mostly going to be immovable at ST but for an option, Andre Silva could be a good option and maybe Felix as a false 9.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_portugal.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_portugal.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Poland</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_poland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_poland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---poland&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Poland&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_231935.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_231935.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Order: Goalkeepers, Defenders, Midfielders, Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the likes of Mexico and Argentina in their group here is hoping Lewandowski can do well in possibly his last World Cup. The usual system at play for Poland seems to be a 3 at the back formation so I&amp;rsquo;ll probably be centering my lineup with the same formation. In goal, Szczesny is a mainstay and Dragowski is a young development keeper who can hopefully take over from him. In the defense, the 3 CBs I would trust are Bednarek, Glik and Kiwior. On the left Zalewski seems to be trusted by the coach. He plays for Roma, is young and OTW. On the right, I would probably put my trust in Cash. I mean he decided to join Poland from England for crying out loud. In midfield, Zielinski is a lock-in. On the defensive side, it will probably be Krychowiak and Zurkowski. Up front, we could expect to see Lewandowski and probably between Milik and Piatek. However, Swiderski was starting in their last game against Wales(L). I would rather trust Milik or Piatek but let&amp;rsquo;s see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_poland.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_poland.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Belgium</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_belgium/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_belgium/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---belgium&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Belgium&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232011.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232011.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like I said in my team summary this is a decent squad in general and the one selected for this tournament is no different. This team has been forever named a dark horse but with the sheer quality they have I expected them to do really well at tournaments but they haven&amp;rsquo;t delivered as much as I thought. A 3rd place finish last time in the World Cup is good but not enough. Coming to the team, Courtois is unshakeable in goal. In defense, I would rather see Faes and Theate rather than Vertonghen and Alderweireld. Maybe one of the latter can be started for the experience. Vertonghen is injured however so it seems like Alderweireld will start mostly. Debast is a young CB also who could be OTW at 19. He played in Belgium&amp;rsquo;s last match(1-0 L to Netherlands). Onana is another OTW. Young CDM and a decent season for Everton. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how he develops along with either Witsel or Tielemans. On the left, it is between Castagne and Carrasco but I would trust Carrasco because of his work rate. Another one for the LM option could be Trossard who has had a great season for Brighton and deserves a run-out. On the right, Meunier is ever present and Doku is OTW who is young and can offer an attacking option. The 2 CAMs in this formation are 2 mainstays: De Bruyne and Eden Hazard. Up front is the conundrum. You have Lukaku who is the usual option or Batshuayi. You have Openda who is OTW: Young and promising and also De Ketelaere who has had a good start at AC Milan and can play either at CAM or ST.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_belgium.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_belgium.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Morocco</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_morocco/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_morocco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---morocco&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Morocco&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_231956.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_231956.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The order is: Goalkeepers, Defenders, Midfielders, Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an okay team in my opinion. With the likes of Belgium and Croatia, it is an uphill battle for Morocco. Ziyech is selected despite playing fewer games and being out of form for Chelsea but I get the reasoning. You sometimes have to have your most talented players.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In goal, we have Bono who is a half-decent keeper for Sevilla and is no slouch. In defense, the fullbacks are sorted with Hakimi and Mazraoui on the left and right respectively. I hope Hakimi can train to be an inverted fullback even more because both he and Mazraoui are young and really good talents. In the middle, you have captain Saiss and the second CB is between Dari and Aguerd. In midfield, Amrabat is ever present at CDM and a combo of Ounahi and Harit is interesting to see(Harit - OTW). In attack, Ziyech is set at RW and up front, En-Nesyri is a good option and Boufal is a constant presence at LW. Ez Abde is an interesting one because although he is OTW, he is injured currently and I have no news on when he&amp;rsquo;ll be back but if he does get fit during the cup, we can hopefully see him in some games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The probable lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_morocco.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_morocco.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Switzerland</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_swi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_swi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---switzerland&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Switzerland&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232107.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232107.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Credit to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goal.com/en/lists/switzerland-2022-world-cup-squad/bltab6e9f29cd83f728#csbf9b00ac759d0aff&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Goal.com&lt;/a&gt;
 for the simplification&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../1e5296fd12c6801b635f0269cfbf54fa.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;1e5296fd12c6801b635f0269cfbf54fa.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../346916016d96f2c4383ff762f9dab888.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;346916016d96f2c4383ff762f9dab888.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../d81bc7f50be37672dcd92522c1261afb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;d81bc7f50be37672dcd92522c1261afb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../8efc69542bdf6a9b45c9a49126c4e6b0.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;8efc69542bdf6a9b45c9a49126c4e6b0.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fairly decent time in the last Euros where they managed to knock out the current WC defending champions France on penalties. The squad is fairly decent with a few young options up front like Okafor and Embolo and a GK in Kobel. Sommer is injured but will be back in time for their first fixture maybe it could be time to trust in Kobel a little more. In defense, Mbabu is not present as he is not in form at Fulham. In the center, it&amp;rsquo;s Akanji and Schar with Widmer at RB and Ricardo Rodriguez at LB. The usual formation for them is a 4-2-3-1. The midfield pivot would be mostly Xhaka(Amazing form for Arsenal lately) and the second one can be between Zakaria and Freuler. Moving forward we have Big Shaq at RW and in CAM Sow has been used there so expect to maybe see him there again there and it is mostly Vargas on the left. Up at ST, we have Breel Embolo who has I think nailed down his spot there. Really good pace and is a decent finisher. On the bench, they have a good target man in Seferovic as well and one to watch in Okafor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_swi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_swi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - USA</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_usa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---usa&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - USA&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../USA_Roster.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;USA_Roster.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the days of seeing only Clint Dempsey and Landon Donovan, I have got to say I am liking the look of this USA team honestly. A good keeper in Matt Turner. Good defense in Robinson, Dest, Scally, Yedlin and Zimmerman. There is a decent midfield in Mckennie, Acosta, Aaronson and Adams. The forward line is also really good with the LeBron James of Soccer(C. Pulisic - LW), Gio Reyna who is doing well for Dortmund. A few ones to watch include Ferreira and Tim Weah.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One point is Mckennie is injured currently and maybe he could be back in time for the first game I think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think a 4-2-3-1 would work with this USA side but a 4-3-3 is also a good shout. This is how those 2 formations would look like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_usa_1.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_usa_1.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_usa_2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_usa_2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Cameroon</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_cameroon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 23:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_cameroon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---cameroon&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Cameroon&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232032.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232032.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fairly normal squad you could say. I am excited to see how Choupo-Moting will perform after being in form for Bayern but I don&amp;rsquo;t know if the coach will play him ahead of Aboubakar cause he is the captain of the team. Maybe he may play at LW but they already got Toko-Ekambi there and Mbuemo is a lock-in at RW. In midfield, the likes of Zambo Anguissa will be vital in shielding the defense. He has had a good season with Napoli so hoping he does well. Ntcham is one of the CM ahead of him along with maybe Hongla or Kunde. In defense, we have the experience of N&amp;rsquo;Koulou and youth in Wooh. In GK it&amp;rsquo;s for sure going to be Onana(Although I would like to see the third GK play to see the commentator struggle).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think the lineup will look something like this. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if this is how they usually play but this is the best from what they have got:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_cameroon.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_cameroon.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EMCM - Eric Maxim Choup-Moting&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squad Reaction - Croatia</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_croatia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 22:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/squad_reaction_croatia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;squad-reaction---croatia&#34;&gt;Squad Reaction - Croatia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221110_232117.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221110_232117.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just to make sure the spaces are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goalkeepers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Defenders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Midfielders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attackers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WC Finalists last time out. Looking at the squad strength, they have a good midfield and a fairly decent target man in Kramaric(Despite my personal feeling about him). Gvardiol at the back should be OTW. I&amp;rsquo;m guessing he will be paired with Lovren who isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly the fastest currently so maybe you can get at him. In the fullbacks, you have Sosa for the LB position and Vida and Juranovic at RB. In midfield, the 3 picks themselves: Brozovic(CDM), Kovacic and Modric(CM). Up front, we could mostly see Vlasic and Perisic with Kramaric(ST)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lineup would look as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../lineup_croatia.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;lineup_croatia.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>