<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tags on WC22 by CSR</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/tags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tags on WC22 by CSR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©2022 CSR</copyright>
    
        <atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 24</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-24&#34;&gt;Day 24&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;3-day-break-before-the-semi-finals&#34;&gt;3 day break before the semi-finals&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;argentina-v-croatia&#34;&gt;Argentina v Croatia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../2a16c9b30d5cb2bd139f24a923096e87.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;2a16c9b30d5cb2bd139f24a923096e87.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Messi messes up Gvardiol. Alvarez the new frontman. Lack of attack becomes Croatia&amp;rsquo;s undoing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was indeed pretty nervous thinking about this game due to Croatia&amp;rsquo;s ability to hold teams to a shootout but in the end, it was relatively easy. The surprising spaces being left from the start were exploited easily by the Argentina players(The manager going for a 4-man midfield to hold Croatia which was executed well). Molina and Tagliafico were the main threats compared to Mac Allister and de Paul. The spaces were evident and the first goal came from a penalty when Alvarez was found in loads of space and he managed to latch on and nudged it past Livakovic who was caught out and tackled him. There were significant protests. From my point of view, Alvarez did run into him but the keeper was unlucky in the end because he didn&amp;rsquo;t get the ball. Hence the stonewall penalty which Messi put away with ease and with that he has drawn level with his PSG teammate Mbappe. He is on a mission. To make sure his last World Cup will be a memorable one and that it will end with the trophy in his arms(Hopefully 🤞). In all the heated conversations between the Croatia players and the referee, Mandzukic was sent off 😅. I swear I forgot that Mandzukic was part of the coaching staff. Croatia is missing a player of your caliber mate and it was even more obvious in this match. Kramaric loved dropping deep too much, Petkovic was hardly able to twist and turn because of the lack of space and also the fact that this isn&amp;rsquo;t extra time 😉. The second goal was all Julian Alvarez. He has become the main frontman for them after Lautaro&amp;rsquo;s quite frankly horror show in this tournament and his delivering big time. This was a result of a corner gone wrong and Messi managed to carry it far before sending Alvarez through who went all the way from just behind the center circle all the way and scored. He managed to get a few 1-2s from the Croatian defenders before poking it past Livakovic. Croatia just didn&amp;rsquo;t have the attacking quality to fight back. Even though they pushed well in possession with their midfield, they just had no one to play to in the box because Kramaric was busy playing CAM like a certain Harry Kane 😑. Petkovic came on and hardly had any room because the coach decided to shore up on defense with Lisandro Martinez coming in. Perisic was so lonely he was pushed to LB because it was getting worse. The 3rd goal was from Alvarez again but all eyes were on that Messi assist because it was just vintage Messi. He absolutely OWNED one of the defenders of the tournament with that dribble. It was unbelievable. He is towards the right side. Closed down by Gvardiol. He just uses a burst of pace and uses all of his experience and dribbling to completely OWN him before supplying the ball for Alvarez who didn&amp;rsquo;t miss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/WPxtQiXaVHCcKaMF5g/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;Vintage_Messi&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a spectacle I was so happy to watch happen live 😄.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_semi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_semi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro_semi.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro_semi.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 21</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-21&#34;&gt;Day 21&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;morocco-v-portugal-and-england-v-france&#34;&gt;Morocco v Portugal and England v France&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../4e8cf446d59588bdf3a16301382e2690.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;4e8cf446d59588bdf3a16301382e2690.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../adc1c53397a2e3640fdc12583c02cfda.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;adc1c53397a2e3640fdc12583c02cfda.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 games that were actually settled in normal time. Surprisingly normal 😅. One was decided by a major error by the keeper otherwise it would have gone to penalties yet again. The second game was just well managed by France because England hardly had any open play chances and the one chance they had to equalize the second time Kane managed to bottle it. The second semi-final is now Morocco v France. The major matchup there is definitely going to be Hakimi v Mbappe but injuries to their backline are going to be hampering them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Major Costa error costs Portugal. Being pragmatic wins you games: This World Cup in a nutshell. Morocco history makers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morocco have become the first African nation to get into the semi-finals of the World Cup. A huge huge achievement from them and it was finished in normal time instead of penalties because of one Diogo Costa error. In the knockouts doing an error that big is inexcusable. The cross comes in and Costa massively misjudges the cross leaving En-Nesyri with an open net giving Morocco the lead. After that, it was chance after chance from Portugal. There didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be enough that were clear-cut chances. Ramos was isolated and hardly could do much(Ronaldo would have been criticized for that 😂 and yes he was benched again along with Cancelo). Felix had 1 chance but it was heavily deflected. He was rather decent actually with the second being a great setup and his left-footed shot was saved well by Bono. Later on, seeing the talent come on with the likes of Leao, Ronaldo, Cancelo and so on, Morocco moved to their trusty 5 at the back formation which had to happen after Romain Saiss their captain couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue further. Portugal tried everything. Chance after chance came and the passes were just misplaced due to the anxiety. And finally, it signaled the end of the road for Portugal. A vastly talented team with experience and youth but have been felled by what is Africa&amp;rsquo;s best team currently. It may also appear to be the end of the road for Cristiano Ronaldo at least in his international career which is just annoying. The smallest of errors lead to this and it is gut-wrenching in general to see this happen. This is one trophy and medal that will forever elude him in what has been an illustrious career. Morocco is on par with Croatia with their resilience for sure. They will not be shaken. In terms of attack, they had to be penned back due to Portugal constantly applying pressure but they managed to hold on. Saiss had a warriors performance despite his leg being heavily bandaged but had to come off eventually. Bono was a rock as always. One stupid moment was the substitute ST who came on. He got a yellow card for a bad challenge and immediately went and made another one and got himself sent off. Hakimi managed to hold on with Leao but Ziyech eventually had to track back and help. In terms of injuries, Saiss and Aguerd are out and so is Ziyech after he had to come off as well. As a certain Mr. Peter Drury put it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../08cb9fb8d867f0f961b211789f77f613.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;08cb9fb8d867f0f961b211789f77f613.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../por_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;por_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ENGLAND&amp;rsquo;S GOING HOME. ENGLAND&amp;rsquo;S GOING HOME. ENGLAND&amp;rsquo;S GOING HOME. 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣👋👋👋👋👋👋👋👋👋&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the first time since I think 1990 the defending champion and runner-up of the previous World Cup have made it into the semi-final of the World Cup now. This was a pretty decent performance from France apart from some shaky moments. England went with the wrong system and the wrong mentality. I strictly said if England doesn&amp;rsquo;t push from the get-go they can get overrun and they did. The beginning stage was all France and the breakthrough came from Tchouameni with a great strike after a little space opened up. It went through Bellingham&amp;rsquo;s legs and past an outstretched Pickford(Maybe a taller keeper like an in-form Ramsdale could have made a difference but he isn&amp;rsquo;t part of the FaVoRiTeS 🙄 because it was saveable being towards the bottom corner). Once France scored, there was a momentum shift as England remembered to suddenly play because they went a goal down and they were pushing but there was not any open play chance created from them throughout the game even if they had the momentum from scoring the penalty. Yes in the second half a penalty was given when Saka(England&amp;rsquo;s best player by a landslide and he gets subbed off 🤦) was fouled in the box and Kane stepped up to score it past his club teammate. With that goal, he has drawn level with Wayne Rooney as England&amp;rsquo;s all-time leading goal scorer. After that France managed to have it handled well because of a lack of a CAM like how Griezmann is for France Kane dropped back way too deep and Southgate didn&amp;rsquo;t trust the likes of Rashford, Maddison and so on to make the difference which it could have. England did have a second penalty but France did give a response back. Giroud missed a great chance from the cross and only put his effort close to Pickford who made a straightforward save and managed to score after a corner after said chance with the cross coming in from Griezmann and his header being on point as always. The second penalty for England was given after a VAR review when Mount was barged off by Theo Hernandez. It was a brain fart from the latter. But Kane could not bring them back in a second time as his shot sailed well over the bar. Since Theo did an NFL-style challenge on Mount, Kane decided to show his NFL side by blasting it home for the bonus point 🤣. Unfortunately, this is not the NFL Harry 🤣🤣🤣🤣. Everyone knows this ball is light. Why you went for it like that I will never know. After this England just didn&amp;rsquo;t have an answer after that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🎵They&amp;rsquo;re going home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re going home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re going&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;England&amp;rsquo;s going home🎵🤣👋&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;england&#34;&gt;England&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../eng_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;eng_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;gareth-southgate&#34;&gt;Gareth Southgate&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../2b0370b011943c8495a71ab72dd4bded.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;2b0370b011943c8495a71ab72dd4bded.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonjour Monsieur Boregate 🤣. The first major test and you have fallen. The World Cup was supposed to begin in the quarter-finals for yall and well I see that you have immediately gone 😂. From the start, the mentality and the system were all wrong. Given the talent is equal between England and France it would have been better to just replicate the same system as France. Griezmann had so much space and was really influential despite you having 3 midfielders 🤦. Kane dropped deep because the midfield couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite get the ball to him. When he did, there was no one in the box to aim at for the wingers and even if the wingers did cut inside they would be easily stopped by the defense and they had no one to also feed in because Kane would be all the way at the halfway line 🙄. The pace was needed and Kane is NEVER EVER going to provide that. Saka was your best player and you bring on Sterling who went through a damn burglary and had to go back to England and come back in. The favoritism has to stop mate. Rashford was in great form and he does not bring him in. I think an in-form Maddison would have made a better difference than Mount in all honesty. From the damn FaVoRiTeS gang to the bad squad choices and stubbornness, you have proved time and time again that you are not the right man to lead this great generation of talent. Misusing the likes of Foden(Pep gets the best out of him week in and week out), Rashford(EtH has got the best out of him and is in great form), Maddison(No minutes whatsoever which is just plain sad). You missed a CAM today and that cost you badly. You only started attacking after Tchouameni&amp;rsquo;s great strike. Just having a happy team is not enough FYI. You actually have to have a decent game plan of attack. Without a CAM, what were you even thinking? Why in the world were you relying on Kane who is a bloody STRIKER BTW for your linkup? It made defending a piece of cake for Varane and Upamecano. This was how you were playing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../what_a_fool.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;what_a_fool.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wingers looking up couldn&amp;rsquo;t see their target man ST which was absolutely hilarious to watch 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So with the utmost respect(which is virtually not much), I am saying to you and your bunch of FaVoRiTeS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/9u4TXfoIM7wQHnfR1p/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;So Long&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-final-four&#34;&gt;THE FINAL FOUR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../6ea0053ef4c00079faa89326a269cfb3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;6ea0053ef4c00079faa89326a269cfb3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 20</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-20&#34;&gt;Day 20&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2-day-break-after-the-round-of-16&#34;&gt;2 day break after the Round of 16&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;quarter-finals&#34;&gt;Quarter Finals&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;croatia-v-brazil-and-argentina-v-netherlands&#34;&gt;Croatia v Brazil and Argentina v Netherlands&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../6a69b541804b632154b59d31141edd12.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;6a69b541804b632154b59d31141edd12.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b2e463e7fafc2d48df423d7c6ced8d8b.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b2e463e7fafc2d48df423d7c6ced8d8b.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b82708c33fc8fbf32b0c2613eda27f9c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b82708c33fc8fbf32b0c2613eda27f9c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../e30eece2bb06bff87cd723c6fef752c7.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;e30eece2bb06bff87cd723c6fef752c7.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am writing this just after the heartbreak. While it is still raw. I am just not interested at all in seeing that sad excuse of a game from Brazil again. Just when I had hoped these guys could go all the way to the final, they had to ruin it. The second was heated, to say the least. We have a Croatia v Argentina showdown. 2 teams who are good at penalty shootouts will face off 😬. Argentina will have to be alert and try to get the game done and dusted and defend like crazy to prevent Croatia from coming back and make sure their lack of attacking threat is neutralized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Croatia hold on again. Build Livakovic a damn statue. Brazil just could not hold onto the ball&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brazil went into the game as favorites as we all know but Croatia played for a penalty shootout from the get-go. Trust me it was such an annoying watch. Chances were not as clear cut for Brazil and the chances that they did get Livakovic managed to save them all. The breakthrough came in extra time because before that in normal time Brazil would attack, and Croatia would defend and slow the game down. Juranovic and Gvardiol were on it throughout the whole 120. But surely I think this should be taking a toll. I know in 2018 they did 2 consecutive shootouts and were off the pace for France but maybe they could do the business if they keep this park-the-bus mentality. I think the problem with Croatia in normal time is they are missing a Mandzukic type ST badly and the likes of Kramaric just ain&amp;rsquo;t cutting it. They did bring on Petkovic for the ET period but he was starved of service for so long. The first goal was a moment of pure pure quality. Neymar passes it quickly and gets the ball in the box, quickly dribbles past Livakovic and manages to score. With that, he has equaled Pele as Brazil&amp;rsquo;s all-time top goal scorer. A truly amazing achievement and something that goes under the radar of all the criticism he always gets. I am sad for him especially considering the loss and this is yet again another failure for the national team to show promise but flounder when the chips are down. Now somehow Neymar is going to get the brunt of the fire from the media despite literally giving them hope. Croatia leveled when Brazil were caught out on the right side (It didn&amp;rsquo;t feel right that Paqueta had to play deep with Casemiro. Maybe a Bruno G could have been the more ideal player&amp;hellip;? We will never know) and Orsic crossed the ball in and Petkovic took the shot which I think if not for the right leg of Marquinhos Alisson would be saving that. The deflection takes it just beyond his reach. Fred was rather dreadful coming on. Thought he would be energetic but he got outran by Modric who was there FOR THE ENTIRE DAMN GAME. Penalties came and Livakovic saved Rodrygo&amp;rsquo;s penalty and Marquinhos hit the post to send Croatia through. Alisson saved a grand total of&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;0 penalties 😑. Neymar can&amp;rsquo;t catch a break 😥.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;brazil&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bra_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bra_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have finally seen the passion that many are trying to suppress. Messi masterclass yet again. Netherlands plays the ultimate bore game to force extra time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The single most heated game of this World Cup. This is what we always wanted to see. Passion and a little bit of fight. This is what the modern game is missing badly. I also think the referee was shambolic for both sides in all honesty. Both sides had the same formation to defend hard. Netherlands however did not have Messi and that was a major difference. For ALLLLL THE SMACK the fans, media and Van Gaal spoke about Messi being finished. Where are ya&amp;rsquo;ll now? 🖐️😤🖐️.  The first goal was from a beautiful defense-splitting pass by Messi to Molina who managed to score. That pass was the best I have ever seen. Nobody expected it. That is Messi for you 🐐. The first half had a few chances but nothing stood out apart from that amazing Messi assist for Molina. The second half began and there was a chance to make it 2-0 when Acuna was tripped by Dumfries. It was soft but the contact was there and it was given. Messi managed to score it with conviction by wrong-footing Noppert. Later on, Netherlands finally decided to play even more boring football 🥱 by bringing on the likes of Luuk de Jong and Wout Weghorst, the latter inspiring a star turn for the Dutch. Basically, Netherlands played a version I like to call &amp;ldquo;Cross and Inshallah&amp;rdquo;. It managed to work due to the lack of proper height in the defense apart from Romero. Weghorst managed to score after a cross from Berghuis. The bounce before coming to the keeper was the deciding factor. There was a moment that broke out when Paredes clattered Gakpo and later fired the ball straight at the Dutch bench and it kicked off a flurry of players rushing onto the pitch. This match saw a record 17 yellow cards alone. You can find the cards below. The second goal was smart. That is all I&amp;rsquo;ll give to the Dutch. It was a sloppy free kick conceded by Pezzella(Why did Romero have to come off ??🤦‍♂️). The freekick was smartly taken by Koopmeiners to Weghorst who managed to turn quickly and managed to slot it past E. Martinez. Going to extra time, 2 major chances were there for both L. Martinez and Fernandez. The former&amp;rsquo;s shot was deflected by van Dijk and the latter hit the bottom of the left post towards the end of extra time. The shootout came. E. Martinez made 2 great saves from van Dijk and Berghuis. The only miss from Argentina was by Fernandez who dragged his shot wide of the post he hit 😑. Finally, it was down to Lautaro Martinez to send them through after Weghorst, L. de Jong and Koopmeiners scored for the Dutch and he did not miss. With that I would like to say with absolutely no shame: &amp;ldquo;BYE BYE NETHERLANDS 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣. AIRPORT IS THAT WAY 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣&amp;rdquo;. This is all of the Argentina and Messi fans right now:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../Screenshot_20221210_113316_Instagram.jpg&#34;
        alt=&#34;Screenshot_20221210_113316_Instagram.jpg&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-cards&#34;&gt;The cards&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a4742252c409391d4ae0f8798bfe478f.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a4742252c409391d4ae0f8798bfe478f.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;netherlands&#34;&gt;Netherlands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ned_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ned_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_quarters.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_quarters.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 17</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-17&#34;&gt;Day 17&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;end-of-round-of-16&#34;&gt;End of Round of 16&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;morocco-v-spain-and-portugal-v-switzerland&#34;&gt;Morocco v Spain and Portugal v Switzerland&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../48961dfb1505b3c88b4c91ffdacac703.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;48961dfb1505b3c88b4c91ffdacac703.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../0fdfc36a3c26d033847ba9fa251f9571.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;0fdfc36a3c26d033847ba9fa251f9571.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../e9f5878658756083930bbbe6c084406c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;e9f5878658756083930bbbe6c084406c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have found our dark horses of this tournament. Ronaldo was dropped but was happy with the team&amp;rsquo;s performance.  His replacement takes the headlines. We have the last quarter-final which is going to be between Morocco and Portugal. Morocco knocking out Spain yet again(They lost to Russia in a PK shootout last WC 🤭). Portugal outplay Switzerland and Ramos was at the center of it all. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morocco withstand Spain easily. Spain had no urgency. Hakimi as cool as can be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was completely embarrassing from Spain. Major major kudos to Morocco for managing to hold on. Spain honestly had just one trick and that was to make sure they just passed and passed and passed us allllll to 😴.  Morocco was also fairly threatening with the likes of Boufal especially. Amrabat was solid as a wall in the midfield holding back the likes of Pedri and Gavi. I think in a situation like this the experience of De Gea(He may not be a sweeper yet but at least he is one of the best shot-stoppers there is), Ramos(Laporte had a chance at the very end of the 90 minutes but completely miscued it. Ramos would have been on the end of it) and they looked lost with just Busquets on the field(Like seriously Enrique just stop being so arrogant and stubborn). Enrique made the players take 1000 penalties. Hah. Guessing they missed all of them because they didn&amp;rsquo;t score a SINGLE one in this shootout. Sarabia had the chance of a lifetime. He was brought on for the shootout and almost won the game at the end of extra time but his shot grazed the left post. He felt hard done by that so he decided to hit the right post in the shootout 🤦‍♂. Unless Enrique stops being stubborn and does not utilize the experience they have and groom the right players for each position they ain&amp;rsquo;t going far. Hakimi was born and brought up in Spain and could have played for them. In the end, he decided to score the winning penalty(A panenka no less 😱) to knock Spain out and he did Ramos&#39; penguin celebration for good measure. Bono also deserves the rightful shout for making 2 saves in this shootout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spain&#34;&gt;Spain&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../spa_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;spa_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goncalo Ramos center stage. Ronaldo dropped but was not fazed. Switzerland provided no competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Major news before the match even began was being circulated that Santos(Portugal coach) was unhappy about Ronaldo&amp;rsquo;s attitude when he was being substituted in the South Korea match. As a consequence of that Ronaldo was DROPPED from the starting 11 and 21-year-old Goncalo Ramos who has been putting up decent numbers for Benfica was starting in place of him and boy did he step up. Scoring the first hat trick at the World Cup that was a great performance. The first goal was Ramos who finished well after a pass from Felix. Top left near post leaving Sommer with little chance. The second was from Pepe. The man turns 40 soon and he is still at the top of his game at the back. A towering header over the likes of Schar and Akanji(The latter saw him late and Schar is usually good aerially) and was aimed brilliantly. He now becomes the second oldest player(39) to score at World Cups after Roger Milla(42) and before Ronaldo(37). Switzerland looked clueless overall. Next in the second half the demolition truly began. Dalot did well on the right and whipped a low cross to Ramos who finished well by squeezing it under Sommer. Next on the list was Guerreiro who managed to make a great forward run and was set up well by Ramos and his shot was in the top corner which Sommer didn&amp;rsquo;t even read properly(Psst. If you see the highlights you will see Ronaldo being happy at seeing the national team score. Some things that the media 🤡s won&amp;rsquo;t tell you). I like how the media just loves to scapegoat. They just conveniently remove the parts where Ronaldo actually was celebrating and just stick stubbornly to the narrative: &amp;ldquo;Oh cRiStIaNo rOnAlDo wAs dRoPpEd fOr rAmOs aNd hE ScOrEd aNd rOnAlDo wAs sUlKiNg aNd pEtTy&amp;rdquo;. Do your bloody research and look at every angle before putting out 💩 like this 😒. Later on, the Swiss brought one back but they knew they were beaten. The corner came in, and Akanji crept in unmarked at the back post to finish it. Funnily enough, Ramos was the one who had the last touch before Akanji(Guess it is a Portugal forward thing of assisting goals for the opponent from corners 😅). Ramos completed his hat trick after a great pass from Felix and he just cooly lifted the ball past the keeper. The final icing on the cake was from Leao who managed to put an outrageous curling effort into the right corner(How is he always smiling before his shots hit the target? 😂). Hit the griddy as well 🤣.  Surely he should be considered for Felix as well despite his 2 assists. He is more of a goal threat. Hopefully, we can see him starting the quarterfinal against Morocco.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../por_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;por_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;switzerland&#34;&gt;Switzerland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../swi_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;swi_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;quarterfinal-showdown&#34;&gt;Quarterfinal Showdown&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../e2e0246190d4fc07f5fd600021409f42.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;e2e0246190d4fc07f5fd600021409f42.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 16</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_16/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-16&#34;&gt;Day 16&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;japan-v-croatia-and-brazil-v-south-korea&#34;&gt;Japan v Croatia and Brazil v South Korea&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../777b7fd12722087f36a9611a715cfbdb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;777b7fd12722087f36a9611a715cfbdb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../6661b92fd9e1da2eecf7655e24d837a2.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;6661b92fd9e1da2eecf7655e24d837a2.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../c789e46f9a3f9bdf46c031e2e956eb12.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;c789e46f9a3f9bdf46c031e2e956eb12.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first penalty shootout. Experience shines through and Brazil have a nice walk in the park. We have a quarterfinal between Brazil and Croatia. Japan&amp;rsquo;s dream run comes to an end. Croatia just have the experience with penalty shootouts. Brazil have fun for Neymar&amp;rsquo;s return. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Croatia&amp;rsquo;s experience shines through. Japan should have been more attacking. Livakovic joins an exclusive club&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had our first-ever extra time and penalty shootout of this tournament. What is it with Croatia and penalty shootouts 😂? Both teams honestly were really lackluster with their passing and chance creation. Japan hardly had enough players in the box and Croatia was sloppy. The opener came from a Japan set piece and the ball fell toward Maeda from Yoshida and he wasn&amp;rsquo;t missing from that range. Perisic managed to bring Croatia back in after a great cross from Dejan Lovren of all people 😅. His cross made it easier for Perisic to just direct his header properly and it was placed perfectly. Later on, it was just a huge stalemate from both of them. In extra time Mitoma had a big chance for Japan and Majer for Croatia but they couldn&amp;rsquo;t finish. So we had penalties and Livakovic has joined an exclusive club of making 3 saves in a shootout along with Ricardo and Subasic(Croatian as well).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;japan&#34;&gt;Japan&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../jap_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;jap_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brazil have fun. Korea needed a worldie for a goal. Neymar is one away from Pele.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What a FUN match to watch 😁. Korea stood no chance against them. I had one look at the lineup and I was scared. Neymar was immediately in the lineup after his injury. Danilo at LB and Lucas Paqueta as well but all of those were squashed really quickly. Brazil got underway in just 7 minutes when Raphinha&amp;rsquo;s cross came all the way to Vini Jr catching out the Korea defense and Vini stayed composed and placed it calmly past everyone. Next was a penalty which was kind of smart where Richarlison literally placed his foot in front of the defender trying to make the clearance and got hit. Neymar scored the resultant penalty and now draws one away from Pele. The third one could be a candidate for the goal of the tournament yet again. It starts with Richarlison juggling the ball on his head and passing it quickly between both center backs Marquinhos and Thiago Silva before having so much space and time to slot it away. The fourth was a cross that came to Paqueta who made the run and wasn&amp;rsquo;t even unmarked. Allison had work to do as well. He wasn&amp;rsquo;t left on his own. Made 3-4 good saves but sadly got beat by a great long-range effort from Korea. Tite actually gave Weverton a chance and with that, he has given minutes to everyone in his 26 man squad. Class act from him 👏.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;brazil&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bra_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bra_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;south-korea&#34;&gt;South Korea&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../kor_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;kor_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 15</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-15&#34;&gt;Day 15&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;france-v-poland-and-england-v-senegal&#34;&gt;France v Poland and England v Senegal&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../0085d6061087041cec8400166e5759ff.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;0085d6061087041cec8400166e5759ff.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../0a5434f62a474d8a077f966733cabec8.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;0a5434f62a474d8a077f966733cabec8.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These results mean we have a mouth-watering clash between the holders and England. Will the holders roll through or will the English defense pen them back? We will know for sure on Saturday. Both games were great. One was all about Mbappe and the other was about moments that can happen if England can attack from the get-go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mbappe Show yet again. Record breaker Giroud. Poland is too pragmatic with one of the world&amp;rsquo;s best STs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 records were broken in this match. Giroud scored his goal which meant he is now France&amp;rsquo;s all-time men&amp;rsquo;s top scorer ahead of Thierry Henry. I don&amp;rsquo;t think many people understood his role in that 2018 France squad(I was one of them yes hello 👋). He was severely underrated and I owe him an apology. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t familiar with your game. He was really good and we almost had another goal of the tournament contender but sadly Szczesny was down injured so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t counted. His earliest chance was around the 28th minute but he miscued Dembele&amp;rsquo;s cross. Poland did have a chance 10 minutes later but Zielinski shot straight at Lloris and it was blocked by the defense later on. Giroud&amp;rsquo;s opener was made to look really easy. Mbappe slips him through and he managed to have great composure with the shot and beat the keeper. He may be slow but he is rather lethal, at least when it comes to France. Later on, it was the Mbappe show yet again. First, it was a counterattack that was taken at pace and Mbappe just cut inside and unleashed a powerful shot in the top left corner. His record was that he managed to surpass Pele by scoring the most goals in the WC. The so-called &amp;ldquo;debate&amp;rdquo; between Mbappe and Haaland. Yeah, that is long dead in the water. You are just seeing that now. Honestly, Mbappe is a really really great player barring his ego. The next one was another curler which was in the top right after a pass from Thuram. This was taken more quickly. Opens space up and bang. Poland managed to get a consolation goal at the end after VAR gave a penalty because of a handball by Upamecano. Lewa had his first attempt saved with his classic stutter run up but it had to be taken again because Lloris went away from his goal line. On the retake, he managed to score.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;poland&#34;&gt;Poland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../pol_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;pol_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;England handles themselves well. Senegal doesn&amp;rsquo;t capitalize on early promise. England needs to be more imposing for the next game&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The score may suggest it was no contest and with the way they took the goals yes it really wasn&amp;rsquo;t but one thing which can be taken as a positive was the fact that Senegal actually threatened by being aggressive from the start which is a drawback in the Southgate system and was the first ones to have a shot on target from Dia but Pickford had a strong hand out to deny him. England punished them with 2 well-worked team goals. The first one was from Henderson after Kane sent through Bellingham and he managed to cut it back for Henderson perfectly. Good experience youth combo. The second was a deadly finish from Kane. England broke on the counter, Belligham to Foden who found Kane and he managed to finish past Mendy. The third to seal the deal was from Saka. Foden managed to slip in behind easily and found Saka on the cut back who finished well. Senegal never had anything after that. If England can be as imposing as they were when they scored their goals from the get-go against France we have a match. Otherwise, I could see France dominate possession and happily just keep crossing the ball in for either Giroud or Mbappe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;england&#34;&gt;England&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../eng_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;eng_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;senegal&#34;&gt;Senegal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../sen_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;sen_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 14 - Start of Round of 16</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-14&#34;&gt;Day 14&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;round-of-16&#34;&gt;Round of 16&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;netherlands-v-usa-and-argentina-v-australia&#34;&gt;Netherlands v USA and Argentina v Australia&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../808f94b497d9b3a689164fbb3871c67d.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;808f94b497d9b3a689164fbb3871c67d.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a73cf9e87978fbc6d9d6a698a741b038.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a73cf9e87978fbc6d9d6a698a741b038.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results now mean we have got a rematch of the 2014 WC semifinal and Argentina had to rely on penalties to get through. Will we see more of that? Given how the Netherlands game went, maybe. One was a boring no-contest with goals and the other was a game that got really REALLY close toward the end but Argentina managed to hang on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A boring counterattack game. USA can be proud. Dumfries heavily involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was honestly not expecting this level of a low block from the Dutch. They just sat back absorbing the pressure and managed to counter quickly. Dumfries and Blind were initially held back by the exuberance of the USA full-backs at the start but they managed to get back in the right headspace, Dumfries more so providing 2 assists and a goal himself. The lone goal for the US came via Haji Wright who has been their only major threat all the way for them. The goal was a half flick on from his right foot more like which looped all the way in. Gave them a bit of hope but Dumfries managed to absolutely demolish any hopes of that after he was found unmarked by the cross. The first 2 were fairly similar. Dumfries bombs down the right, low cross to someone waiting. It was Depay and then Blind. We can understand why Ten Hag wanted Dumfries. He is pretty solid in defense and he has got that eye for the cross and is tireless going forward and back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;netherlands&#34;&gt;Netherlands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ned_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ned_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;usa&#34;&gt;USA&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../usa_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;usa_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Messi finally gets a knockout stage goal. Martinez is called The Butcher for a reason 😤. Australia had a really good team spirit to pose a challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Close one towards the end but Argentina is through safely to face the Dutch. The opener came from Messi(With the form he was in before this tournament, I was hardly surprised 😅) in his 1000th career game. Peter Drury put it best &amp;ldquo;A 1000 games and still, he excels&amp;rdquo;. It was a free kick and the loose ball falls to MacAllister(TIL that his father played with the late Diego Maradona 😱) who passes it to Messi and a quick pass to Otamendi who in reality just touched it before Messi pulled off a beautiful curler from that left boot of his which has scored and provided. Alvarez scored in the second half after playing from the back went horribly wrong for Ryan the keeper 🤦 and Alvarez pounced and slotted it away. Things seemed rosy&amp;hellip;until it wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Roll on the 76th minute and Goodwin tries a long-range shot and it manages to go in after a rather hefty deflection of Enzo Fernandez(I big up him so much and something this unlucky happens to him 😅). Australia all of a sudden has halved the deficit. A big moment happened in the 80th minute where Behich almost made it 2-2 but Lisandro Martinez said &amp;ldquo;Not today sunshine&amp;rdquo;. He&amp;rsquo;s called the Butcher of Manchester for a reason 😤. Lautaro however had a golden chance provided by Messi but for some reason, he forgot his shooting boots. Chances were there on both ends. Australia had good spirit to keep pushing and holding on. Another last-gasp save was made by Emi Martinez from Kuol who was free after most of the defense was lying down but the keeper made himself big and managed to save it 👏.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;australia&#34;&gt;Australia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../aus_ro16.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;aus_ro16.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 13</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_13/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-13&#34;&gt;Day 13&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;final-matchday-in-groups-g-and-h&#34;&gt;Final Matchday in Groups G and H&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-h&#34;&gt;Group H&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ghana-v-uruguay-and-portugal-v-south-korea&#34;&gt;Ghana v Uruguay and Portugal v South Korea&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../7779555c0f0b7cc5ae6aeb6bf3179d74.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;7779555c0f0b7cc5ae6aeb6bf3179d74.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../dd360dd13f1b211ece411fc2dcbca16e.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;dd360dd13f1b211ece411fc2dcbca16e.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We called this group the &amp;ldquo;Group of Death&amp;rdquo;, at the very least me. It delivered massively on the final matchday. Uruguay prevented Ghana from getting revenge for 2010 but Korea provided it anyways by pipping Uruguay on goals scored(4 to Uruguay&amp;rsquo;s 2) by beating Portugal who had a host of rotations. They have &amp;ldquo;dreamed&amp;rdquo; and they have achieved passage into the Round of 16. Let&amp;rsquo;s get into each match.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uruguay prevents Ghana revenge. Ghana do the same thing again. Farewell Suarez and Cavani.
Damn you Ghana, I thought you could really pose a threat but this grudge match turned into a damp squib. This was complete Uruguay domination in terms of chances but a moment of controversy in the 16th minute where a penalty was given to Ghana after a foul by the keeper on Kudus who lifted the ball just past his outstretched hands. But Captain Andre Ayew had his penalty saved and the goalie made up for his mistake by making a great save. Funny thing you know: Asamoah Gyan missed a penalty against Uruguay in 2010 and Ghana got knocked out. Now Ayew misses his penalty and Ghana are knocked out but now its Uruguay who will be joining them after what happened in the other game. The goals came from a brace by De Arrascaeta. Man has great experience and does well. The first came after a cross missed Ghana&amp;rsquo;s defense 😅 and came straight to Suarez who floored a defender before shooting and it was saved before being bundled in by De Arrascaeta. Suarez switched on his prime form all of a sudden, one highlight being him nutmegging Inaki Williams 😆. The second came after a good passage of play led to Suarez who looped the ball perfectly for him for the volley. Later on, once it was notified that Korea had scored a stoppage time winner against Portugal, Uruguay needed one more goal to go through on Goal Difference. Despite all the pressure they posed(Coates did a Pique by going forward in attack) they were not clinical and it was crushing for Suarez to see such a pathetic showing in front of goal. Cavani was lackluster. He got a header on target but was offside anyways and he went diving for a penalty. Word of advice: Sometimes actually trying to get the ball on target is better than looking for a penalty. Anyways it is most definitely going to be the last WC for Suarez and Cavani which I think should mean a change of system hopefully and a bigger focus on Nunez up top and having more than 2 in the middle of the park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;ghana&#34;&gt;Ghana&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../gha_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;gha_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;uruguay&#34;&gt;Uruguay&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../uru_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;uru_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dreamers make it through. Son comes through for his country. Hello from the other side by Cristiano Ronaldo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Korea have done a madness by pushing to the Round of 16 by beating Portugal. Son has finally delivered when they needed him most. It was a whole set of rotations from Portugal barring a few like Pepe, D.Costa and Ronaldo. The lead came via Ricardo Horta from a Dalot cross(He got in so easily and maybe the Cancelo and Dalot combination I mentioned is probably the way to go for Portugal). The lead didn&amp;rsquo;t last long from 5 minutes as Korea managed to get back into it with a helping hand from none other than Cristiano Ronaldo who made a scuffed clearance which fell perfectly for the defender to score the equalizer(That&amp;rsquo;s what I meant when I said Hello from the other side). Apart from a few chances for Ronaldo there was not anything much that happened. So as it stands Korea are not going through. But the sub of Hwang Hee Chan changed it and made a huge difference. The corner was botched by Portugal and the counter was on and it was led by Son who was quickly closed down but he managed to find Hwang by nutmegging Dalot 😑 and he kept his composure to finish it and Korea were going through on goals scored(That&amp;rsquo;s why 0-0&amp;rsquo;s can bite you). Sadly the other game was behind by around 5 minutes 😅 so Korea had to wait till the Uruguay game was done to know for certain and sure enough they had done it. Later on, &amp;ldquo;Dreamers&amp;rdquo; which was the so-called &amp;ldquo;official&amp;rdquo; WC track by Jung Kook from BTS was blasted in the stadium which was nice to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;south-korea&#34;&gt;South Korea&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../kor_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;kor_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;portugal&#34;&gt;Portugal&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../por_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;por.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-h-table&#34;&gt;Group H table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../5ce2db175fba4014bc6041a949f122bb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;5ce2db175fba4014bc6041a949f122bb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-g&#34;&gt;Group G&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;serbia-v-switzerland-and-cameroon-v-brazil&#34;&gt;Serbia v Switzerland and Cameroon v Brazil&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../0a13fb4437408da1721020c1dfe3710e.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;0a13fb4437408da1721020c1dfe3710e.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fa9bd47c4a6fe494c23ddf4d117328dc.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fa9bd47c4a6fe494c23ddf4d117328dc.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One interesting game with a record matched. One upset but at the expense of a red card 😅. These results now mean that Brazil and Switzerland are going through and will face South Korea and Portugal respectively. Let&amp;rsquo;s dissect both matches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-3&#34;&gt;Match 3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 goals and it was a Swiss win. Let&amp;rsquo;s break it down now. Switzerland were attacking from the get-go. No, literally their first chance came after 25 seconds but was saved twice by GK Milinkovic-Savic. The lead eventually came to the Swiss and it was scored by none other than Big Shaq. A powerful shot after Sow waited and set him up with the pass. Now Shaqiri has joined an elite club that only had Cristiano Ronaldo thus far by scoring in 5 consecutive tournaments and has scored in his 3rd World Cup. The only other players to do it are Messi and Ronaldo. Shaq loves playing in international tournaments. Serbia found an equalizer from Mitrovic who managed to score a pinpoint header from the cross by Tadic. Next Vlahovic(who didn&amp;rsquo;t even get a look in so far) managed to score after a bad touch from the defender. Next was Embolo who managed to score from close range after a great Widmer cross. The winner came from Freuler after a great set of passes including a backheel assist from Vargas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;serbia&#34;&gt;Serbia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ser_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ser_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;switzerland&#34;&gt;Switzerland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../swi_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;swi_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-4&#34;&gt;Match 4&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just 1 goal in it and Cameroon started both Choupo-Moting and Aboubakar and it paid off with Brazil doing hefty rotations. Sadly the main news apart from the winner from Aboubakar was the injuries sustained by Alex Telles and Gabriel Jesus which is difficult news only in defense as Brazil&amp;rsquo;s attack is stacked. This combined with Neymar&amp;rsquo;s rush to fitness after his ankle injury means Brazil is in a tough spot overall. Aboubakar&amp;rsquo;s finish was perfect. The cross was put in and he headed it in perfectly. Ederson was rooted to the spot. Sadly he was on a yellow card and took his shirt off to celebrate so he got the second yellow and got a red card. The way it was given though was funny. It is quite possibly the friendliest way to give a red card 😂.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../redditsave.com_9iw0vxjvkk3a1.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;redditsave.com_9iw0vxjvkk3a1.gif&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cameroon&#34;&gt;Cameroon&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cam_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cam_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;brazil&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bra_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bra_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-g-table&#34;&gt;Group G table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../083855a3f1bc9d532da8cc058a8c1289.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;083855a3f1bc9d532da8cc058a8c1289.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-knockout-bracket&#34;&gt;THE KNOCKOUT BRACKET&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../b4e2754a9b06b05696773878a503db9a.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;b4e2754a9b06b05696773878a503db9a.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 12</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-12&#34;&gt;Day 12&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;final-matchday-in-groups-e-and-f&#34;&gt;Final Matchday in Groups E and F&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-f&#34;&gt;Group F&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;canada-v-morocco-and-croatia-v-belgium&#34;&gt;Canada v Morocco and Croatia v Belgium&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../914774bfa8354d075cbc76a98331b760.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;914774bfa8354d075cbc76a98331b760.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../8d9c2ae7af7314e6c2bd38c7d45a06cb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;8d9c2ae7af7314e6c2bd38c7d45a06cb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One pretty alright game and one COMPLETE DUD from one of the teams in the other game. I thought Morocco will be able to give a great game to the other teams but never a group topper 😅. It is an amazing show from the African nations. Maybe we could see more teams from AFCON because it is coming up. Don&amp;rsquo;t sleep on them that&amp;rsquo;s all. The second game does not deserve the time here because it was YET ANOTHER 0-0.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Canada gave it everything but Morocco was just on another level. Bono was back after going off at the start of the last game because of a bout of dizziness. The first came after just 4 minutes with a crazy mistake from the Canada GK. The ball comes through and the keeper rushes forward and takes the biggest of touches and it comes straight to Ziyech who has an easy target to aim at now that the keeper did himself in with that horror touch. CAN SOMEONE CHECK THE BANK ACCOUNT OF THE KEEPER FOR A BIG STACK THAT SHOULD HAVE COME IN? 💰️.  Anyways, the next goal was by En Nesyri who finally has a goal in the World Cup. I really thought he could do business for Morocco but hey better late than never and they are in the knockouts as group toppers so amazing work. Morocco got another but it was ruled out for offside and everyone except En Nesyri knew that 🤣&amp;hellip;.for a while. Canada pulled one back when a cross that came in was deflected off Aguerd for what was the first own goal in this tournament so far. Later on, it was just damage control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;canada&#34;&gt;Canada&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../can_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;can_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;morocco&#34;&gt;Morocco&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mor_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mor_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll just keep it brief for Croatia. Gvardiol is a different-level beast. No wonder Chelsea want him. He has been a solid rock at just 20. Apart from that nothing major apart from a few chances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;belgium-belgium-belgium&#34;&gt;Belgium Belgium Belgium&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The major team I wanna bash on which is what I was waiting for because for starters I don&amp;rsquo;t know how this team of pathetic potato sacks is still number 2 in the world. They have been knocked out and deservedly so. No bad luck of any sort. They were just bad. Everyone does not have the right mentality including even Kevin De Bruyne. Calling out your own national team as too old to the press. I get they&amp;rsquo;re not your billion-dollar Man City team but why you gotta make that public I have no clue. Apart from that, I thought their squad selection was alright but as always the fault starts at the very top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;roberto-martinez&#34;&gt;Roberto Martinez&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../a8dc2c26841e7752c2b7ff092f6997eb.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;a8dc2c26841e7752c2b7ff092f6997eb.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Freshly unemployed after this idiotic campaign(Glory Hallelujah 🙌), this Belgian Baldi is downright arrogant and stubborn to the point where Gareth Southgate actually looks better and you know how much I hate Southgate. This guy you see loves picking absolute 🐌s in his lineup who are in various retirement leagues. Vertonghen and Alderweireld are in the Belgian league. No wonder he keeps picking them. You hardly have to move countries to check others out. You have Faes who has been solid for Leicester so far and he&amp;rsquo;s rotting on the bench. Tielemans is a top-quality player and has had a great season as well. But Monsieur Martinez is like &amp;ldquo;Oh i dOn&amp;rsquo;t wAnNa pIcK HiM BeCaUsE He iS NoT A sNaIl&amp;rdquo; and instead the fool picks Witsel and Dendoncker for this game who are as fast as a damn 18-wheeler without the 18 wheels. Don&amp;rsquo;t even get me started on the damn attack. Barring De Bruyne who while he has the quality DOES NOT have the mentality of a champion and is so used to Man City&amp;rsquo;s oil money squad, the others are a joke. Mertens plays in a Turkish retirement league. Hazard does not have the pace and agility of 4 or 5 years ago. You do not trust the likes of De Ketelaere(Plays for Serie A champions AC Milan) or even Doku who has amazing agility and pace. You still trust Lukaku who was the reason you didn&amp;rsquo;t even get a goal from this game. No focus on youth and trusting snails. Are you seriously picking snails because they&amp;rsquo;re the only ones who can keep your unemployed head shiny or what? I seriously don&amp;rsquo;t get your lineups at all. You got lucky with Canada because you sat back and managed to catch them out. Against the rest, you are just as clueless as they come. Castagne is great going forward and where does he sit: IN THE CENTER OF DEFENSE WITH THE OTHER 2 SNAILS. God this man just infuriates me. This so-called &amp;ldquo;golden generation&amp;rdquo; has been thoroughly ruined by this knockoff Sivaji and they are indeed &amp;ldquo;too old&amp;rdquo; De Bruyne to win anything unless your damn coach changes up his selection because he had 0 future-proofing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;croatia&#34;&gt;Croatia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../cro_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;cro_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;belgium&#34;&gt;Belgium&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../bel_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;bel_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-f-table&#34;&gt;Group F table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f8af400b00c74670645ecbbb6e6c2f9e.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f8af400b00c74670645ecbbb6e6c2f9e.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;to-roberto-martinez-and-the-belgium-national-team&#34;&gt;To Roberto Martinez and the Belgium National Team&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/TxOxbS3NTcjgTMIEFd/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;Joe&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-e&#34;&gt;Group E&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;costa-rica-v-germany-and-japan-v-spain&#34;&gt;Costa Rica v Germany and Japan v Spain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../1c465834f7176647224253a47f733417.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;1c465834f7176647224253a47f733417.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../5470ea06aa6efb87bd41a3de0303c165.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;5470ea06aa6efb87bd41a3de0303c165.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The slightest of margins. The country with the highest xG(Expected goals) out and Spain gets beaten by a side who had only 14% possession 😳. With these results, Japan actually goes through as the group toppers and Spain survives to go second. This means the fixtures are: Spain v Morocco and Japan v Croatia. A historic moment also happened as an all-female refereeing team took charge of the game between Germany and Costa Rica in the men&amp;rsquo;s World Cup. A massive massive achievement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;since-so-much-happened-in-this-group-i-will-be-combining-both-matches-together-to-show-how-crazy-the-table-moved-in-this-final-matchday&#34;&gt;Since so much happened in this group I will be combining both matches together to show how crazy the table moved in this final matchday&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;first-half&#34;&gt;First Half&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10&#39; - Raum with a great cross for Gnabry who heads it home. Germany at this point still isn&amp;rsquo;t getting out of the group because it is still 0-0 in the other game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11&#39; - Great cross from Azpilicueta for Morata who managed to finish with a bullet header. Man has only started one game and has the same goals as Gakpo and Mbappe 😅. Now, Spain and Germany are going through at 1 and 2 respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After 1 half, Spain and Germany are going through from the standings with Spain on 7 points and Germany on 4 points and Japan on 3 points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;second-half&#34;&gt;Second half&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;48&#39; - Doan manages to pull Japan level after Spain makes a huge hash of playing out from the back. His goal was a bullet outside the box. Hard true and Simon is caught out. Game on. Now it is Spain on just 5 points and Japan are on 4(GD - 0) and Germany stay on 4(GD - 0) so second place is
going to be chosen by the number of yellows and all that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;51&#39; - Controversial moment here as Tanaka has scored but the goal is ruled out. Doan first makes a great run and manages to drill the ball in and Mitoma actually hit the ball back in for Tanaka after it ran out of play apparently here. VAR is checking it&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;and it is a goal. JAPAN LEAD SPAIN through Tanaka. Maybe this moment could be talked about for a long time but Japan don&amp;rsquo;t care they are celebrating like crazy. Now Japan are going through as group toppers and Spain are now on 4 points but ahead of Germany on the same points by GD and if Spain level it Germany could squeak through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;58&#39; - Bad defending from Germany and Costa Rica have thrown a spanner in the works by equalising now from Tejeda after Neuer makes a meal out of a cross yet again and as usual Germany are second best in getting to the rebound and its 1-1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;70&#39; - It is getting worse for Germany. After missing a slew of chances to go ahead. Costa Rica has managed to score again and I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I am saying this but JAPAN and COSTA RICA are poised to go through now because they both are on 6 points but Japan are ahead on GD. It was a scramble from the free kick and it looks like the final touch came from Neuer(off his right foot to be precise) so it will be classed as an own goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;73&#39; - Sane puts the ball in but it was cleared out till Kimmich managed to head to Fullkrug who managed to sneak Havertz in who manages to calmly slot it past Navas. So now Spain is now ahead of Costa Rica on goal difference(Funnily enough that 7-0 win for Spain keeping them alive 😅)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;85&#39; - Havertz puts Germany ahead and it was coming after a load of chances including a big chance from point blank range which was saved well by Navas. Gnabry with a peach of a cross to find him. Germany is third now. Unless Spain draws level, Germany ain&amp;rsquo;t going through and it still is 2-1 to Japan now&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;89&#39; - Fullkrug makes it 4 and it is the 3 points for Germany but with Spain still unable to find a way to equalize it seems to be all for nothing. A great pass from Kimmich again and Sane sets it up on a plate for Fullkrug who easily scores it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FT - And breathe 😱. With the results the table looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../47d7ff7e8174fcac918cd18f8dc3375f.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;47d7ff7e8174fcac918cd18f8dc3375f.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GD bailed Spain out. If they leveled against Japan, Germany would have gone through. A former Barcelona manager knocks out a former Bayern manager. You love to see it 😆&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lineups&#34;&gt;Lineups&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;costa-rica&#34;&gt;Costa Rica&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../crica_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;crica_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;germany&#34;&gt;Germany&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ger_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ger_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;japan&#34;&gt;Japan&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../jap_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;jap_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spain&#34;&gt;Spain&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../spa_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;spa_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/world-cup-2022/posts/day_11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-11&#34;&gt;Day 11&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;final-matchday-in-groups-c-and-d&#34;&gt;Final Matchday in Groups C and D&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-d&#34;&gt;Group D&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;australia-v-denmark-and-tunisia-v-france&#34;&gt;Australia v Denmark and Tunisia v France&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f3ecd40cbbdba9ad59addc7a80dd542c.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f3ecd40cbbdba9ad59addc7a80dd542c.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../c1e9bb4869e40c388891d714f48a2de7.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;c1e9bb4869e40c388891d714f48a2de7.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 surprise results but only one of them mattered and that was Australia v Denmark. I never realized how bad they were and the fact that Australia managed to get into the Round of 16. Denmark lost twice and never won once. I never realized how bad they look without a proper ST like Poulsen. At least Eriksen is getting a longer rest before the next Man United game. Denmark better use a better ST than the ones they used because they were shambolic. Tunisia got an amazing result but France was resting all their key players and was not in the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-1&#34;&gt;Match 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first time Australia has qualified for the Round of 16 since 2006. It is an absolutely amazing achievement and they deserve it with how lackluster Denmark was. Leckie scored the lone goal of the game after a great counter-attack and he managed to get past 2 defenders and slotted the ball really well past Schmeichel. Apart from that, I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything left to say apart from the fact of how SHAMBOLIC Denmark is in attack. The likes of Skov Olsen, Cornelius, Braithwaite and so on are so lackluster in their finishing. They are creating so many chances thanks to Eriksen and they are just letting him down. Eriksen went through hell and back for you lot and this is how you repay him? Just pathetic is all I can say about Denmark&amp;rsquo;s finishing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;australia&#34;&gt;Australia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../aus_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;aus_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;denmark&#34;&gt;Denmark&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../den_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;den_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-2&#34;&gt;Match 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TUNISIA STUNS THE WORLD CHAMPIONS. On a serious level though France was taking it easy and it showed from the get-go. Tunisia meant business from the start and really dominated France who rested quite literally everybody. The goal came from the legend of Tunisia Wahbi Khazri who managed to make his mark in this tournament. As someone who knows only 2 players in this Tunisia side and one of them hardly plays it was nice seeing him score. The goal itself was not a bad one. Just casually dribbling past many people and beating Varane with a quick shift and just tapping it past Mandanda. You know the one. France thought they came back via Griezmann who was brought on but it was ruled out for offside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tunisia&#34;&gt;Tunisia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../tun_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;tun_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;france&#34;&gt;France&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../fra_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;fra_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-d-table&#34;&gt;Group D table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../43e46c4073af781d1b60ef5a4d36aece.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;43e46c4073af781d1b60ef5a4d36aece.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I AM ASHAMED OF YOU DENMARK. ASHAMED I SAY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-c&#34;&gt;Group C&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;poland-v-argentina-and-saudi-arabia-v-mexico&#34;&gt;Poland v Argentina and Saudi Arabia v Mexico&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../deae745c61f443e0cd5907146479c0dd.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;deae745c61f443e0cd5907146479c0dd.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../f14962e669e221017340d0bfeeac02e7.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;f14962e669e221017340d0bfeeac02e7.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first game was dominated by Argentina so that was a no-brainer but the second game decided so much. Mexico and Poland&amp;rsquo;s fate were in the balance for the second game and Mexico were knocked out via a goal from Saudi Arabia which meant they went out on goal difference. They were going home anyways because of more yellow cards if that goal had not been scored. They just switched off defensively and let in a goal by Saudi. This now means Poland and Argentina are through and the Round of 16 matches are France v Poland and Argentina v Australia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-3&#34;&gt;Match 3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From River Plate to the World Cup. An unwanted Messi record and Lewandowski survives&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Really dominant from Argentina. Poland tried to sit back deep and hold them but they found the gaps really well and managed to constantly get shots away. The first chance was a penalty which I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest was very soft because the keeper when saving hit Messi&amp;rsquo;s face it really wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big hit at all but it was given anyways(The keeper said he had a bet with Messi that a penalty will not be given by VAR which was just brushed off by Messi when it actually was given 😅) and Messi wound up having his penalty saved and with that, he has become the first player to have 2 penalties saved in the World Cup. Argentina didn&amp;rsquo;t stay down for long as they had a blistering start to the second half with a great cross by Molina bundled in by Mac Allister(from bloody Brighton 😂). The second was scored by Alvarez with a beautifully curled effort past the keeper. The first sentence was written because both Enzo Fernandez and Alvarez had started and they were winning things with River Plate in Argentina and are now on the big stage of the World Cup playing alongside Messi. Lewandowski is not too fussed about the result after seeing what happened in the other game&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;poland&#34;&gt;Poland&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../pol_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;pol_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;argentina&#34;&gt;Argentina&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../arg_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;arg_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;match-4&#34;&gt;Match 4&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;saudi-arabia&#34;&gt;Saudi Arabia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../ksa_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;ksa_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mexico&#34;&gt;Mexico&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../mex_3.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;mex_3.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chavez becomes this World Cup&amp;rsquo;s Forlan. The minimum margins that didn&amp;rsquo;t matter. Mexican complacency and arrogance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🎵Let me sing a Kutty Story, pay attention, listen to me 🎵
There was a ball all the way back in 2010 known as the Jabulani and it was notorious and had a load of complaints from goalkeepers for being highly unpredictable but it was actually mastered by one person alone and that person was&amp;hellip;.Diego Forlan. He was called the best player of the tournament and scored 5 goals including a cracking free kick against Ghana(Had an infamous situationnnnnn as well 👀). And people around him said he trained relentlessly to get used to the ball and he used it well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So with that in mind, it seems like Chavez from Mexico seems to have a handle on this World Cup&amp;rsquo;s ball which is lighter and is actually discouraging players to take shots from range because a little power could be enough to send the ball flying into Row Z. Chavez had 2 freekicks and both were on target and one of em was a goal which was just beautifully struck. Just slightly below the absolute top corner but amazing nonetheless. The second was for the left corner but it was saved well. The first goal was a simple flick from a corner bundled in by Martin who was alert. Technically with this scoreline, they had a chance to go through but they had more yellow cards so which meant Poland will go through so they pushed really hard for a third and got one but were ruled out for offside by VAR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mexico got complacent and was weak towards the end of added time and Saudi had a chance and took it. With the lack of defenders, he easily got past and slotted it home. This meant with Poland&amp;rsquo;s loss Mexico was eliminated on goal difference anyways. And now we say goodbye to a World Cup legend: Memo Ochoa, the goalkeeper for the big stage and the big stage alone&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../2acec77cffdd46dd46706adbb1642e5f.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;2acec77cffdd46dd46706adbb1642e5f.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;https://media.giphy.com/media/rHR8qP1mC5V3G/giphy.gif&#34;
        alt=&#34;Salute&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;gracias-por-los-recuerdos&#34;&gt;Gracias por los recuerdos&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;group-c-table&#34;&gt;Group C table&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img  src=&#34;../group_c_table.png&#34;
        alt=&#34;group_c_table.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;remember-when-you-were-at-the-top-of-the-group-at-one-point-saudi-arabia-funny-how-life-has-a-way-of-hitting-back-&#34;&gt;Remember when you were at the top of the group at one point Saudi Arabia? Funny how life has a way of hitting back 😂&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>